My heart
So full
So ready to give to you
And when you ask
I give without a second glance 'cause
I want you
To have to
Want for nothing my~ friends
And when they say
That they want more, I obey~
Want for nothing my~ friends
But you didn't have to take~ it all~~~
But you wanted every piece~ of me~~
I was willing to give you more
And you took ungratefully
But I guess that's the price I pay
For being generosi~ty~~~
I want to
Go back to
When I could give you all you needed
I could give you all you needed
But now I'm beat down
I'm sprawling
I can't walk
I'm crawling
Could I never give you all you wanted~~?
But you didn't have to take~ it all~~~
But you wanted every piece~ of me~~
I was willing to give you more
And you took ungratefully
But I guess that's the price I~ pay
For being generosi~ty~~~
Generosi~ty
But you didn't have to take it all~, yeah~
But you wanted every piece of me~~, yeah~!
I was willing to give you more
And you took ungratefully
But I guess that's the price I~ pay
For being generosi~ty~~~~
For being generosity~~~!