I did some things that I regret
Oh-oh-oh, and it's been hurting like hell in my hands
I wore my flaws upon my sleeve
Oh-oh-oh, I wanna bury my shell in the-e-e-e-e sa-and
So I part with my ways
Let 'em wash with the waves
I've been cautious to~ not let my gospel decay
Let tomorrow lead the fray
'Cause my past's not today
'Cause my past's not today~
Watch me turn my back and let the sunset shimmer~, yea-a-ah
On the ocean sho-ore, I feel the sunlight glimme-e-e-e-er
I've begun my path, headed for something bigger~, oh~ ye-a-ah
It's time to let it shine~ and make the magic flicker
Oh-oh oh
Time to lay my sins to rest
Oh-oh-oh, and let the fires in hell burn my tan
I'll shed my skin with past beli-ie-e-efs
Oh-oh-oh, and then I'll rise up and try this a-a-a-a-aga-ain
So I part with my ways
Let 'em wash with the waves
I've been cautious to not let my gospel decay
Let tomorrow lead the fray
'Cause my past's not today
Reawakened thro-ough ages of love, war, and fate
Sunset shims from daylight
Starlight glims through the night
Twilight sparkles thro-ough darkness, and everything's alright
Till tomorrow comes, I pray
That my past is not today
'Cause my past's not today
Oh-oh oh
Watch me turn my back and let the sunset shimmer~, yea-a-ah
On the ocean sho-ore, I feel the sunlight glimme-e-e-e-er
I've begun my path, headed for something bigger ~, oh yeah~, oh!
It's time to let it shi-i-ine and make the magic flicker