A beautiful heart, so strong and true
A gentle to-ouch that I always tu-urn to
Yeah, she helps me pu-ull through
These walls that I built up around
Crumble do-own with that wondro-ous sound
This timid voice that I've fo-ound
Her head upon my shoulde-er...
As she whispers in my ear...
The hurt we keep inside, it burns
And when we never speak, we learn
Our silence has more power than we realize
But when we let it out, and cry
And through tears we speak our minds
And find the words that ring true to our he-eart
Every da-ay becomes better than the last
Her words, so soft, a pleasant plea
She voiced those thoughts that lived inside o-of me
Let my feelings flow free
I face my pain by letting go
Put trust in fate and now I always ha-ave hope
I no longer need to be alo-one
Cuz her head's upon my shoulde-er...
As she whispers in my e-e-ear...
The hurt we keep inside, it burns
And when we never speak, we learn
Our silence has more power than we realize
But when we let it out, and cry
And through tears we speak our minds
And find the words that ring true to our he-eart
Every da-ay becomes better than the last
A-and to-o this day
I shall remember
So-o fa-ar away
A time I never will let go
A-and to-o this day
I thought I should break
Out of my shell
Thank yo-ou my beautiful filly
For sho-owing me-e the-e way
Yo-our wo-ords will always be with me
Thank yo-ou my de-ear
Fluttershy!