Heads high, ponies!
Marching proud!
All together now, every one of you!
Nopony left behind!
Life is so grand in our town
We're always filled with cheer
We never have to look around
To know that we're all here
In our town, in our town
We don't have to wait
To find out that our destiny
Is just to emulate
Let's see those big, happy smiles
Life is a smile in our town
Our Cutie Marks the same
Because we do not separate
Ourselves by more than name
In our town, in our town
We dare not compete
Winning only breeds the worst
Ego-filled conceit
You see, now everypony wins
Life is a joy in our town
We're all equal here
No-one is superior
And no-one shakes in fear
In our town, in our town
We work as a team
You can't have a nightmare
If you never dream
Other ponies argue
Do you ever wonder why?
When you think your talent's special
You don't see eye to eye
There's just too many differences
That lead to disarray
But when you learn to act as one
It's like a holiday
In our town, in our town
We don't complicate
When you learn to simplify
Life is oh so great
Join in our utopia
Come out of the dark
Banded by equality
By our Cutie mark