Maybe I'm too young
To really understand or
Maybe I'm too old to let it go
Maybe I'm too jaded
Never appreciated
The little things you a-already know
I can see the wonder
Shining in your face
But it's not in me anymore
With a tiny glance
I get a second chance
I remember what I was searching for
When I look i-in your eyes
I can see what I could be
When I hear you-ur words
I hear the sou-und of harmony-y
And I want to lea-arn from you
The wisdo-om in your hea-art
And no matter where we go-o
We will never be apa-a-a-art
Little laughs, little smiles
Bring me back a thousand miles
To a place a lifeti-ime away
To a time when I was free
To be whatever I could be
To say whatever I wanted to-o say
I think I lost it
Somewhere along the-e line
But I can find it once mo-o-ore
You give me one mo-ore glance,
And I get another second chance
I remember what I was searching for
When I look i-in your eyes
I can see-e what I used to-o be
When I hear you-ur words
I remember harmony-y
And I want to lea-arn from you
All the-e wisdom in your heart
And no matter where we go-o
We will never be apa-art
I miss your eyes
And the-e way we used to be
I can't hea-ar your words,
But I remember harmony-y
And I sti-ill will learn from you-u
And all the wisdo-om in your heart
And no matter ho-ow you gro-ow
We will never really be-e apart
Never really be-e apart