Hay hmmm~ yeah~ yeah~~ yeah~ hah
The way you trot with your stride
That lovely hair those beautiful~ eyes~
It doesn't take a fool~ to reali~ze
That I've fallen for your clever dis~guise~
Oh~~ Sweetiebelle~~ yeah
What will it take for me~ to get to you
Oh~~ Sweetiebelle~~yeah
My heart's forever true
What will it take for me
to plant that seed of love deep inside your mind
And steal~ your breath away from you
Sugarcube you're the apple of my eye~
Another sharp thorn in my soft side
'Cause just the thought of you is enough to drive me crazy
And send me singing through~~ the night
Oh~ Sweetiebelle yeah
will it take for me to get to you
My heart's forever true
What will it take for me
to plant that seed of love deep inside your mind
And steal~ your breath away from you
Now I know that I'm deeply in love and that may sound insane
But girl without you in my life
I could never be the same
And if you are my Rarity
then I am your Spike
So give me just one chance to show that I can love and treat you right
Na na duh duh duhnuh nuhnuh huh
be bah nah bah bah bah bah bah bah bah ho ho ho
oh na na na na na~
Oh~ Sweetiebelle yeah
will it take for me to get to you
My heart's forever true
What will it take for me
to plant that seed of love deep inside your mind
And steal~ your breath away from you~~
Ah~~~~~
Ah~~~~~~~
Ah~~na na na na na na na na