As the night~sky changes
And the world goes to sleep~
The moon shines above them
Which secrets will it keep?
And one sleepy pony
Looks up to the sky~
While she gets lonely
She begins~ to wonder~ why
Delicate as a flower
And raised~ to bloom~
She had to struggle
Sadness and~ gloom
To make ponies care
Fighting her~ despair~
She would carry on
Proving them they are~ wrong
But just like a~ rose she'd grow
And maybe one day~ will show
That thorns of sorrow
Will become the true hor~ror
Rose Luck, isn't she lucky?
Raising flo~wers, showing beau~ty
Though behind the glory~ lies
Her horrors, fears and~ freights
This pony shared all
With the ones she cared for
But nopony gave her~ her due~~~~
And she would go~ on
Without anyone
To help her~ get~ through~~~~
Fulfilling her destiny
Because~ she will~ be
Once again~
The lucky one~
This rose shall be happy
And bloom~ in its beau~ty
Which she was~
All along~
But just like a~ rose she'd grow
And maybe one day~ will show~
That thorns of sorrow
Will become the true hor~ror
Rose Luck, isn't she lucky?
Raising flo~wers, showing beau~ty
Though behind the glory~ lies
Her horrors, fears and~ freights
Rose Luck, oh Rose Luck
Don't~ forget~
You are worth~ it~
Do not fret
Nor should you regret
One day a pony
Will make~ you smile~
And show you tru~ly
You are worth~~while