Sitting here with my head in my hands
Ideas that come and go
Sketching my heart out, nothing will turn out
Everything seems so-so-o
I've been here before, and I know that I can
Do it if I try-y
But why-y, oh why-y
Do you stumble before yo-u fly?
My wheels keep turnin'
My fire's still burnin'
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
How to get to the other side
It's a game of waitin'
Anticipatin'
But I keep creatin'
So I can get to the other
Get to the other si-ide
He-y!
So I can get to the other
Get to the other
Keep on believin'
I'll be achievin'
The harder that I go-o
Don't really know how
I won't give up now
Until I steal the sho-o-ow
With time, it gets better
I'll be a trendsetter
Doin' it my own wa-ay
He-y, hey he-y
Won't stop 'til I seize the-e day
My wheels keep turnin'
My fire's still burnin'
'Cause right now I'm learnin'
How to get to the other side
It's a game of waitin'
Anticipatin'
But I keep creatin'
So I can get to the other
Get to the othe-er si-ide
Get to the other si-ide
He-y!
So I can get to the other
Get to the other si-ide