Haven't we all had enough of Diamond Tiara?
Do we really need a big statue of her?
Especially where our playground equipment should be?
A vote for Pip is a vote for the playground
It's time to make a change
This is our chance
Don't be afraid to do what's right
He's it, vote for Pip!
We got an opportunity
To have fun again
A vote for Pip and you can join the fight
It's time for a new leader
It's time to make a change
We're here to fight for what we believe
Vote for Pip!
It's finally time we beat her
And play a better game
'Cause when we vote together
There's nothing that we can't achieve
We'll let the voting decide
C'mon now ponies, don't listen to her!
You've gotta vote for change
It's time for a new leader
End all the tyranny
Vote now and we can beat her
It's now another day
And we believe in what's right
Vote for Pip! Vote for Pip!
Our victory is in sight
GASP!
Well, if that's how you treat your best friend
Then I choose Pipsqueak!
Stand strong and don't be afraid
Let's free ourselves from the past
He's it! Vote for Pip!
We'll let honor win out
Against the tyranny
And make a change that will last
Vote for Pip!
It's time for a new leader
It's time to make a change
We're here to fight for what we believe
Vote for Pip!
It's finally time we beat her
And play a better game
'Cause when we vote together
There's nothing that we can't achieve
Vote for Pip!