A vote for Diamond Tiara is a vote
For more Diamond Tiara
I don't believe what I am hearing
I'm the only one you should be cheering
Pipsqueak, try Pips-weak, don't you think?
But a diamond is perfection
It's natural selection
So your vote better be for me
Not the weakest link
Everypony has their little secrets
I know you do
A vote for me will help you keep them safe
Like your creepy super strength
Or your mane extension
A little thing I won't mention
Or those freakish large teeth in your face
Stop!
Everypony who hasn't voted, listen up!
Pip makes promises he can't keep
But I can do more
You could really use a new book bag
'Cause I'll make things happen
That none of you here can afford
To do, like ever
Wouldn't you like a little something sweet?
Here's a parasol to hide you from the heat
Who says tha-at I can't be nice?
But first there's one thing
An itsy-bitsy little string
And voting for me is the price
I've a tiny suggestion
That you should be aware
You could probably win this election
If you showed them all you rea…
I don't recall asking you to speak!