At sunrise, the clouds hover high
The shadow I cast fades away
The rain falls like tears from the sky
My conscience is clear in this way
If you know me
It's no matter if I'm there for you
If you wish me
I will take the time to see it through
Don't deny it
There is hope, don't stop, believe in me
Close your eyes and
Fall away 'cause I'll show you my loyalty
As souls go-o, the sun won't live on
The stars will someday turn to dust
Yet afte-er our loved ones are gone
There still shall be someone to trust
If you know me
It's no matter if I'm there for you
If you wish me
I will take the time to see it through
Don't deny it
There is hope, don't stop, believe in me
Close your eyes and
Fall away 'cause I'll show you my loyalty
See
What everything
Means to me
And everything
That can be
Within our hearts
Just Believe
And I will be
By your side
If you know me
It's no matter if I'm there for you
If you wish me
I will take the time to see it through
Don't deny it
There is hope, don't stop, believe in me
Close your eyes and
Fall away 'cause I'll show you my loyalty