We're gonna read you the books
And sharpen our fishing hooks
To make an earth pony o-out of you
Because there's evil out there
They'll cut you up if you dare
So keep away from the great big blue
Because they come in the dark
They'll feed your guts to a shark
'Cause there's nopony who's out of their reach
They're gonna climb up your stairs
And put seaweed in your hair
Don't let me catch you swimming at the-e beach
They say all
Hippogriffs scare the living shit outta me
Steal us away to eat you under the sea
You wanna survive, better not go for a dive
'Cause they might eat you alive, but no-ot me
Yo-ou ma-ares a-and colts in the back
With cutie marks on your flank
Tell me do you ever ta-ake a dip
'Cause if you're down there too long
And feel like something is wrong
You better have a harpoon on your hip
They say all
Hippogriffs scare the living shit outta me
Steal us away to eat you under the sea
You wanna survive, better not go for a dive
'Cause they might eat you alive, but no-ot me
Whoa yeah
They say all
Hippogriffs scare the living shit outta me
Steal us away to eat you under the sea
You wanna survive, better not go for a dive
'Cause they might eat you alive, but no-ot me
Everypony now
Hippogriffs scare the living shit outta me
Steal us away to eat you under the sea
You wanna survive, better not go for a dive
'Cause they might eat you alive, but no-ot me
(incoherent screaming from getting eaten)
Hippogriffs scare the living shit outta me
Steal us away to eat you under the sea
You wanna survive, better not go for a dive
'Cause they might eat you alive, but no-ot me