Ponies' voices fill the night
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
Happy hearts so full and bright
Oh, what a sight
Look at the light
All for tonight
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
Clouds arranged so they're just so
Gonna make some awesome snow
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
The chill wind blows
Making a show
Snowflakes aglow
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
A day that's filled with songs to sing
Ding-dong, ding-dong-ding
Cakes and pastries we shall bring
So busy making merry
Windigos should all be wary
As our mighty voices carry
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
Decorations we shall make
Perfection you just cannot fake
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
Not one mistake
Don't let that break
Oh, goodness' sake!
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once...
Happy, happy Hearth's Warming Eve
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again!
Hearth's Warming Eve is filled with presents
Some take you by surprise
A story shared by your good friends
That makes your spirits ri-i-ise
Sometimes you just let go of the past
Enjoy the present while it lasts
And really it's not that mu-uch to-o ask
With good friends by your side
Now it's time to celebrate
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again
All together, feeling great
Can't hardly wait
We'll party 'til late
Our favorite date
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once...
Happy Hearth's Warming Eve
Hearth's Warming Eve is here once again!