It has been a thousand years
Since I have had someone
To hold me close and give me hope
But I fear those nights are gone
My subjects tend to fear me
Not see me as I am
I've tried so hard to be myself
But they don't understand
I have lived a thousand years
In loneliness and pain
Watching friends be born to die
While knowing I'll remain
I long to have another
In whom I can confide
My heart is far too heavy
From all my past goodbyes
But we know that one day we will overcome
For we know that we are capable of love
Like the stars that shine into the night
I'll always dare~ to dream
Like the sun that shines above~ us
Things are brighter than~ they seem
There is no light without the dark
No dark without~ the light~
Time cannot deny a day
Our hearts are free from strife
We know that one day we will overcome
For we know that we are capable of love
Times are always changing
And I know that I'm behind
My subjects know my power
But not my troubled mind
My romance is outdated
I'd just embarrass myself
They come to me with questions
Concerned with someone else
But still I find a hope in knowing
This is not the norm
Life and love both come and go
We battled through the storm
One day we'll dine on happiness
We share with those we love
Our worries and our struggles
Will melt away because
We know that one day we will overcome
For we know that we are capable of love
We hope that out there someone's thinking of
The princesses that rule~ Equestria