All of the city
Turns to black~
And fades away~
Oh, dreams~ of the crystal heart~
Turn into night~mares as it breaks apart~
Dark~ness has overtaken
An ancient e~vil has been awa~kened~
They all expec~ted me~ to sa~ve them
Who could have guessed~ I would~ have failed~
After where~ we've been
Time and time~ again
We fall
We let them down and now we're captive just as well~
Tried so hard, but in the end~
Lost it all~ anyway~
All of those who trusted us~
Locked and caged
Can't get away~~
Who's to blame now
You're to blame now
Who's to blame
It's you~
Failed to save us
Sombra slaved us
Darkness changed us
Hate deranged us
Who's to blame now
Who's to blame
It's you~
It's you~~
She had a chance to save~ the lives~ of e~veryone
She held it in her hooves and now it's gone~
Who designed the minds~ of kings~ to be so cruel
Who's anger could~ have made this hatred spawn~
Might as well just give myself away~
I'm not the one to save them
Trust in what I could have been
I will not let you down this time~
Sombra's darkness crystalizing
Friendships made are now dividing
Hypnotizing, paralyzing
Harmony destabilizing
Damn myself and give away what's left of me
A sacrifice to save the ones I love so dearly
Hold me as the end grows closer
Chained up to this crystal prison
Weighing on my last decision
Feed me to the entity~ of hate~~