Teardrops fade
Then I saw
You had them in your pocket
And from the first day
I saw through it all
As it could be without your wallet
The snake oil salesmen
These ponies always were
This ain't your home
So I'm showing you the door
Wave goodbye
Now it's time for you to go
Don't come back anytime
Ponyville doesn't need your kind
Give us our bits back
MoneyGrabber
You're not welcome anytime
When you're the ones that robbed us blind
This is your payback
MoneyGrabber
Through all your sweet talk
All I see
Is your smoke and mirrors
Like the time you did the same thing to me
Don't look for trouble
Here's my advice
I don't think twice
For a chance to buck you out the door
One, two, three
One is for the money
Three is for the greed
We just don't need
Oh three
Two
One
Don't come back anytime
Ponyville doesn't need your kind
Give us our bits back
MoneyGrabber
You're not welcome anytime
When you're the ones that robbed us blind
This is your payback
MoneyGrabber