Can't sleep cause I'm in too deep and I'm wide awake
Cold tears for the years they've taken away
Dawn breaks, every muscle aches and it's just begun
And we won't sleep 'till the sun's gone
And the moon takes its place~~~~
But I need to fight to be the best
You gotta train if you want it
Nothing ever changes without it
And I need to fight to be the best
Glory only comes to the winner
I guess I'll have to be better
Better
Bet~ter
Sweat stings, every new step brings an unending pain
Push on like the only pawn in the game
Train hard 'till you're bruised and scared and then train again
Hoping someday the pain will end
Knowing it won't be today~~~~~
But I need to fight to be the best
I gotta train if I want it
Nothing ever changes without it
And I need to fight to be the best
Glory only comes to the winner
And I'm gonna be better
Better
Bet~ter