I had it all worked out
Inside this twisted mind
A little game to play
A travel back i-in time
To seek what I deserve
Revenge that I can serve
But now I messed up
From this path, I ca-an't turn
We are living in a wasteland
Barren worlds of dust and
Nowhere we can hide
Sa-ated, my thirst has aba-ated
This world I've crea-ated
There's no hope to find
In this wasteland of mine
It was my final plan
Stop telling me your lies
It's not my fault
That you can't wi-in, tho-ough you try-y
But now I'm losing too
There's nothing I can do
I sought revenge on you
But now I'm so confu-used
We are living in a wasteland
Barren worlds of dust and
Nowhere we can hide
Sa-ated, my thirst has aba-ated
This world I've crea-ated
There's no hope to find
In this wasteland of mine
I had my heart set on only one thing
Bringing you down for what you broke
But now I see I was messing wi-ith fate
I finally understand there are things that I do-on't know
We are living in a wasteland
Barren worlds of dust and
Nowhere we can hide
Sa-ated, my thirst has aba-ated
This world I've crea-ated
There's no hope to find
In this wasteland of-
We are living in a wasteland
Barren worlds of dust and
Nowhere we can hide
Sa-ated, my thirst has aba-ated
This world I've crea-ated
There's no hope to find
In this wasteland of mine