I comb the crowd~~
But I~~ can't see your face out there~, no~
I'm playing now~~
Won't wait on~ love
I'm paralyzed~~
From all~~ these whispers in my brain~
I'm focused now~~
I won't give~ up
I'm resonant
Won't stop for~ you
Playing away~ playing away
You play your games
You bring me pain
Playing away~ playing away
You hurt me now
But I won't~ cry
I am Octa~vi~~~a
You hurt me now
But I won't~ cry~
I am Octa~vi~a
Ditch me now~~
But it's you~ who'll have lost it all~, yeah~
Lost now~~ and bleeding~ love
Rain it pours~~
But I~~ won't let it bring me down~, no
I'm playing now~~
Won't wait on~ love
I'm resonant
Won't stop for~ you
Playing away~ playing away
You play your games, you bring me pain
You hurt me now but I won't~ cry
I am Octa~vi~~~a
You hurt me now but I won't~ cry~
I am Octa~vi~~~~a~~~
I am Octa~vi~~~~a
Born strong believe none
Dying over broken~ dreams
Born strong
And raised with class~~~~~ so~ yeah~~~
You hurt me now but I won't~ cry
I am Octa~vi~~~a
You hurt me now but I won't~ cry~
I am Octa~vi~~~~a
You hurt me now, but I won't~ cry