Nothing stays the same for long
But when it changes doesn't mean it's go-one
Time will always get away
As it leaves behind another da-ay
Things may come and things may go
Some go fast and some go-o slow
Few things last, that's all I know
But friendship carries on through the a-ages
Things may come and things may go
Some go fast and some go slow
Few things last, that's all I know
But fri-endship carries on through the a-ages
Been around for a long time
Rockin' out hard, 'cause I'm in my prime
Maybe it'll change further do-own the line
But my friendship carries on through the ages
Every single style has so-omethin'
Diff'rent it ca-an sa-ay
Nothin' wro-ong with bein' unique
And special in your o-own way
Maybe you wanna be a pop star
Get your fifteen minutes of fame, wah-ah, ah-ow
That won't last fore-ever
But friendship remains the same, ah-oh-oh
Things may come and things may go
Some go fast and some go-o slow
Few things last, that's all I-I know
But friendship carries on through the a-ages
Things may come and things may go
Some go fast and some go-o slow
Few things last, that's all I know
But friendship carries on through the a-ages
Oh-oh, carries on