I can’t count the years since
We all lost our voice~
And not a day goes by
That I don’t regret my choice
I wish I had the words to make them
Change their ways
I wish I had the courage to~
Leave like Autumn Blaze
Now there's a mare in front of me~
And she’s asking if I speak
She must not know about the stream~
She says her name and then repeats
And then slumps down in defeat
And I don’t know if I should dare to dream~~
I lost track of all the things
I’ve wanted to say~
All the thoughts I've held in so I could stay
But we have peace now
And surely peace must be upheld
But there’s a mare in front of me
And it seems she wants to help~
Now there's a mare in front of me~
And she’s asking if I speak
She must not know about the stream~
She says her name and then repeats
And then slumps down in defeat
And I don’t know if I should dare to dream~~
'Cause rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you let it rain
No, you can't give up your laughter
'Cause you're scared of a little pain
No rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you let it rain~
No, you can't give up your laughter
'Cause you're scared of a little pain
Now there's a mare in front of me~
And she’s asking if I speak~
She must not know about the stream~
She says her name and then repeats
And then slumps down in defeat
And I don’t know if I should dare to dream~~