Ponyville, I was in lo-ove with yo-ou
But I'm trying something ne-ew
Ya don't need me no-ow
I knew it was too-oo good to be tru-ue
I knew that we'd both lo-o-ose
And you've let me do-own
It's time to say goodbye
'Cause I've learned how to fly
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
All tension's thin out here
In this cool atmosphere
So, I'll be living here on the moon
La da da da da
La da da da da da
Look at me, trottin' here o-on my o-own
I mean, look how far I've flo-own
It's already growi-ing on me
Come to think of it, you'll never see me-e aga-ain
Don't even ask me how I've be-e-een
And don't even think a-about me-e-e, ye-e-eah
No-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
It's time to say goodbye
'Cause I've learned how to fly
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
All tension's thin out here
In this cool atmosphere
So, I'll be living here on the moon
Here o-on the moon
This is no game of hide and see-ee-eek
I guess I just need time to thi-i-i-ink
So, fa-ace the facts
'Cause I won't be-e back
It's time to say goodbye
'Cause I've learned how to fly
Don't wanna see you anytime soon
All tension's thin out here
In this cool atmosphere
So I'll be living here on the moon
I'm not playing hide and seek
I just need time to think
So I'll be thinking here on the moon
La da da da da
La da da da da da
La da da da da-a da
La da da da da da-a-a
La da da-a da da
La da da da da