It's always a good time~
Woke~ up on the right side of the bed
What's~ up with this Prince~ song inside my head?
Hands up if you're down to get down tonight
'Cause it's always a good time~
Slept~ in all my clothes like I didn't care
Hopped~ into a cab take me anywhere
I'm~ in if you're down to get down tonight
'Cause it's always a good time~
Good morning and good night
I'll wake up at twilight
It's gonna be al~right
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
Whoa~~~~ oh oh oh~ oh
Whoa~~~~ oh it's always a good time~
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
It's always a good time~
Freaked~ out dropped my phone in the pool again
Checked~ out of my room~ hit the ATM
Let's hang out if you're down to get down tonight~
'Cause it's always a good time~
Good morning and good night
I'll wake up at twilight
It's gonna be al~right
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
Whoa~~~~ oh oh oh~ oh
Whoa~~~ oh it's always a good time~
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
Whoa~~~~ oh oh oh~ oh
Whoa~~~~ oh it's always a good time~
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
Doesn't matter when it's always a good time then
Whoa~~~~ oh oh oh~ oh
Whoa~~~~ oh it's always a good time~
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~
Whoa~~~~ oh oh oh~ oh
Whoa~~~~ oh it's always a good time~
We don't even have to try it's always a good time~