They took me out of my house
Now I have~ a new~ home
I gobble pills like a good girl
And I get a new~ bone~~~~
I wiggle around my fake tail despite how they treat me
They make me feel so alone~ even when they're here
So many orders to tell me
I dunno what to do~
I wanna run on all fours
Just like anyone around~ me~~~~
So I run after my friends
But my friends wanna catch~~~ me ~
I'm not like anyone else
Cause they just wanna hurt~ me~
stop me and torture me~ but that's alright~
Cause I know who I am
But still no one believes~ me~
believes~ me~,
believes~~ me~~~~~
Now I see everyone else
From a small win~dow
They all seem so normal
It feels really~ shal~low~~
So I wondered why everyone were against~ me~
I thought that it's normal to~ be who I want to be~
And they all call me crazy
but I just wished to be free~~~~~~
I wanna run on all fours
Just like anyone around~ me~~~~
So I run after my friends
But my friends wanna catch~~~ me~
I'm not like anyone else
Cause they just wanna hurt~ me~
stop me and torture me~ but that's alright~
Cause I know who I am
But still no one believes~ me~
believes~ me~
believes~~ me~~~~~~~~~~~
Wah~~oh~~~
I'm not like anyone else
Cause they just wanna hurt~ me~
stop me and torture me~ that's alright
Cause I know who I am
But still no one believes~ me~
believes~ me~, believes~~ me~~~~~