With an ever-caring soul and soft blue eyes
And a kindness from your heart, you've stolen mine
Let me borrow you a mo~ment
Can you see where this is goin'?
Don't be afraid, I'm always right behind~~
'Cause you make my heart flutter
You make my heart flutter
It's a thought in my mind
It's a feeling inside~
You make my heart flutter
I can see it's a sign~
But you make me so blind~
You make my heart flutter
All the judging eyes~, clouding up your day
And the harmful words~, everything they~~ say
But no matter what the weather
You're as beautiful as ever
Come along with me, its nothing in our way
'Cause you make my heart flutter
You make my heart flutter
It's a thought in my mind~
It's a feeling inside~
You make my heart flutter
I can see it's a sign
But you make me so blind~
You make my heart flutter
It's a thought in my mind
It's a feeling inside~
You make my heart flutter
I can see it's a sign~
But you make me so blind~
You make my heart flutter
Ooh ooh ooh