Well I bit the bullet, I drunk it dry
My heart is spillin' over~ the sides
Of a tall glass of whiskey that's killin' the pain~~
My wings were broken, all feathers and flame
Heart pumpin black and blue, swirling down~ the pit
I ain't been me since Zephyr came and went
They told me I would fly
A talent I~ received
But that didn't keep her with me
My mind's full of this déjà vu~ but it ain't curin' my broken wing blues
The columns of my city, in youth I would spend
Twixt ivory chute and slalom with Zephyr, my first~ friend
Stripe war poised to strangle, but fringe to fringe we knew~~
The pair~ of us would scare us up a victory or two
For sun and moon and country, it ends, we all go home
One mortar shell shot that to hell~, now ground-bound I'm~~ alone
They told me I would fly
The treatment I~ received didn't bring her back to~ me
My mind's full of your déjà vu~, but it ain't curin' my broken wing blues
Docs pumped me full of magic, spruced me up real good
My burnt wings strapped to plastic, a new hoof out of wood
My wings are fixed, done with healin', but
Losing my wingmare's got me feelin' like
Only you could break that ceiling and
Every second's time~~ I'm stea~lin'
They told me I would fly~~~~~~
They told me I would fly~~~~~
They told me a lie~~~~~~
It hurts to laugh~
When six feet under's my better half~ oh
You can bury me there too, through this bottle
I'll follow you~ and finally be through~~
With these broken wing blues
Broken wing blues
Broken wing blues~~~
Mmmmmm~
Mmmmmm~~~
Broken wing…