Your heart is in two places, you can only live in one
You're torn between the hilltops and the-e tide
Thank goodness that the Cutie Mark Crusaders have begu-un
To give you hope and help you to decide
These hills, they call to you, they say "Harmonizing Heights"
This is your home, simple and serene
The sun-dappled leaves or a mountain terrace
You can see twenty-three different shades of green
To dare to compare anywhere to there
Is unfair and just plain wrong
Colt or mare or you wear
Feathers, fins, or hair
This is where you belong
Well, on the other hoof,
I can think of a place that's way more exciting and cool
Not to mention more you!
Come on, you know exactly where I mean!
Seaquestria's the most, you're supposed to be there
Underneath the sea, where you can feel at home
Swimmin' with your friends, you can spend all day here
Playin' in the bay here, splashin' in the foam
Sailin' through the wavy blue
You'll view a slew of tortoises
Forget the rest, the sea's the-e best
For all intents and porpoises
Build your nest
Here on Harmonizing Heights
Live it up here in Seaquestria-a-a
Nothing compares to Harmonizing Heights
The eagles are regal
The schools are cooler
Their claws are so awesome
With their sweet maneuvers
Star wishes every night
Starfish by e-el light
Better
Wetter
Shinier
Brinier
Seaquestria
Harmonizing Heights
That's it
This is the end
Don't ever talk to me again