yay
Sing it loud, sing it strong, sing a pony song
Shout it out to the break of da-a-awn
Crank it up, 'cause the mares are rockin' on
Sing it all night lo-o-ong
Listen up 'cause the party's goin' down
Ponies dance to the kick-ass so-o-ound
Party animals want the best around
Shakin' up the to-o-own
Feel the bass of the instrumental power
Hooves are moving in the musical encounter
Shake it up, as we party on for ho-ours
So come on, and sing it
LOUDER!!
yay
Sing it loud, sing it strong, sing a pony song
Shout it out to the break of da-a-awn
Crank it up, 'cause the mares are rockin' on
Sing it all night lo-o-ong
Listen up 'cause the party's goin' down
Ponies dance to the kick-ass so-o-ound
Party animals want the best around
Shakin' up the to-o-own