I'm lyin' in bed, can't sleep
'cause I'm tryin' to think
When did we last speak?
I left you on hold
So untrue
Just been working so hard
Like you know I do
It's taking a toll
It seems
And our friendship is cold
With how long it's been
But I need you to know
Just this
It's not only you who's feelin'
It's always hard
When we're miles apart!
But don't you start thinkin'~
I'm not here for~ you!
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin' to you
I'll come runnin' back
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin to you
I'll come runnin'
Vinyl!
It's not fair!
You sayin' I don't care
Just say the words to me
I'll come running
Don't you dare
Go sayin' I don't care
I'll always be there for you~
I'll come running yeah
I'll come running
I'm packing my bags tonight
Put rehearsals on hold til' I~ make this right
The train leaves at four
There's still time
I can't wait anymore to say what's on my mind
But what could this mean?
It's surreal
Going out of my way, 'cause of how I feel
And what will they think of me?
I say it's you I'm runnin' to!
I'm not scared!
And my heart's laid bare
So just wait right there
I'll come straight to you
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin' to you
I'll come runnin' back
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin to you
I'll come runnin'
Vinyl!
It's not fair!
You sayin' I don't care!
Just say the words to me
I'll come running
Don't you dare
Go sayin' I don't care
I'll always be there for you~
I'll come running yeah
I'll come running
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin' to you
I'll come runnin' back
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin to you
I'll come runnin'
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin' to you
I'll come runnin' back
I'll come runnin', yeah~
I'll come runnin to you
I'll come runnin'