Caught in a trap, a magic spell
I've got an urge that I can't quell
I am a prisoner to~ the beat~
I am a slave and it's absurd
I simply cannot fight the words
Rhythmically moving my feet~
That pulsing beat, it carries on
I could be here until the dawn
Back and forth and back I sway
That pulsing beat comes from above
A gentle hand turned to a shove
And I might never get away
You sweep and sweep and sweep and sweep that floor
You sweep and sweep until you can't sweep no more
You sweep and sweep and sweep until you're sore
Dust is the enemy and you're at war
You sweep and sweep and sweep and sweep that room
You sweep until you've worn down the entire broom
You keep on sweeping and I assume
You'll keep sweeping until your doom
Caught in a trap that I can't break
It's sad, it seems this is my fate
So I guess I'll just sweep sweep sweep~
I'm a prisoner I can't escape
My life's no longer mine to shape
If you cry for me, you better weep~
That pulsing beat, it carries on
I could be here until the dawn
Back and forth and back I sway~
That pulsing beat comes from above
A gentle hand turned to a shove
I might never get away
You sweep and sweep and sweep and sweep that floor
You sweep and sweep until you can't sweep no more
You sweep and sweep and sweep until you're sore
Dust is the enemy and you're at war
You sweep and sweep and sweep and sweep that room
You sweep until you've worn down the entire broom
You keep on sweeping and I assume
You'll keep sweeping until~ your~ doom