Three friends
Taking on the world together
Big plans in a bigger world
Still kids afraid of being young forever
Young eyes watch life unfurl~
Why do you sit there sighing
Instead of trying one more time?
I've been there
I know exactly what you're thinking
But why try growing up too fast~?
Now, I've learned it's better living in the moment
Enjoy youth, cause it doesn't last
Now you're hoping, trying, praying, crying
For your destiny to come this time
You are so young
And you are so free
But you're aimless
And I can't help but see
That you don't know
What you really need
"Are we there yet
Are we there yet?"
You've done it all
From A to Z
Are you trying
To find your destiny?
One day you'll know
Who you wanna be
"Are we there yet?
Are we there yet?"
Young eyes see everything you've ever wanted
Hope dies when it won't come true~
But realize the possibilities are endless
And in time it will be all for you
And you're hoping, trying, praying, crying
But your destiny will come in time
You are so young
And you are so free
But you're aimless
And I can't help but see
That you don't know
What you really need
"Are we there yet
A- A- Are we there yet?"
You've done it all
From A to Z
Are you trying
To find your destiny?
Still you don't know
Who you wanna be?
"Are we there yet?
A- A- Are we there yet?"
You are so young
And you are so free
But you're aimless
And I can't help but see
That you don't know
What you really need
"Are we there yet,
A- A- Are we there yet?"
You've done it all
From A to Z
Are you trying
To find your destiny?
Still you don't know
Who you wanna be~?
"Are we there yet?
A- A- Are we there yet?"