It breaks me when she cries
and when she sings goodnight
her kindness is a kiss
such a gentle pegasus
but when the tears fall down
from the shame that she feels now
it keeps her from the sky
she just wants to ru-u-un and hide and hide
childhood memories come rushing in
she can't hold back the tears
all the years can't heal the pain
will it be the same
like it was back then
no the wind will lift her wings
she will find her way
she will bring the rain
She will bring the rain
She wishes she could fly
like Rainbow in the sky
her wings won't let her try
the fear runs deep inside
it ties her down keeps her on the ground but
she will try-y
She can fly
She can fly she can really fly
Fluttershy
She needs every ounce of strength
to make the grade to bring the rain
she can't give up
she can't slow down
she won't let the fear tie her to the ground
Butterflies can't hold her do-own
the wind will lift he-er wings
she will find her way
she will bring the rain
she wishes she could fly
like Rainbow in the sky
her wings wont let her try
the fear runs deep inside
it ties her down keeps her on the ground but
she will try-y
She can fly Fluttershy
She can fly she can really fly
She can fly
she can really fly
Fluttershy
let yo-our wings
take you to the sky
don't let their eyes hold you back