You don't have to fear~
This night of ours~~
Won't you listen chil~dren?
Those nightmares are~ gone
You don't have to fear~
This night of~ ours~
Won't you listen chil~dren?~
Those nightmares are~ gone
Princess remember watch the screaming
Why do you cower before me?
All that I ask is you bathe in my glory
Creature of nightmare no longer
Adoration my only desire
Is it too late for~ me?
Why must hist'ry re~peat?
Wasn't my sojourn on the moon enough?
Why must I brave this silence?
This night~ of~ ours~~
Won't you listen chil~dren?
Those nightmares are gone
Sometimes it's just really fun to be scared
We'll if it's frights that you seek
I've got horrors to make you weep
Legion with legs beyond count
How the buck do you like me now?
Nightmare Night is cancelled!
Is~ it too late for~ me?
You don't have to fear
This night~ of~ ours~~
Won't you listen chil~dren?
Those nightmares are gone
This night~ of~ ours~~