Being
Faith~~ful~
Is easy
When you're winning~
No one ever~ leaves
But when
Cha~os~
Starts to gather
They will let you down~~
You will see
The~ thunder~
I can make it
Like if the drums of war~~
Could rain down~
And~ with pops like guns~~
Fire~ sweetness
To the mouths of the hungry ones~
When they come around
One~
By one
They~ joined me~~
All~ at a time~ they treat you bad~
Do~
You feel~ your power slipping~
I can't take~
What you never~ had
E~ven in play~
It's war that you~ made~
And your penance~
Is Discord~
Color fades away~
You know you lost the~ game~
And the winner~
Is Discord~
You can cry but I won't feel~
It's reality I~ steal~
What will you do~ now~
With Discord~
I've been hurt and I feel used~
Put away left out a~bused~
You're gonna have to deal~
With Discord~