As fa-ar as the e-eye ca-an see
A-all e-eyes are o-o-on me
They think I~ have what the-ey need
But how can I~ answer every plea?
The-ey te-ell me "He-e-ey,
can't you see that we're hu-urting?"
"You got the a-answer, cure all the ca-a-ancer
within our ho-omes"
What should I sa-a-a-ay?
There's no perfect solu-ution
I end up decla-aring something tempora-ary
Because I'm no-o-ot allowed to~ say "I don't know"
One million vo-oices all a-at once
They all say I~ ha-ave what everyo-o-one wants
And I he-ear so-ome say that I have it a-all
And ye-et I ca-an't answer every call
The-ey te-ell me "He-e-ey,
can't you see that we're hu-urting?"
"You got the a-answer, cure all the ca-a-ancer
within our ho-omes"
What should I sa-a-a-ay?
There's no perfect solu-ution
I end up decla-aring something tempora-ary
Because I'm no-o-ot allowed to~ say
I'm one of yo-o-o-ou, I'm no one spe-e-cial
But my shi-iny cro-own convinced you otherwise
I wish they kne-e-e-ew, my situa-ation~
I'm an o-ordina-ary nothing in disguise
"He-ey, can't you see that we're hu-urting?"
"You got the a-answer, cure all the ca-a-ancer
within our ho-omes"
What should I sa-a-a-ay?
There's no perfect solu-ution
I end up decla-aring something tempora-ary
Because I'm no-o-ot allowed to~ say "I don't know"