He's a stallion of very few words
There is seldom a sound to be heard
He's got big green eyes that shine in the sun
And I love to see them when the day's begun
His coat is red like the sweetest rose
Or more like the color of his apples I suppose
Those three little freckles on his cheeks
That bounce up and down when he finally speaks! Ooooh
I guess maybe I'm just a little bit messed up
But my heart skips a beat when he says…
"Eeyup"!
That big green apple on his side
That gently sways with him in his stride
That dirty blonde mane and unkempt tail
Messy, yet perfect to the smallest detail!
He's a great big pony, he can fill any space
And unless he bends down I can't reach his face!
His apple-bucking makes him super strong too
You better hope that kick is never aiming at you! Ooh
I guess maybe I'm just a little bit messed up
But my heart skips a beat when he says "Eeyup"!
His voice is the softest baritone
And the harmonies are perfect when it's with my own
He's a caring pony anyone would agree
Just ask anypony in the Apple Family
I~~ guess I'm a little bit messed up
But my heart skips a beat when he says "Eeyup"!
Oooh I guess I'm maybe just a little bit messed up
But my heart skips a beat
Yes my heart skips a beat
Oooooh my heart skips a beat
When he says "Eeyup"!