See the shapes~ and colours~
Of the patterns all around
I'm lifted, soft like dawn
Know the waves~ of light~~
Tiny fragments of self
They shifted, paint the town
I don't got a care in the world
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Rain drops
I don't have to be that kind of girl
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Rain drops
See the sparks~ and shadows~~
See
They reach o~ver shine
I'm crossed in grids and lines
Grids and lines
Know the ne~gative spaces~~
Know
That you move~ within
That you move~ with~in
I'm dancing, in between
In between
Slow pause
Slow~ motion as I~ pause
I see the beau~ty and the flaws
Rain, dia~monds~~
Rain drops like~ dia~monds~
I don't got a care in the world
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Rain drops
I don't have to be that kind of girl
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Rain drops
I don't got a care in the world
I don't got a care in the world~~
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Drops
They bounce right off my
I don't have to be that kind of girl
No I, no I
City slicker
Rain drops, they bounce right off my back
Drops
They bounce right off my
Rain~ drops