Don't trust a word from that evil wicked mare
Stay awake or she'll be in your nightmares
She's the princess of the night
But once was a villain
who caused pain andfright
She claims she's reformed
but it's hard to believe
That she's strayed from
her villainous path
Trapped in her archaic ways
She loves exe cu tions
like back in the-day
Thinking she'd give that up
seems totally naive
Now no one is safe from her wrath
I'm not convinced that she doesn't eat
fillies after stalking them in their dreams
Don't let her outward
appearance deceive
you 'cause she's not
as sweet as she seems
Don't trust a word from that evil wicked mare
Though she denies it
she's pure evil through and through
Preying on any foals
who claim that they're not scared
If you're not careful
then she might come for you
You had better hope
that your dreams tonight are spared
Stay awake or she'll see you in your nightmares