Hey you could you give a lis~ten?
Watched you from afar can't help~ but think
My~ love for you is a given
Just the sight~ of you has~ me tickled pink~
Cause it's late I'm awake
and I really can't think
'cause the girl is walking by me
and I just don't wanna blink
Cause she's here out my fearI just don't know what to say
but then again she isn't real
but I just can't look away
And I can't fathom the thought~ cause she's the perfect girl
Right now I cannot mistake~ she really rocks my world
But how am I any dif'rent from the ten million guys~
Feeling all the same when they all look in her eyes~
Twilight why can't you meet me?
Why can't you see beyond~ the lighted stage?~
Twilight girl please believe me
Because tonight I'm feelin' lonely
Gonna break you out of your cage~
Crossed paths with the girl of my~ dreams
Life since not as easy as~ it seems
Broke down the fourth wall to see you
Just the thought of you here though too good to be true~
But never even thought that I'd see you
Got too many questions how are you even true?
Twenty four seven always showered with attention
Did I mention you're an internet sensation?
And I can't fathom the thought~ cause she's the perfect girl
Right now I cannot mistake she really rocks my world
But how am I any dif'rent from the ten million guys~
Feeling all the same~ when they all look in her eyes~
Twilight why can't you meet me?
Why can't you see beyond~ the lighted stage?~
Twilight girl please believe me
Because tonight I'm feelin' lonely
Gonna break you out of your cage~~~
Listen to my words~ 'fore I forget again
Promised you my love~ that this would never~ end
But your duties have tak~en you girl
I'll send~ you all my feelings through this song wait for you 'round the bend
Listen to my words~ 'fore I forget again
Promised you my love~ that this would never end
But your duties have taken you girl I'll
Send~ you all my feelings through this song waitfor you 'round the bend
Listen to my words~ 'fore I forget again
Promised you my love~ that this would never end
But your duties have taken you girl I'll
Send~ you all my feelings through this song wait
for you 'round the bend
And I can't fathom the thought~ cause she's the perfect girl
Right now I cannot mistake she really rocks my world
But how am I any dif'rent from the ten million guys~
Feeling all the same~ when they all look in her eyes~
Twilight why can't you meet me?
Why can't you see beyond~ the lighted stage?~
Twilight girl please believe me
Because tonight I'm feelin' lonely
Twilight why can't you meet me?
At least you saw beyond~ the lighted stage~
Twilight girl please believe me
Because tonight I'm feelin' lonely
Gonna break you out of your cage~