So there you are, my dad
A statue oh so cold, so dead
You tore their world apart
And everypony lost their heads
Now I must carry on
Making chaos for you instead
'Cause you are my Dad~dy Discord
And I am a piece of you
I miss you, daddy...
Please do not~ cry, my dear
Your daddy is still very here
And when I do bust out
We can respread the random fear
Our joy will be their pain
As their world drowns in choc'late rain
'Cause I am your Daddy Discord
And you are a piece of me
Remember that one time
You took me to that baseball game
I got my cutie mark
And things were never quite the same
My wild~ pitches flew driving the ponies all insane
'Cause you are my Dad~dy Discord
And I am a piece of you
(Take) me out to your mind game
If chaos loses it's a real shame
That's my Screwball!
Oh simple~ spawn of mine
Without you I would be so~ lost
You have stuck by my side
No matter what the tragic cost
My crazed imagined thoughts
Have given you a newfound strength
'Cause I am your daugh~ter Screwball
And you're breaking out of there!
Daddy, you're alive!
I'm free, free once again!
May Equestria return to its natural chaotic state!
Come, my little abomination, we have work to do!
I missed you, daddy...