You cannot see
But your heart is pure
I know you fe-eel tra-apped
In a da-ark world
Some brush you o-off
And ca-all yo-ou weak
But your na-ame i-is Snowdrop
One day the-ey'll se-ee
If you hold fast and sta-a-and strong
You'll discover who you are
If you listen to the world at night
You can hear the twinkling stars
If you use love to guide your heart
You're bo-ound to go-o fa-ar
You have the po-ower to change the world
Being uniquely who-o you a-are
You ca-anno-ot se-ee
But your mi-ind i-is su-ure
I know you fe-eel sick
When there's no-o cu-ure
Some brush you o-off
With wo-ords to clip yo-our wi-ings
But you have to know this
So I-I'm he-ere to sing
If you hold fast and sta-a-and strong
You'll discover who you are
If you listen to the world at night
You can hear the twinkling stars
If you use love to guide your heart
You're bo-ound to go-o fa-ar
You have the po-ower to change the world
Being uniquely who-o you a-are