Oh oh ah ah ah oh
Oh oh uh oh uh
Oh oh ah ah ah ah
Looking forward to some fun
Knowing all our friends will come
'Cause we're here to spend the day
Ev'rybody come and play
Let's all pick a meeting place
And we're gonna have to race
Ev'rybody follow me
This is where we're gonna be
With my best friends
Though we're different
We feel like we still be-elong
And every day it makes our friendship
Stro-o-o-o-ong
Let's go find what games to win
Ev'rybody's joining in
'Cause we're having such a blast
Hey, did I just come in last?
Doesn't matter win or lose
When we always are amused
My friends stand out in a crowd
Having fun and laughing loud!
With my best friends
We can depend
They will always follow through
It's a perfect day for fun
When I spend it with you
Oh oh ah ah ah oh
Oh oh uh oh uh
Oh oh ah ah ah ah
Taking photos with my friends
Never want this day to end
But the time is going fast
So come on and make it last
Get the band up on the stage
Doesn't matter what your age
Hear the music, now's your chance
Ev'rybody start to dance!
With my best friends
Though we're different
We feel like we still be-elong
And every day it makes our friendship
Stro-o-o-o-ong
With my best friends
We can depend
They will always follow through
There's a guarantee for fun
When I spend it with you