For all my life
All I've wanted to do
Was make my friends
Want to smi-le true
But maybe I was wrong
And Pinkie Pie
Shouldn't plan parties at all
I'll try to get up on my hooves
And try a different task
I'll find something new to do
There's gotta be more to me
Than planning a party or two
I put away my party cannon
I deflated all my balloons
The bubbles all burst
Now what is next for you?
For you
Oh, I remember this one
My first party ever
My whole family was there
And that's Twilight's welcome-to-Ponyville party
She didn't even expect that one
*giggle*
Oh, look at Gummy!
He just looks so excited for this birthday party
Hmm!
Shining Armor and Cadance's
Wedding sure was special
Especially once *I* got a hold of the music
Oh, look at those happy faces
All the parties that I had thrown
I made them laugh, had such a blast
A smile that's all the-ir own
They loved seeing me, the real Pinkie
Show them the time of their life
Like they've never known
Like they've never kno-o-own
I've got to get back out there
Have to show them that I've tried
For there's only one great party pony
That is Pinkie Pie
Won't let Cheese Sandwich beat me
Won't let him get me down
For I am Pinkie
The bestest party pony around!