Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything is certainly fine
There's the mayor en route to her office
There's the sofa clerk selling some quills
Morning, kid!
My Ponyville is so gentle and still
Can things ever go wrong?
I don't think that the-ey will.
Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything is certainly...
Life in Equestria shimmers
Life in Equestria shi-i-ines
And I know for ab-solute certain
That everythi-ing
Yes everythi-ing
Yes everything is certainly fi-ine
It's fine
Yes, everything is gonna be just fine