Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
I do-on't know where they're go-o-ing
but I doubt we'll find out soon
Is Dashie followi-ing behind 'cause toughness is her pri-ide,
Or because the animator just could not fit her inside?
So I guess there's not-
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
Although that seems so la-a-zy it's at least a catchy tune
It's hard to write the so-ong and make the animation too~
So if any other artists wanna work with me
Make contact ple-ease, in the meantime
I'll just sing about…
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
I do-on't know where they're go-o-ing
but I doubt we'll find out soon
Is Dashie followi-ing behind 'cause toughness is her pri-ide,
Or because the animator just could not fit her inside?
So I guess there's not-
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
Although that seems so la-azy it's at least a catchy tune
It's hard to write the so-ong and make the animation too~
So if any other artists wanna work with me
Make contact ple-ease, in the meantime
I'll just sing about…
(Pony Pony Pony Pony Pony Pony Pony Pony)
Pony
Po-
I'll just sing about…
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
I do-on't know where they're go-o-ing
but I doubt we'll find out soon
Is Dashie followi-ing behind 'cause toughness is her pri-ide,
Or because the animator just could not fit her inside?
So I guess there's not-
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a pink ho-ot air balloon
Six ponies fly-y-ing in a-
Six-
ponies
fly-ying
fly-y
y- y-
I'll just sing about…