Can't move, bucked out
Can't stand long on my own, now filly
Won't listen, no sir
If you're wanting to help me out~
What I'm saying to you
Is the honest truth
Sure as sugar
That you can't stop me from helping my friends
Do better than their best
Trot further and ascend!
I'll always be there for my friends
Aw yeah
With any help that I might lend
Grab my rope, we'll put your
Problems in their pen
And we'll succeed
Because your
(Soul is tough)
With friends like you
I cannot get enough
You know your
(Heart is pure)
Faithful and strong
You know I know for sure
Uncivil, uncouth, table's too good for me
That's what you said
Bright lights, big city, can't seem to fit myself in
...to your polite company now
That's okay anyway
I'm bustin' flank back to the farm
What was I doin' thinkin' I was wrong?
I didn't learn nuthin'
I was right all along!
I'll always be there for my friends
Aw yeah
With any help that I might lend
Grab my rope, we'll put your
Problems in their pen~
And we'll succeed
Because your
(Soul is tough)
With friends like you
I cannot get enough
You know your
(Heart is pure)
Faithful and strong
You know I know for sure
You gotta
(Trust yourself)
I know you can do it
I know you know it, too
(Just be free)
Faithful and strong
That's what I want to be, now
Be a shining light
A Champion of what is right
Bless those around you and you'll see
Exactly who you're s'posed to be~~~
Woo!
(Soul is tough)
With friends like you
I cannot get enough
You know your
(Heart is pure)
Faithful and strong
You know I know for sure
You gotta
(Trust yourself)
I know you can do it
I know you know it, too
(Just be free)
Faithful and strong
That's what I want
That's what I want to be!
Yeah~~~~~~~~~~~~~!