Everypony thinks you're crazy
They don't know what's going on
Tell them all your potions 'plenished
Yesterday they used to be gone
Am I just a piece of fiction
Feeding into your addictions
Or am I the real thing~?
I'm all you need
Let's see you try and escape from~ me~
You'll never succeed
An addict is all you'll ever~ be~
Let me lead you to the bottle
One more I hear you say
I can feel you lie to yourself
I heard it yesterday
Who's on top now?
Are you feeling the burn now?
It's time you got used to me
I'm all you need
Let's see you try and escape from~ me~
You'll never succeed
An addict is all you'll ever~ be~
I'm all you need
Let's see you try and escape from~ me~
You'll never succeed
An addict is all you'll ever~ be~
A part of you
I'll always be
The former you
They'll never see
A part of you
I'll always be
The former you
They'll never see
I'm all you need
Let's see you try and escape from~ me~
You'll never succeed
An addict is all you'll ever~ be~
I'm all you need
Let's see you try and escape from~ me~
You'll never succeed
An addict is all you'll ever…~