In the darkest hours
Of the blackest nights
We are the voice of the neglected youth
For the new generation
We give our call
This is the young rebel crusade...
By the light of the silver moon
Hear the voices of the wind
Give a sign to the younger ones
Our hour's~ about to begin
For we are dreamers and we give our lives
To the children who can't find their way~
We are the ones who will help you survive
For tomorrow's your brightest day~
Destiny isn't free
You must know what you need
In the depths of your heart
Clear your soul of the lies
You must stand up and fight
For the crusade to start
Don't you dare cry, my fellow friend
We have been in your shoes
Though the jour~ney is treacherous
The turnout is your path to choose
For we are dreamers
And we give our lives
To the lost and the blank and dismayed~
We are the ones who will help them survive
For the flag is their own to raise~
Destiny isn't free
You must know what you need
In the depths of your heart
Clear your soul of the lies
You must stand up and fight
For the crusade to start
In your eyes there is fire
Show the world your desires
For your passion to burn
Born again, start anew
For our dreams will come true
Now my friends, it's your turn
Destiny isn't free
You must know what you need
In the depths of your heart
Clear your soul of the lies
You must stand up and fight
For the crusade to start
In your eyes there is fire
Show the world your desires
For your passion to burn
Born again, start anew
For our dreams will come true
Now my friends, it's your turn
In the darkest hours
Of the blackest nights
We are the voice of the neglected youth
For the new generation
We give our call
This is
The young rebel crusade!