Take my hand and we can run
Hold my heart 'cause we're no~t done
Death is not the e~nd
Close your eyes, fore~ver re~st
I know you tri~ed your best
So long my~ friend
This is not the~ end fo~r you and I~
It's okay to say goodbye~
Fade away, oh~ fa~de a~way, in ti~me
We'll meet again
Our story's just begu~n, so goodbye~
Take my heart and I wi~ll cry
Hold my hand, take to the~ sky
Our chapter's at an e~nd
But there's still more for us to see~
After the end, again we~'ll me~~et
You'll always be~ my friend
This is not the~ end fo~r you and I~
It's okay to say goodbye~
Fade away, oh~ fa~de a~way, in ti~me
We'll meet again
Our story's just begu~n, so goodbye~
Trust me
I don't want to see you go~
This pain won't last fore~ver
You~'ll see
This won't be the end, we'll fi~nd
A whole new~ world toge~ther
This is not the~ end fo~r you and I~
It's okay to say goodbye~
Fade away, oh~ fa~de a~way, in ti~me
We'll meet again
Our story's just begu~n, so goodbye~
I'll see you aga~~in
So goodbye~
It's okay to part wa~ys
So goodbye~~
Our story isn't over
So goodbye~