Tia?
TIAAAA!
Does thou wanna see the moonrise~
Watch the ending of the day
I have been working, oh, so very hard
To move the stars
Into a beautiful 'ray
It's just been kind of lonely
All these things I do
And nopony seems to care
Does thou wanna see the moonrise~
Oh, we can hang out 'till the sunrise
Not tonight, Luna
Okay, fine
*Sob*
Why does everyone sleep through my gorgeous night?
*sob*
Celes?tia?
Does thou wanna see the moonrise~
I wanna show you, come with me
Orion's stars are out and shining bright
It's such a gorgeous night, oh won't you come and see
It's just that no one seems to notice
All the things I do
I feel like I'm going mad
Don't feel it, don't fight it anymore
There can only be one princesscess in Equestria
MUAHAHA
And that princesscess shall be me!
I'm sorry, sister
I must do this
You must be stopped!
Nooooooooooo~
Oh, Luna
Sister, please forgive me
Why did it have to end like this
If only I had just been there for you
Just like I ought have to
I was remiss
So distracted by my duties
Now I'm alone
I just don't know what to do
D'you wanna see the moonrise~
Luna
I'm sorry
LUNAAAAAAA!