Well Derpy wrecked the roof
With her clumsy little hooves
So they had to get some bits to fix it up
Rainbow tried her best
But Derpy is the best
At derping up and making a big mess
AJ said she'd win the prize
They stomped the ground and watched her smile
When she said she'd give it all away
So she took the train to Canterlot
Thought she'd go and win a lot
For all her friends back there in Ponyville
Well a week went by and they all cried
When AJ scribed and said goodbye
Sayin' that she wasn't coming back
Didn't know why but they couldn't stand by
So they ran out the door and the pegasus fly
To search the town for Applejack
Poor little AJ lost her pride
It made her hide it made her cry
She couldn't show her face in town again
She ran away 'cause she lost the game
And got a job for the pay
Buckin' cherry trees for some bits
And Cherry Jubilee was just as nice as she could be
But Applejack was hiding facts and dodging questions
So Rainbow Dash and Pinkie Pie
tried to get her to confess
And put her to the test with cherry chimmy chongas
Kumquat picklebarrel made her crack
'Cause she couldn't really take much more of that
And so she said she tell them all what happened
But she broke her pinkie promise and Pinkie raged
So they stole a cart and began to chase
'Cause friendship is persistent
Tears were shed and much was said
As AJ told the truth about the reason she left
And said i'm sorry
But it doesn't matter if you didn't win
It's who ya are beneath your skin
Wouldn't be the same here without you
'Cause we all love you
Here in Ponyville, Equestria
We all love you