Day in, day out
Monotone throughout
Then tomorrow we'll do it all again
No more cares left to give
This is the life I live
What's worse, it's cursed to never end
You could never know
Yes sister you could never know
Rainbow flowing hair
The smile I have to wear
These are the things in which I drown
You're the most ungrateful snot
In all of Canterlot
I'll burn this whole place to the ground
Night in, night out
Nought but dark and doubt
And loneliness setting in
No one here to say
How are you today?
Just the voice that lives within
Translucent flowing hair
The dreams under my care
These are the things in which I drown
The great Celestia
Of Equestria
Just a fake smile and a crown