The blue sky
Is all I need
The wind in my face
And the warmth of the sun
I'm just beaming
Wherever I am to go~~
I will know~~~ today~~
If ever the world~ should slow
I'll be in the sky making my own shade
And I
Will just fly~ away
Let the breeze carry me
Skyward dancing~
And I
Will just soar~ today
Let the gusts of wind
Glide under my wings~~~
Freedom flies
Fast and free
The rain clouds are too slow
And they will never catch up with me
Catch up with me
I'll drift beyond~ the sky~~~~
Fill my lungs with untouched~ air~~
Soar where there is no such war
Not even the trees can reach us here
And I
Will just fly~ away
Let the breeze carry me
Skyward dancing~
And I
Will just soar~ today
Let the gusts of wind
Glide under my wings
And I
Will just fly~ away
Let the breeze carry me
Skyward dancing
And I
Will just soar~ today
Let the gusts of wind
Glide under my wings~~~
Gotta leave Cloudsdale
There's more than this home
If you wanna see beauty
Beyond what you've known
Look to the moon
As it sits in the sky
The magic, the wonder
Of floating on high
...Will just fly~ away
Let the breeze carry me
Skyward dancing
And I
Will just soar~ today
Let the gusts of wind
Glide under my wings
And I
Will just fly~ away
Let the breeze carry me
Skyward dancing
And I
Will just soar~ today
Let the gusts of wind
Glide under my wings~~~