We're off
On the road to friendship
Our ride might be tiny and small
Beats walking though eh, Trix?
I'm glad we're sticking to it
We've already got a song
We're off
On the road to friendship
Side by side just like peas in a pod
Our bond of friendship is stronger
Than this tour's demands
Wait, what did he say?
We're so tight, we can't move around
I guess we're stuck together
'Cause we're friendship
You too, buddy!
We're off
On the road to friendship
We've each got the other to blame
Any trip can be exhausting
If you make a fuss
We're off
On the road to friendship
And there's nowhere that we'd rather be
In summer, winter, spring, and fall
We're friends throughout the year
For nine, at least!
We're so tight we can't move around
We're friendship bound
Or like a buddy movie where the two protagonists
Can't get away from each other
Because they're wearing hoof-cuffs!
We're friendship bound!