Open your mind
And you shall feel~
That everything around you
Is more than real~
As time fades away
And as we get old
Our memories will last
Framed in gold
We've only got one life to live
So I'ma live it up~~
We've only got one life to live~
So I'ma live it up~
We've only got one life to live
So I'ma live it up~~
We've only got one life to live~
So I'ma live it up~
Our memories will last
Framed in gold
We've only got one life to live
So I'ma live it up~~
And when we're done
That final day~
What will they know about you?
What will they say
Out of all the things I say
Hear this somehow
We've only got one life to live
And it starts now
Our memories will last
Framed in gold
We've only got one life to live
So I'ma live it up~~
So I'ma live it up~~~