Once 'pon a time
You came into my world
And made the stars align
Now, I can see the si-igns
You pick me up
When I get down
So I can shine
Shine like ra-inbo-o-o-ows
Friends, you are in my li-ife
And you can count on me
To be there by-y your side
And when the music comes ali-ive
You sing our songs
To lift us up
So we can shine
And the sound
That we hear
In our hearts
Makes a crescendo-o-o-o-o-o
And the light
That ignites
In the dark
It makes us all glo-o-o-ow
And shine like ra-inbows
We shine like ra-inbo-o-o-ows
Shine like ra-inbows
Together we stand
As the rain begins to fa-a-a-all
And holdin' our heads up high
As the sun shines thro-ugh it a-all
And the sound
That we hear
In our hearts
Makes a crescendo-o-o-o-o-o
And the light
That ignites
In the dark
It makes us all glo-o-o-ow
And shine like ra-inbo-o-o-ows
We shine like ra-inbo-o-o-ows
Shine like ra-inbo-o-o-ows
Shine like ra-inbows