I wish that Starlight was here to see
How strong friendships can be
When we trust each others
And work together
You've all taught me
I~ did~ my~~ time~
And I want out
So effusive~ fade~
It doesn't cut
The soul is not so vibrant
The reckoning~
The sickening~
Packaging subversion
Pseudo-sacrosanct perversion
Go drill your deserts
Go dig~ your graves~
Then fill your mouth
With all the money you will save~
Sinking in~, getting smaller again~
I'm~ done~
It has begun
I'm not the only one~
Best friends until the end of time~
We'll have each other's backs
And let our true selves shine~
And that's because everything we need
Is all~ right here
When we're with our team
Oh~ there~ are cracks~ in the road~ we laid~
But where the temple fell~
The secrets~ have~ gone~ mad~~
This is nothing new~
But when we killed it all~
The hate was all~ we had~~~
Who needs another mess~?
We could start over
Just look me in the eyes
And say "I'm wrong~"
We bring the best out, that's our goal
There's no telling how far we'll go
Best friends until the end of time~
We'll have each other's backs
And let our true selves shine~
And that's because everything we need
Is all~ right here
When we're with our team!