Sunday night
Silent by the pilot light
All the stories
All the endless fantasies I wanna write
By your side
Searching through the blue and white
Seashells on the beach
The finest angel wings and ammonite
Half-moon smile
Weekends on the Emerald Isle
You and me, a glowing sea
And memories of a lonely child
Running wild
Nothing left to reconcile
Stars align and good things come
Around every once in a while
Oh I know that this can't last forever
I know that you are far
Too brilliant and bright
There are futures that we will not weather
But for now we'll be alright
Flying like we're satellites
Stars and waves and satellites
Rising tides
Higher than I realized
Oh~ the o~cean in your eyes
It had me hypnotized
Mesmerized
All the pain that we've disguised
Lots of hues of red and blue
From where the ocean meets the skies
Have we fallen, fallen so far
That we can't remember who~ we are
All these years and all these fears
Hold back the water and the tears
No more
Sitting by the golden shore
Holding hands and holding fast
To what we know we can't ignore
Love and war
Fighting back the rain before
All the ocean comes alive
The power of the raging storm
There are moments that we will not weather
I know that we will one day give up the fight
So let's make this moment last forever
Take my heart and hold it tight
Flying like we're satellites
Wow oh wow oh
Wow oh wow oh oh
Flying like we're satellites
Wow oh wow oh
Wow oh wow oh oh
Flying like we're satellites