Let's get down to business
To defend the throne
Do you think you'll last here
When you're on your own?
You're the saddest bunch I've ever met
And you can bet before we're through
Filly, I'll make a bolt out of you~
Tranquil as the darkness
But a light
Within
We maintain this balance
With it we can win
You're the weakest fliers I ever met
And you haven't got a clue
Somehow I'll, make a bolt out of you
I'll never get these wings to work
The ground's so far down below me
Boy was I a fool for joining with this size
This mare's got 'em scared to death
Hope he doesn't see right through me
Now I really wish that I knew how to fly Wow!
Be a Bolt
You must be swift as the coursing river
With all the force of a sonic rainboom
With all the strength of a million stallions
Mysterious as the mare inside the moon
Time is racing toward us
Til our foes arrive
Will you fight against them?
Are you on our side?
You're unsuited for the flying corps
So pack up, go home, you're through
How could I make a bolt out of you?
Be a bolt
You must be swift as the coursing river
With all the force of a sonic rainboom
With all the strength of a million stallions
Mysterious as the mare inside the moon
Be a bolt
You must be swift as the coursing ri~ver
With all the force of a sonic rainboom
With all the strength of a million stal~lions
Mysterious as the mare inside the moon