I think a lot of us look into the mirror
And don't like what we see
But I've been thinking and learning
And friendship means looking past these things
So keep your head held high
And just stay by my side
'Cause I've been watching and waiting
And I think these things are worth saying
You hold the door for me
You spend your time on me~
We laugh hysterically
And I've been seeing
You're always there for me
You see me honestly~
I think there's some thing, you have it
I think that you've got magic
You couldn't be self-centered even if you tried
There's something~ that I see inside
And you don't know~ I've been watching
The way you fix people's hurting
So stop the way you hate
The way you act because I see~~~
Something perfect in your smile~
I know it's worth it all worthwhile
You hold the door for me
You spend your time on me~
We laugh hysterically
And I've been seeing
You're always there for me
You see me honestly~
I think there's something, you have it
I think that you've got magic
So come~ and follow me
While we~ breathe harmony~~~
And find it's meant to be
We've got what the world all ne~eds
So take my hand ‘cause I~
Still need~ you by my side~~~
We've found the point at last and
I think that we've got magic
So come and march with me
Let's spread~ this harmony~~~
You'll never be that far from me~
Even if we have to leave~~
So take my hand, let's go
There's something more I know~~~
I think that you have it
I think that you've got magic
You hold my heart, it helps
You share pieces of yourself
When I hurt, you smile at me
And I think I see that
You never leave me there
We can always clear the air~
I think there's something, you have it
I think that you've got magic
You hold the door for me
You spend your time on me~
We laugh hysterically
And I've been see~ing
You're always there for me
You see me honestly~
I think there's something, you have it
I think that you've got magic