Power
Was all I desired
But all that grew inside me
Was a darkness I aquired
When I began to fall
And I lost the path ahead
That's when your friendship found me
And it lifted me i-inste-ad
Like a phoenix burnin' bri-ight
In the sky-y
I'll show there's another si-i-ide to me
You ca-an't deny
I may not know what the fu-utu-ure holds
But hear me when I-I sa-ay
That my past does no-ot define me-e
'Cause my past is not today
Ambition
Is what I-I beli-eved
Would be the o-only way
To se-e-et me free
But when it disappeared
And I found myself alone
That's when you came and got me
And I fe-elt like I was ho-ome
Like a phoenix burnin' bri-ight
In the sky
I'll show there's another side to me
You ca-an't deny
I may not know what the futu-ure holds
But hear me when I-I sa-ay
That my past does not define me
'Cause my past is not today