Oh please excuse me
I don't mean to alarm
And certainly I mean you no physical harm
I'm just the reigning king of chaos
Here to rock your world
So just sit tight and let this little story unfurl~
My mission is simple: Neverending Strife
I'll worm into your heart and then I'll cut like a knife~
My intentions are clear so just surrender your will
I'm like a predator and I'm going in for the kill~
Don't hate me cause I'm funny
Don't hate me cause I'm beautiful
You should hate me cause I'm better than you
I only want to party
I only want to play it cool
I'm beholden to seeing this through
I could trot around your little pony head
Spreading white lies and whispers
I'm gonna tell you 'bout your fickle pony friends
Your rage is so hot it blisters
I have your attention now it's futile to flee
Your Elements of Harmony are worthless to me~
So please, you can't beat me, just fire away
I'll shrug it off and live to laugh another day~
My hatred and wisdom are a thousand years old
Millennia trapped in stone and desolate cold~
Your princess couldn't save you now you have no hope
You're hanging yourself, I'm just providing the rope~
Don't hate me cause I'm funny
Don't hate me cause I'm beautiful
You should hate me cause I'm better than you
I only want to party
I only want to play it cool
I'm beholden to seeing this through
I could trot around your little pony head
Spreading white lies and whispers
I'm gonna tell you 'bout your fickle pony friends
Your rage is so hot it blisters