Maybe I'm not one to look past all the years I slave~ away~
But I'm far from where I'll be someday
They'll find~ me free from them at last
Picking up pieces of~ me~
Pieces of me~
But my head's down on the pavement
Wondering where the years went
All the time I spent
Under eyes full of contempt~
My mind's still a crutch as
I stand at the edge of what's ahead
I'm frozen instead
I might be chas~ing pipe~ dreams
At least I'm chasing something more
Than shadows on the city street
They always said that I was green
That I won't amount to anything~ more
Than shadows on the city street
They'll take back everything
I'm not one to look past all the times I've been outcast~
But someday I know that
They'll find~ me free from them at last
Picking up pieces of me~
Pieces of me~
When will I get to prove to them?
When will I get my chance to win?
Someday I'll finally piece myself toge~ther
Yeah
But my head's down on the pavement
Wondering where the years went
All the time I spent
Under eyes full of contempt~
My mind's still a crutch as I stand at the edge
Of what's ahead
I'm frozen instead
I might be chas~ing pipe~ dreams
At least I'm chasing something more
Than shadows on the city street
They always said that I was green
That I won't amount to anything more
than shadows on the city street
They'll take back everything
I might be chas~ing pipe~ dreams
At least I'm chasing something more
Than shadows on the city street
They always said that I was green
That I won't amount to anything more
Than shadows on the city street
They'll take back everything