It's so lonely on the moon~
I hope that I~ can come home soon
Will it be the same~ when I~~ return?
I know there's a lesson I have learned
Why does the night~ no more~ inspire?
As I raise the sun~, I start to tire
I long for you~ to be~~ with me
But there are things~ that cannot be
And it takes some time~ away to see
And I've spent half my life waiting for your~ call
Why do I feel I don't belong anywhere~ at all~?
When I come~ home and see you~~ again
I'm gonna bring the night as my old~~est friend~
I'm gonna stay with you, and won't repeat mistakes
I no longer want to roam
I'll do whate~ver~ it takes~
To come home
There once lived in me a~ great fire
But it's been cooled by o~verwhelmed desire
There's a crater but it's just bone deep
And it deepens every time I sleep
I've spent a thousand years wishing on a~~ star
I feel so close but I've never been~ so far~~~
Why can't I tell you you were~ right all along?
Why must I forge a tragic plight with my~ song?
Why can't we meet between the moon and the sun?
Why must the sun shine when the night is~~ done?
When you come~ home and see me~~ again
I'm gonna welcome you as my old~est friend
I'm gonna stay with you, and won't repeat mistakes~
I don't wanna be alone
I'll do whate~ver~ it takes
To bring you home
It's so lonely on the moon~
I know Luna...
I hope that I~ can come home soon
Me too...
For a coming sunset I~~ will yearn~
The longest day will end~ and I will~ return~