Thread by thread stitching it together
Twilight's dress cutting out the pattern snip by snip
Making sure the fabric folds nicely
It's the perfect color and so hip
Always gotta keep in mind my pacing
Making sure the clothes' correctly facing
I'm stitching Twilight's dress
Yard by yard fussing on the details
Jewel neckline
Don't you know a stitch in time saves nine?
Make her something perfect to inspire~
Even though she hates formal attire
Gotta mind those intimate details
Even though she's more concerned with sales
It's Applejack's new dress
Dressmak~ing's easy for Pinkie Pie something pink
Fluttershy something breezy
Blend color and form
Do you think it looks cheesy?
Something brash perhaps quite fetching
Hook and eye couldn't you just simply die?
Making sure it fits forelock and crest
Don't forget some magic in the dress
Even though it rides high on the flank
Rainbow won't look like a tank~
I'm stitching Rainbow's dress
Piece by piece snip by snip
Croup dock haunch shoulders hip
Thread by thread primmed and pressed
Yard by yard never stressed
And that's the art of the dress
Now the stars on my belt need to be technic'ly accurate
Orion has three stars on his belt not four
Stitch by stitch stitching it together
Deadline looms
Don't you know the client's always right?
Even if my fabric choice was perfect
Got to get them all done by tonight
Pinkie Pie the color's too obtrusive
Wait until you see it in the light
I'm sewing them together
Don't you think my gown would be more me with some lollipops?
Well I think
Balloons? Well do it!
Hour by hour~ one more change
I'm sewing them together take great pains
Fluttershy you're putting me in a bind
Rainbow Dash what is on your mind?
Oh my gosh there's simply not much time
Don't forget
Applejack's duds must shine~~~
Dressmaking's easy every customer's call
Brings a whole new revision
Have to pick up the pace still hold to my vision
That constellation is Canis Major not Minor
French haute couture please ugh
What if it rains? Galoshes!
More balloons!
Oh no that's too many balloons
More candy! oh, less candy
Oh wait I know streamers
Streamers?
Whose dress is this?
Streamers it is
What?
Aren't you going to tell me to change something too?
No I just want my dress to be cool
Do you not like the color?
The color's fine just make it look cooler
Do you not like the shape?
The shape's fine just make the whole thing you know cooler
It needs to be about twenty percent cooler
All we ever want is indecision
All we really like is what we know
Gotta balance style~ with adherence
Making sure we make a good appearance
Even if you simply have to fudge it
Make sure that it stays within our budget
Got to overcome intimidation
Remember it's all in the presentation
Piece by piece snip by snip
Croup dock haunch shoulders hip
Bolt by bolt primmed and pressed
Yard by yard always stressed
And that's the art of the dress