We're getting closer to finding our destinies
I won't falter as long as they're with me
The lessons we live will continue to give
To everyone as we make history
So to my mom and my dad
I'll come back safe to my town and my life
Just you wait I'll return safe and sound one day
But until then~ I guess I'm just waiting, just waiting
I promise I'll always come home to you but
right now~ I have something I need to do
So though I take more steps from Ponyville
I know I will
I promise I'll always come right back home
But I have my friends
I swear I'm not alone
We're getting closer to finding our destinies
With laughter, we're moving on cheerfully
So though we don't know, somehow we'll show it
To everyone as we spread harmony
So to my dragon and my Princess I'll come back safe
I'll put my all in this, I'll try not to make you wait
I'll return safe and sound one day
To spread a message of harmony
Everywhere and always
But until then~ I guess I'm just waiting, just waiting
I promise I'll always come home to you
But right now I have something I need to do
So though I take more steps from Ponyville
I know I will
I promise I'll always come right back home
But I have my friends
I swear I'm not alone
But until then~ I guess I'm just waiting, just waiting
I promise I'll always come home~ to you
But right now I have something I need to do
So though I take more steps from Ponyville
I know we will
I promise I'll always come right back home
But I have my friends
I swear I'm not alone
We're on the road to fulfilling our destinies
With friendship, we'll overcome adversities
So though we're not~ there, I swear we'll share
Our magic at every opportunity
So to my friends by my side
We'll do our best, we're along for this ride
But I passed that test
We're on a journey
We're stuck here in transit
But as we make our way farther
Friendship is Magic
But until then I guess I'm just waiting, just waiting
I promise I'll always come home to you
But right now I have something I need to do
So though I take more steps from Ponyville
I know I will
I promise I'll always come right back home
But I have my friends
I swear I'm not alone