It's been a while to~day
Since I last saw your face
Though ticking time creeps on so fast
Dark is the shadow cast
A light spills through anyway
Cutting through my dark dismay
I don't need your permission
Won't be held to your disposition
Are you~ proud~ of choices you've~ made
Do you~ smile~ on the path you take
Though the road has been long~, my time has come
Make a choice~
Do you know what's right
Is their pain worth a coat of glowing fur
It's time that you decide
Make a choice
Or else they'll choose a path for you
Will you just stand idly by
Or can you stand to do what you have to~
Fillies mares and colts
It seems our path is set
Though I can't fix what was
I'll keep~ on looking for~ward because~
While you look at me
With eyes telling stories
Mares~ like me can't be trusted
Those tales need to be readjusted
Are you~ proud~ of choices you've~ made
Do you~ smile~ on the path you take
The time has come for me to
Make a choice
Do you know what's right
Is their pain worth a coat of glowing fur
It's time that you decide
Make a choice~
Do you know what's right
Is their pain worth a coat of glowing fur
It's time that you decide
Make a choice~
Or else they'll choose a path for you
Will you just stand idly by
Or can you stand to do what you have to~
Your words that held me down
Don't matter in the end~
I'll turn this world around
You can continue to pretend
That showing them your heart~
Is something you can't do
I'll show them that there's love
When showing love's all you refuse