I saved a ro-ow even though
I know it wo-on't be taken
I thought at fi-irst you'd never go
I was so-o mi-istaken
I was told
Life won't last fore-ever
But I've go-one beyond the ma-arker
What's one to-o do
How's one to-o fee-ee-eel
Where's one to-o go-o when their heart won't open?
So far away, yet so nearby-y-y
Feels as if so-omeone's still watching over me
So, here's to hoping
Nowada-ays, I pick and choose
My circumstances
I don't belie-ieve that fate is up
For giving se-eco-ond chances
If I'm right
Time goes on fore-ever
Feels like there's so-o much to remember
What's one to-o do
How's one to-o feel
Where's one to-o go-o when their heart won't open?
So far away, yet so-o nearby-y
Feels as if so-omeone's still watching over me
So here's to
Holding o-on to a little-e faith
Keeping u-up with the present day
Standing we-ell with the friends I-I made
Making su-ure that I do-on't lose my-y way
What's one to-o do
How's one to-o feel
Where's one to-o go-o when their heart won't open?
So far away, yet so nearby-y-y
Feels as if so-omeone's still watching over me
So, here's to hoping