Looking back on a hard working day
Feeling the warmth of the sun on my face
Laying back down with my head on the grass
Watching the clouds as they pass
The moon shines bright in the night
And the stars they remind me of you
And the great things we do
A thousand colours decorate these trees
Feeling the wind~ as it blows through the leaves
You're family and I know you know that
So won't you rely on me
Won't you rely on
Make yourself at home
Please don't feel alone
I'll be here with open arms waiting
When you're~ out there feeling lonеly
Just know that you have a family
Waiting for you
Waiting on hand to help you see things through
Thesе fields of green
They echo wi-ith
A voice in the sky
A voice in the sky-y
Trust in me
I know you ca-an
I won't tell a lie
I won't tell a lie~
You know that I'll always be straightforward with you
'Cause honestly that's honesty
Hold on to me, never let go
Everything will be okay
Just keep moving forward
And I know we'll see a brighter day
They say honesty is the best policy
And that sounds like the truth to me
When you're~ out there feeling lonеly
Just know that you have a family
Waiting for you
Waiting on hand to help you see things through
Thesе fields of green
They echo wi-ith
A voice in the sky
A voice in the sky-y
Trust in me
I know you ca-an
I won't tell a lie
I won't tell a lie~
You know that I'll always be straightforward with you
'Cause honestly that's honesty
Thesе fields of green
They echo wi-ith
A voice in the sky
A voice in the sky-y
Trust in me
I know you ca-an
I won't tell a lie
I won't tell a lie~
Fields of green
They echo wi-ith
A voice in the sky-y
Trust in me
I know you ca-an
I won't tell a lie
I won't tell a lie~
You know that I'll always be straightforward with yo-o-o-ou
'Cause honestly that's honesty~