I used to hide myself away
From the cloudy skies of gray
I didn't laugh I didn't know how
But all that's behind me now
No clouds today the sky is clear
Just laugh to make them disappear
I was going to bring cupcakes
But I ate them all so-o
I put balloons in my basket
And watched them float away
I hope that it fills you with laughter
And sweeps your fears away
I put balloons in my basket
It usually gets a laugh or two
It's much more fun when it's unexpected
I threw this party just for you
I know that I'm hard to understand
Sometimes I don't even get myself
But where's the fun thinking so-o hard?
Let's just go roll on the ground
The-ere's lots of other things that I'd rather do
eating lots of sugary things with you
Ice cream candy pie and chocolate rain
ignore the crowd they just think we're insane
run into the forest just to laugh at the trees
then run back out while giggling at the ghostly
there's Evil enchantress
who does evil dances
when you look deep in her eyes she puts you in the punch bowl
I put balloons in my basket
And watched them float away
I hope that it fills you with laughter
And sweeps your fears away
I put balloons in my basket
It usually gets a laugh or two
It's much more fun when it's unexpected
I threw this party just for you
I-I may seem so very crazy
When I say my tail makes the future less ha-azy
but come along with me-e and I'm sure you'll find
falling pianos won't get you when you're right behind me
All it really takes is a cup of flour
and suddenly you're going ninety miles an hour
everypony thinks I'm annoying sometimes
but they all agree my parties are really fun times
Learning how to laugh at your flaws is part of the fun
but I don't laugh at anyone
I'm energetic sympathetic there when you need me
silly ponies who don't listen get eaten by the parasprites
Candy cakes and pies o-oh my-y
where were you when I was kickin' it with Fluttergu-uy?
with a twitchin' twitch twitch Twi fell into a ditch
I got knocked into a bush with a bump from Flutterbitch
I wouldn't trade my sense of humor
for all the sugar in the world
cause I'm the partyingest pony in town
stick with me and I'll show you how to rock that frown
Upside down
I put balloons in my basket
And watched them float away
I hope that it fills you with laughter
And sweeps your fears away
I put balloons in my basket
It usually gets a laugh or two
It's much more fun when it's unexpected
I threw this party just for you