It's quite the lack of
Common sense to be out this far
Especially since nobody will know where you are~
Lost deep, inside the Everfree
An easy pray for those that hide behind~ the trees~
Do you feel it in the air?
The stench of which you can't compare
They sneak, they prowl, they hunt, they hunger
Soon you will be torn asunder
Always lurking in the shadows
Can't escape these living gallows
Run you might but find they will
You'll just be another kill
It's your demise, can't escape the eyes
Oh you're the prize of the Timberwolf
You can try and hide but it's just a soothing lie
Everybody dies to the Timberwolf
So here they come you better start running
Ah oh wow oh
Here they come you better start running
Oh oh wow oh
Ah oh wow oh
Here they come you better start running
Oh oh wow oh
What have we here?
Oh another poor lost soul
You've wandered out a bit to far from your cozy home~
Well pay no mind~, to the sounds that seem surround
There's not much you can do once you have entered their grounds
Can you sense it on the fringe?
Perceptions dull as minds unhinge
This panic grips and tightens hold
Your composure is swallowed whole
The final grains of sand now fall
Into their ever hungry jaws
Your life now theirs, you tear they tear
You're not going anywhere~~
It's your demise, can't escape the eyes
Oh you're the prize of the Timberwolf
You can try and hide but it's just a soothing lie
Everybody dies to the Timberwolf
Here they come you better start running
Ah oh wow oh
Oh oh wow oh
Here they come you better start running
Ah oh wow oh
Ohohwow oh
Flesh is tearing blood is spilling
Bones are breaking one by~ one
They'll eat until they have their filling
But you are not the only~ one
There's plenty others lost and waiting
For someone to hear their cry's
Just like all the ones before them
They go unanswered in the~ night
So if you find yourself uncertain
And wandering without an aim
Take solace in the fact that you will
Never be afraid a~gain
'cause nevermore will you feel sorrow
And nevermore will you feel fear
Once they get their jaws around you
You'll shed your last and final~ tear
It's your demise, can't escape the eyes
Oh you're the prize of the Timberwolf
You can try and hide but it's just a soothing lie
Everybody dies to the Timberwolf
It's your demise, can't escape the eyes
Oh you're the prize of the Timberwolf
You can try and hide but it's just a soothing lie
Everybody dies to the Timberwolf~~~