She's on~ly a princess
In the eyes of the world
But she's~ my~ queen
She's a night~ at the cir~cus
Lemon ice cream swirl
'Cause she's so sweet
Like a field of roses~~
Like a melody
Sung by an angel choir
I had al~ways ima~gined
It was just my mind
But she's no~ dream
Bound as one we will stay
Close beside or far away
No one's ever gonna say~
You and I are just a game
Never wanders without me
Never drops his guard
And that's all right~~
Says he can't live with out me
Says I'm in his~ heart
But he's my life~
Like a reverent sol~dier
Like a guardian
Who's always looking out
Never thought I would find him
Or that he'd find~ me
But now he's mine
Bound as one we will stay
Close beside or far away
No one's ever gonna say~
You and I are just a game
Bound as one we will stay
Close beside or far away
No one's ever gonna say~
You and I are just a game
Just a game