Hello again~, did you really think you had me gone?
Hah, you know there is a place for every right you wrong
You thought your dreams would keep you far away from me
But I've been hearing your dead quiet plea, yeah
No, you're never coming out again-
Don't be so sure
You've heard me knocking on the other side of every door
I have been lurking far too deep within for you to see
But believe me now
I am coming free
It is true you have been lurking far within my soul
But you're in trouble now, I see you only 'cause you roll
You've had the best of me now for far too many years
But I'm growing stronger
I know your fears
Hah
You really think you got me there, well bless your soul
I've been doing this ever since you were a foal
I bet you're thinking there's something here that you can do
But your trying is pathetic
We will never be through
Your confidence alludes you
And you know that it's true
You keep on pulling the same tricks
And never think I'll learn
You're reigning ever shorter terms
And I can feel your grasp
It's fading just like all your dust into the blue~~~
You can try to fight me but I will always win
You're getting far too cheeky
You know I cannot lose
Your mind it will be mine
Just like all the other times
You claimed me many times before, that much is true
But I start to wonder is it I who beat you?
How dare you even say that
I'm the one who rules
I've been tying down your heart and mind
And wore them as my shoes
Yet here I stand again and I'm already renewed
Face it, you're the one who keeps on failing
I've been tearing at your soul
For more than twenty years
I've been beating on your mind
Just to drown you in your fears
You get weaker everytime I fight, and I get strong
I'm the ruler of my heart and mind
You're the one who's always been wrong
You're mine