(One, two, three, four!)
(Hey, hey!)
Tell me, tell me, what am I supposed to~ do?
Where's the manual to everything that's~ new?
I'm losing control
Anxiety takes its toll~~
Show me, show me, how to act and what to~ be
What's my part in all that's going on 'round~ me?
So foreign and strange
I'll never be the same
And I'm sure I'll see~ what~ this has done for me~
But now my shaking world is breaking, crumbling underneath~
I'll try to stand as tall as those before~
But I'm not there yet, and I wish that I~ were more
(Hey, hey!)
Make me, make me, into what would fit the~ part
When's the moment that my confidence might~ start?
I'm not feeling strong
I gotta keep movin' on
And I'm sure I'll see~ what this has done for me~
But now my shaking world is breaking, crumbling underneath~
I'll try to stand as tall as those before~
But I'm not there yet, and I wish that I~ were more
I'm sure I'll see~ what~ this has done for me~
But now my shaking world is breaking, crumbling underneath~
I'll try to stand as tall as those before~
But I'm not there yet, and I wish that I~ were
Not there yet and I wish that I~ were
Not there yet and I wish that I~ were more