Look
You've been a sarcastic
Sharp spastic
Smart-ass jerk for so long you've turned plastic
Now let me tell you there's another way to think of things
Instead of jaded and bitter the way you've hated things
This bile venomous enemy that you've had to be
It doesn't have to be this way
Because it's sad to see
There's a movement
Dude's getting attuned to the root of emotions
Saying the truth as improvement
I mean sincere from the heart's core
I mean bereft of the fear, and clearly far more
Say what you mean and truly mean what you say
They're honest with their words
And there's earnesty in their praise
Yeah, so raise 'em up for this way of thought
To wear your hearts on your sleeves is just saying a lot
And I ain't playing, 'cause Rhyme Flow is saving a spot
The New Sincerity plan that I'm aiming to rock
The world that we can see
It shows no authenticity
We want transparency
Without the snidey irony
No shallow vanity
We value our humanity, yeah
Let us set it free
A kind of New Sincerity
Get in your head and don't bet on the bad
Abandon the fad
Embed in your mind
Prepare to be glad
I was jaded as the next man, just glaringly mad
I carried the past on my shoulders
Despairingly sad
But
I found I felt the fear falling away
I'll call it decay
Appallingly lost
Not sorry to say
This sincerity apparent in me
This caring in me
Just staring at me right in the face
Just daring to be
So
I let it go
I let it fly
I let the truth from the soul I was holdin' inside
And I can tell you it's a blessing and a gift
Because the weight pressing on my heart
It started to lift
And started to drift
This anger I wore
It started to rip
And beneath spoke a genuine part of the script
It said:
"Be true to yourself, be honest and kind
This new sincerity inherently is brought in the mind"
Yeah
The world that we can see
It shows no authenticity
We want transparency
Without the snidey irony
No shallow vanity
We value our humanity, yeah
Let us set it free
A kind of New Sincerity, yo
The world that we can see
It shows no authenticity
We want transparency
Without the snidey irony
No shallow vanity
We value our humanity, yeah
Let us set it free
A kind of New Sincerity