Well, I can see the food situation
Well, I'm just here to check the decor- decorations
Well, I'm here to supervise the preparations for the
Summer Summer Sun Cele-Sun Celebration
Sorry, we have an awful lot to do
You see, this prophecy must not come true
I 'unno, gettin' busy gettin' busy gettin' ready for the
Summer Summer Sun Cele- Sun Celebration
Spike! Spike?
Over here!
Ugh! That's just it, my dear
The day after tomorrow is the thousandth year of the
Summer Summer Sun Celebra-Celebration
Find me the copy of predictions and prophecies
Time to learn more about the Elements of Harmony
Spike? Take a note, please, quick
Send it. Now? Of course!
He's so sweepy, he can't even keep his bawance!
Keep his widduw bawance, bawa-
We can't just waste an opportunity to find out our talents
Find out our- find out our
Fii--ind out our ta~~~~
He's so sweepy, he can't even keep his bawance!
Keep his widduw ba~~~~~~~~~~~
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
~~~~~~
Find out our talents
Find out our- find out our
Find out our- o~~~~~~~~~~~
A~~~~~~~~~~~~~
O~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
Sorry, we have an awful lot- uation
Well, this prophecy must not come true!
I 'u- well, gettin' busy gettin' busy gettin' ready for the
Summer Summer Sun Cele- Sun Celebration!
Sorry, Spike?
Over here!
Ugh, this prophecy must not come true!
I 'u- day after tomorrow is the thousandth year of the
Summer Summer Sun Cele- Sun Celebration
Find me the copy of predictions and prophecies
Well- to learn more about the
Elements of- preparation
Well- take a note, please, quick
Send it. Now? Of course! Celebration