The second chan~ces came~ and they wrote my~ past~ away
But it all~ comes back again, again~
All the ho~llow faces and lonely hearts~ from the days~ I fal~tered
And the fight in their eyes~~~~
If the castle should come down~, will I fall~~~
Will I se~ver right~ from~ wrong, after all~~~
I'm~ afraid~ I left my heart~ back on the throne~~~~~
Can I do~ this on~~ my~ own
Have I~ grown~~~~~~~~~~
How am I~ to know if I'm ready for~~ the rest~
You know the mind's~ a fickle thing
I~ know~~
And as time has~ told~, I don't have~ hold~ on the roads~ I~ fo~llow~~~
And I don't trust myself to take~~ control~~
If the castle should come down~, will I fall~~~
Will I se~ver right~ from~ wrong, after all~~~
I'm~ afraid~ I left my heart~ back on the throne~~~~~
Can I do~ this on my own~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
And I know~~, I've been lost in~ my~ own~ glow~~~
It could all~ come back~ again~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
When we're~ down to the wire, will I hold~ onto my~ old~ ways~~
I don't know~~, and it shows~
Oh~~~~
Who am I~
Can you see~ to my soul~~
Am I clean~, or am I~
Just the vi~llain we all know~~