Create a fantastic sound, filters turned on
Twist handles all around, worries are gone
Wub-wub-wubbing to the drop
Track is hard, you'll never stop to
make them feel the beat, it's all you want
(You) set volume to the max, so they can dance
Neon lights are shining bright, putting in trance
Crazy ponies on the street
Hearts are beating to this beat and
everything for them stopped making sense
You never know if ponies like your song
But you just need the party to go
on and on and on
And oooooon!
Vinyl! Get up tonight! Look at the
moonlight dancing to your music
Vinyl! Don't let it die! The city
loves your beat, you cannot lose it
Vinyl! Turn on the lights! You're like a
shooting star fell from the sky
For ponies on the floor
To keep the beat alive!
Thousand ponies on the floor, a huge success
Even royalties are here, you're always stressed
Break it down, DJ-P0N3.
You'll never happen to be free
Without you party will just go to waste
You never know if ponies like your song
And sometimes you just want to be alone
You'd like to come back home where you belong
But you just need the party to go on
And on and on! Yeah!
They love your tracks so much, you know that they're sincere
And every time you see this crowd, you shed a tear
But you deserve it so get used to it, my dear
And have no fear
And have no fear!
Vinyl! Get up tonight! Look at the
moonlight dancing to your music
Vinyl! Don't let it die! The city
loves your beat, you cannot lose it
Vinyl! Turn on the lights! You're like a
shooting star fell from the sky
For ponies on the floor
To keep the beat alive!
To keep the beat alive yeah-eah!
To keep beat alive. Sing it!
Vinyl!
Vinyl! Get up tonight! Look at the
moonlight dancing to your music
Vinyl! Don't let it die! The city
loves your beat, you cannot lose it
Vinyl! Turn on the lights! You're like a
shooting star fell from the sky
For ponies on the floor
To keep the beat alive!
To keep the beat alive
A~live!