We were holding the skein
Its thread was fleeing mad~ly
And our eyes
Opened up on infinity
No landmark and no limit
Seen almost without seeing
Its water current jour~ney
In our ending world's crumpling
Strings of all our dreams
Being torn apart
Carried a~way by the storm
Dispersed into time~
But what are we befalling
What are all those co~lors
Which suddenly burn ourworld
Eternity turned upside~down
All alone, weaving our dreams
Alone in quiet cold~ness
With no dawn and no twilight
Without todays or yesterdays
Our reign was our everything
There were neither borders nor elsewhere
Yes, we waited without waiting
'Cause nothing was underneath
What were those steps in the sand
On which we’ve always walked~
In this dry desert
Where no sound and no laughter
Never no, nothing was heard
Powerful yet emp~ty
Without a laugh's melody
Without a heart'swarmth~
With no dawn and no twilight
We were queens and yet nothing
Because what is yesterday
Today or tomor~row
But what is this blinding light
What are those colors
Softnesses upon us
Could almost make our heart sing?
Everything flows, mixed up
Carrying away in a torrent of disorder
Past, present, fu~ture
What was frozen be~fore
Disappeared to day~~
Is it the foreseen end?
Is it for tomorrow?
Would everything be lost
Because we found this warm light
In our heart
That which is called friend~ship?
What will be of our reign
Where nothing ever happened?
Is it a new dawn~?
Is it a new destiny?
We didn't know we were on our own…
We didn’t know we were on our own…
We were on our own…