This day is going to be perfect
The kind of day of which I've dreamed since I was small
All those armor loving bores
Say I look great in uniform
What they don't know is that I have fooled them all
This day was going to be perfect
The kind of day of which I've dreamed since I was small
But instead of having cake
With all my friends to celebrate
My wedding bells may never ring for me at all
I care not a thing about the ring
I won't partake in any cake
Vows? Well I'll be lying when I say~
That through any kind of weather
I'll want us to be together
The truth is I don't care for her at all
No, I do not love the bride
For my heart is dead inside
But I still want her to be mine
We must escape before it's too late
Find a way to save the day
Hope? I'd be lying if I say~
I don't fear that I may lose her
To one who wants to use her
Not care for, love and cherish her each day
For I oh so love the bride
Oh, in my heart she does reside
Oh, Princess Ca~dance, I'll soon be by your side
Finally, the moment has arrived
For me to take a very lucky bride
Oh, the wedding we won't make
She'll end up marrying a fake
Princess Cadance will be
Mine
All mine