This is our big night
We're getting ready
And we're doing it up right
This is our big night
Friendship survived,
Now we'll start it out right
The time's right
Gonna make it last
'cause it's the first night
That we're ever gonna
Start to just have fun together
We're so glad, so happy
We could never be mad
Did it right, now
This is our big night now
Six friends on the way up no-o-o-ow
Six friends here to show you ho-o-o-ow
This is our big night
We're getting ready
And we're doing it up right
This is our big night
We made it happen
Now let's party all night
We're here now
And we worked so hard
To make it come around to tonight
So let's try to make it last forever
The school lights so bright,
Beat is pumping through the night
Party's starting, DJ's got the music just right
Six friends on the way up no-o-o-ow
Six friends here to show you ho-o-o-ow
This is our big night
We're getting ready
And we're doing it up right
This is our big night
We made it happen
Now let's party all night
This is our big ni-i-ight