It's just so-o simple, a si-imple~ song
But not~ so simply beautiful as you are
No, not~ by far
One~ plus one isn't yoou a-and I,
'Cause I'm~ just one and you catch every eye
Fluttershy
Listen to the music in the sky
Feel it flowing through you as you fly
Softly as a whispered lullaby
Fluttershy
Everypony says you don't sta-and out
Well~, now I know that they we-ere wrong
There's too many ways to describe yo-ou
So, I'll just sing you a bi-irdso-o-o-ong
Your way with creatures and ani-imals
And how yo-ou reach them, take the-em into your home
Nopo-ony knows
Your kindness may show them who-o yo-ou are
But they wi-ill never see the light or the sta-ars
You're bright as a star
Listen to the music in the sky
Feel it flowing through you as you fly
Softly as a whispered lullaby
Fluttershy
Everypony says you don't sta-and out
Well~, now I know that they we-ere wrong
None of your animals could te-ell yo-ou
But you can hear it in bi-irdso-o-o-o-ong
La, la, la la la la
Don't you hide
Don't yo-ou see?
Please don't hide fro-om me, fro-om me-e-e
Everypony says you don't sta-and out
We-ell, now I know that they we-ere wrong
There's too many ways to describe yo-ou
So, I'll just sing it in bi-irdso-o-o-o-ong
So, I'll just sing it in bi-irdso-o-o-o-ong (la la la la)
La, la, la la la la