Take on the rain~boom
Follow the way~ to
Open your eyes
And see new hori~zons
Fly up to Clouds~dale
Promise the wind's sail
Hoping to feel~
The soft colors glow
When I~ feel~ the~ arid sun~ set
And the world's but a silhouette
I just can't help but feel
I'd rather~ be danc~ing with~
Pepper~mint Po~nies
Peppermint Ponies~~
Oatmeal~ and rai~sins
Blue par~ty can~nons
Feeling~ so grand
With hooves in the sand~
Rocking~ the sun~set
Life doesn't end, yet
All of~ the things
That show the way home
When I~ feel~ the~ arid sun~ set
And the world's but a silhouette
I just can't help but feel
I'd rather~ be danc~ing with~
Pepper~mint Po~nies
Peppermint Ponies~~
All you have to do is take a cup of flour~
Flour~, flour~
Then you take a little something sweet not sour~
Sour~, sour~
All you have to do is take a cup of flour~
Flour~~~
Then you take a little something sweet not sour~
With Pepper~mint Po~nies
Peppermint
Peppermint Po~nies~
Po~nies
With Pepper~mint Po~nies
Peppermint Ponies~
Pepper~mint Po~nies
Ponies~~