You could be a light in the dead of the night
Instead of searching for the light yourself
Reflecting on the moments you~ lost
The moments you thought
Would finally be~ the e~~nd
Searching for the li~ght in the dead of the night
When I could light the way for someone else
Forgetting all the moments I~ lost
The more that I~ thought
I'd never see~ the e~~nd
And now the timing is right
Stepping into the light
You've finally found a way to be yourse~lf
I realize that I needed this road
I needed to~ know
I'd find it i~n the e~~nd
Whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-oh
So here we are!
I was starting to~ believe that we would never get this fa~r
But here we are!
There's no turning back now, we're further than the sta~~rs
And here we are!
After searching a~ll those years, we've finally found our destiny~
So here we are!
And we'll make a~ ne~w mark by helping others see~~
See who they really want to be!
Time moves fast if you're too busy to watch it go
But I remember the years by realizing all we didn't know
These young eyes looking all around for something bigger than we could see
But no doubt could ever slow us down
Drawn by the promise of eventually
Drawn by the promise of eventually~~
And now the timing is right
Stepping into the light
You've finally found a way to be yourse~lf
I realize that I needed this road
I needed to~ know
I'd find it i~n the e~~nd
Whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-oh
So here we are!
I was starting to~ believe that we would never get this fa~r
But here we are!
There's no turning back now, we're further than the sta~~rs
And here we are!
After searching a~ll those years, we've finally found our destiny~
So here we are!
And we'll make a~ ne~w mark by helping others see~~
See who they really want to be!