Well I used to be a farmer and I made a living fine
I had a little stretch of land along the C.P. Line
But times went by, and though I tried, the money wasn't there
And the bankers came and took my land, and told me "fair is fair"
I looked for every kind of job, the answer always no
"Hire you now?," they'd always laugh, "we just let twenty go!"
The government, they promised me a measly little sum
But I've got too much pride to end up just another bum
Then I thought, who gives a damn if all the jobs are~ gone
I'm gonna be a pirate on the river Saskatchewan~
And it's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores
Well, you'd think the local farmers would know that I'm at large
But just the other day I found an unprotected barge
I snuck up right behind them and they were none the wiser
I rammed their ship and sank it, and I stole their fertilizer
A bridge outside of Moose Jaw spans a mighty river
Farmers cross in so much fear their stomachs are a-quiver
'Cause they know that Captain Tractor's hidin' in the bay
I'll jump the bridge and knock 'em cold and sail off with their hay
And it's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores
Well, Mountie Bob, he chased me, he was always at my throat
He followed on the shoreline, 'cause he didn't own a boat
But the cutbacks were a-coming, and the Mountie lost his job
So now he's sailing with me and we call him Salty Bob
A swinging sword, a skull-and-bones, and pleasant company
I never pay my income tax and screw the G.S.T.
Sailin' down the Saskatoon, the terror of the sea
If y'all wanna reach the Co-op, boy, you gotta get by me!
Ah ah!
It's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores
Well the pirate life's appealing but you don't just find it here
I hear in north Alberta there's a band of buccaneers
They roam the Athabasca from Smith to Fort McKay
And you're gonna lose your Stetson if you have to pass their way
Well, winter is a-coming and a chill is in the breeze
My pirate days are over once the river starts to freeze
But I'll be back in springtime, but now I have to go
I hear there's lots of plundering down in New Mexico
And it's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores
And it's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores
And it's a heave-ho, high-ho, coming down the Plains
Stealing wheats and barley and all the other grains
And it's a ho-hey, high-hey, farmers bar your doors
When you see the Jolly Roger on Regina's mighty shores