My return is a mystery
Thought you had control of me
I'm offended that you're so surprised
That first defeat was a practice round
But I pulled myself off the gro-ound
And I've already planned your demise
I won't stop fighting cause I'm not done yet
You're gonna regret
This time I won't let you forget
You're not gonna get away this ti-ime
I'll strike when you're blind
You'll awake just to find you are mine
You thought you won
Thought the battle was over
But I, I
I, I’m just getting stronger
Enjoy your freedom
It won't last much longer
Cause I, I
I, I keep getting stronger
When the sky turns to gre-ey
When the light fades awa-ay
You will say I just keep getting stronger
I just keep getting stronger
You can try to prepa-are
Or attack if you da-are
I don't care, cause I'm just getting stronge-e-er
Oh!
I, I
I, I’m just getting stronger
I, I’m just getting stronge-e-er
Cause I, I
I, I’m just getting stronger
I, I… just getting stronger
I am the nightmare that replays in your head
I am the shadow lurking under your bed
And when I lose it's never really the end
You should have known I'd have a plan for revenge
And I won't stop fighting cause I'm not done yet
You're gonna regret
This time I won't let you forget
You're not gonna get away this ti-ime
I'll strike when you're blind
You'll awake just to find you are mine
You thought you won
Thought the battle was over
But I, I… just getting stronger
I, I’m just getting stronger
Enjoy your freedom
It won't last much longer
Cause I, I
I, I keep getting stronge-e-e-er
When the sky turns to gre-ey
When the light fades awa-ay
You will say, I just keep getting stronger
Stronger every day
Stronger every da-ay
I, I keep getting stronger
I, I keep getting stronge-e-e-er
Ca-ause I, I keep getting stronger
I, I keep getting stronger
I, I keep getting stronge-er
I, I keep getting stronge-e-e-er