So here we are
The last goodbye
If only I could find some perfect phrase
To make you laugh
To make you cry
To bring you joy~ before I fade~ away
But in the end
We're just pretend
Some fleeting thoughts~ before the dark~ of sleep
But I can feel
So I am real
So let's escape~ before we're~ in~ too deep
So take~~~ me back to where it all began
And if you wait~~~
Then you will hear it all again
The innocence in my heart
When I had all my life ahead
But every song that we start
It has to end~
Woah oh oh wow oh
Woah oh oh
Raise your hands just one more time~
Woah oh oh wow oh
Oh oh oh wow oh wow
I'll see you in some other life
Woah oh oh wow oh
Woah oh oh wow oh woah
The atmosphere is raining light
Woah oh oh wow oh
Oh oh oh wow oh woah
I'll see you in some other life
We're setting sail
Across the sky
The constella~tions they will be~ our guide
And suddenly
Our promises
Are just a me~lody that slipped our mind
But maybe we
Will meet again
When all the stars~ align a path someday
But as we are
The scattered stars
Are spreading us~ across the Milky Way
Life's a par~ty pounding in a heartbeat
That's all I know
But if you listen real close
Every beat will heal~ those
Scars on your soul
'Cause oh
Life it hurts but in the end it's worth it
Joy through the tears
The years they say goodbye
With memories that try~ to
End all your fears
End all your fears~
Woah oh oh wow oh
Woah oh oh
Raise your hands just one more time
Woah oh oh wow oh
Oh oh oh wow oh woah
I'll see you in some other life
Woah oh oh wow oh
Woah oh oh wow oh woah
The atmosphere is raining light
Woah oh oh wow oh
Oh oh oh wow oh wow
I'll see~ you~ in some other life
Oh I am sailing~ on
I'm sailing on
Goodbye to all I've~ known~~~
To all I've~ known
And I~ will wait for~ you
I'll whisper out across the galaxy
"I'll see you~ soon"
Oh oh woah
Oh oh oh
Woah oh oh
Oh oh woah
Oh oh oh
I have changed, I have grown
Now I am on~ my own~~~
Knowing now who I'll be
I am free