I'm not a fan of puppeteers, but I've a nagging fear
Someone else is pulling at the strings
Something terrible is going down
Through the entire town
Wreaking anarchy and all it brings
I can't sit i-idly, no-o, I can't move at all
I curse the name
The one behind it a-a-a-a-all
Discord, I'm howlin' at the moon
And sleepin' in the middle of a summer afternoon
Discord, whatever did we do
To make you take our world away?
Discord, are we your prey alone
Or are we just a stepping stone for taking back the throne
Discord, we won't take it anymore
So take your tyranny away!
I'm fine with changing status quo, but not in letting go
Now the world is being torn apart
A terrible catastrophe
Played by your symphony
What a terrifying work of art
I can't sit i-idly, no-o, I can't move at all
I curse the name
The one behind it a-a-a-a-all
Discord, I'm howlin' at the moon
And sleepin' in the middle of a summer afternoon
Discord, whatever did we do
To make you take our world away?
Discord, are we your prey alone
Or are we just a stepping stone for taking back the throne
Discord, we won't take it anymore
So take your tyranny away!
Discord, I'm howlin' at the moon
And sleepin' in the middle of a summer afternoon
Discord, whatever did we do
To make you take our world away?
Discord, are we your prey alone
Or are we just a stepping stone for taking back the throne
Discord, we won't take it anymore
So take your tyranny away!