In the light that falls at moonrise
In the rhythm of the rain
In the miracle of o-ordinary days
In the hush of night
I will be in the whispers of lovers
Every-ywhere
You will find me there
In the rustle of a curtain
In the bustle of the-e world
In a tho-ousand little unexpected ways
When you lift your gaze
I will be like the shimmer of o-one small star
O-out there
Shining everywhere
I will be there
Besi-ide you
Through the lo-onely nights that fall
So close your eyes
Reme-ember my embrace
I will be there
Like me-ercy
I will fi-ind you through it a-all
This do I swear
I wi-ill be there
In a language never spoken
With the promises we made
In the endless low that owns me heart and soul
In the certainty
I will always be true and as near as my next prayer
You will find me there
In the echo o' the ocean
In the haunting of the wind
In mysterious extraordinary ways
Through the darkest sky
I will be like the shimmer of one small star
O-out there
Shining everywhere
I will be there
Besi-ide you
Through the lo-onely nights that fall
So close your eyes
Reme-ember my embrace
I will be there
Like free-eedom
I will find you through it a-all
This do I swear
I will be there
In the harbour quarter
In the sto-one and mortar
In the star that we both share
In the sound of laughter
Now and e-ever after
Look for me I will be there
I WILL BE THERE
BESI-IDE YOU
THROUGH THE LO-ONELY NIGHTS THAT FALL
SO CLOSE YOUR EYES
REME-EMBER MY EMBRACE
REMEMBER MY EMBRA-ACE
I WILL BE THERE
I'LL BE THERE
LIKE JUSTICE
I WILL FIND YOU THROUGH IT A-ALL
This do I swear
I will be there