I know you're busy~ here~
But would it hurt to take a break my dear~?
You're working yourself mindless~
You'll drive yourself in~sane
You're pent up all~ alone
You're going down~ a lonely road~~
There's no shame in leaning~
On somepony else
So follow your sto~ry, follow your song
But follow your friends when the days get long~
Lay down your soul~ at the fireside
Lay down your bur~den and sing a~way your strife
All this time you've been alone~
You don't have to be~ alone~~~
Just let go your inhi~bitions now, enjoy yourself~~~
Let the magic fill~ your~ soul~~
I don't want you to change~
But maybe you could rearrange~
'Cause what fun's living life if you don't
Live it with some friends?
So you go your own way
But you'll look back on life one day~
And you'll see the wonders of being with others~
And wish you went out to play
Follow your sto~ry, follow your song
But follow your friends when the days get long~
Lay down your soul at the fireside
Lay down your bur~den and sing away your strife
All this time you've been a~lone~~
You don't have to be a~lone~~~, no
Just let go your inhi~bitions now, enjoy yourself~~~
Let the magic fill~ your~ soul~
Follow your sto~ry, follow your song~~
Follow your friends when your days get long
Lay down your soul at the fireside~~
Lay down your bur~den and sing away your strife
All this time you've been alone~~~~~~~~~~~~
You don't have to be a~lone~
Just let go your inhi~bitions now, enjoy your~self~
Let the magic fill your soul~~~
Follow your sto~ry, follow your song
But follow your friends when your days get long~
Lay down your soul at the fireside
Lay down your burden and sing away your strife
All this time you've been a~lone~~
You don't have to be a~lone~~~
Just let go your inhi~bitions now, enjoy yourself~~~
Let the magic fill your~ soul~~