My Little Pony, My Little Pony
What is friendship all about
Friendship is magic
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Until you all shared its magic with me
When I was young I was too
Busy to make any friends
Such silliness did not seem
Worth the effort it expends
But my Little Ponies
You opened up my eyes
And now the truth is crystal clear
As splendid su-ummer skies
And it's such a wonderful surprise
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Until you all shared its magic with me
When danger makes me wanna hide
You'll Rainbow Dash to-o my side
Kindness is never in short supply
Once smitten twice Fluttershy
For honesty nopony can deny
You are the Applejack of my eye
A heart that shines so beautiful
A Rarity to come by
And you all make fun and laughter
As easy as Pinkie Pie
My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Until you all shared its magic with me
Our friendship's magic and it's growing all the time
A new adventure waits for us
Each day is yours and mine
We'll make it special every time
What a wonderful wonder friendship brings
Do you know you're all my very be-est friends
You're my very best friends