OK, you know what you have to do, right?
Beg for help, then quit when I get frustrated
*glare*
Just kidding! Total opposite of that, got it
You think he can do it?
Everypony has times in their lives
When their hearts are filled with doubt
Frustration builds up inside
And it makes you wanna shout
Bu-ut if you just take that first step
The next one wi-ill appear
And you find you can walk, then run
Then fly-y-y
Into the stratosphere
You've got to give it your best
So you can pass the test
Give it everything that yo-u've go-ot
And we know you can win
You just have to begin
Have to give it your very best sho-ot
There are times when you wa-ant to give up
When you think that you can't go-o o-on
But if you fight through with all of your might
You will find that you can't go wrong
That you could do it all along
Everypony has ti-imes in their lives
When their hearts are filled with doubt
But if you just give it yo-ur all
You'll start to work it out
And I know I can't give up too soon
Get myself in the zone
And I find I can walk, then run
Then fly-y-y
I can do it on my own-ah
You can do it on your o-own
I can do it on my own
I did it!
I actually finished something
By myself!