OK, you know what you have to do, right?
*glare*
You think he can do it?
Everypony has times in their lives
When their hearts are filled with doubt
Bu-ut if you just take that first step
The next one wi-ill appear
And you find you can walk, then run
Then fly-y-y
Into the stratosphere
You've got to give it your best
So you can pass the test
Give it everything that yo-u've go-ot
And we know you can win
You just have to begin
Have to give it your very best sho-ot
But if you fight through with all of your might
You will find that you can't go wrong
That you could do it all along
Everypony has ti-imes in their lives
When their hearts are filled with doubt
But if you just give it yo-ur all
You'll start to work it out
Then fly-y-y
You can do it on your o-own