Ah yeah
Trapped in the frozen wastes
Another evil you must face
The Crystalline Kingdom reappeared
He will feast upon all your fears~
King Sombra will make everything burn
You must fight to stop his return
The empire of light was sealed away
Corruption and crystal decay
Evil ri~ses from its arctic pri~son
To realize it's apocalyptic vision
But with the Elements and Princess Ca~dance
The Crystal Heart will be charged to save~ us
He breaks through the barrier
As Her magic grows ti~red
The Crystal Fair from the start
Is the key to the Crystal Heart
Twilight is trapped by his cage
Countering the magic cast by the mage
Her dragon brings the Crystal our hope~~
Cadance, a missile, reclaims~~ her throne~~
Evil ri~ses from its arctic pri~son
To realize it's apocalyptic vision
But with the Elements and Princess Ca~~dance
The Crystal Heart will be charged to save~ us
Oh Oh~~~~~
Return to the shadows from where you came
Evil ri~ses from its arctic pri~son
To realize~ it's apocalyptic vision
But with the Elements and Princess Ca~~dance
The Crystal Heart will be charged to save~ us
To save us