Some days get the best of me
Sometimes I feel I'm givin' up~
Givin' up~~
I'm not who I wanna be
I know I'm not the only one~
Everybody needs somebody
I'm somebody too~
If you ever need somebo~dy
I'll be there for you~
Yeah
You know the truth is
We're not so different after all
Can you feel it~?
I need a friend too
I'll be here to catch you when you fall~
Can you feel it~?
'Cause we're~~~~ better
Together
We're~~~~ better
Together~
Some days get the best of me~
Sometimes I feel I'm not enough~
Not enough~~
That's not who I wanna be~
I know I'm not the only one~
Everybody needs somebody
I'm somebody too~
If you ever need somebo~dy
I'll be there for you~~~~
You know the truth is~
We're not so different after all
Can you feel it~?
I need a friend, too~
I'll be here to catch you when you fall
Can you feel it~?
'Cause we're~~~~ better
Together
Together~
We're~~~~ better
Together
Together~
Everybody needs somebody
I'm somebody too~
If you ever need somebody
I'll be there for you~~~
You know the truth is~
We're not so different after all~
Can you feel it~~~?
I need a friend too~
I'll be here to catch you when you fall~
Can you feel it~?
'Cause we're~~~~ better
Together
We're~~~~ better
Together~