Ooh~~
Ooh~~~
Welcome fillies and gentlecolts no reason to scream
Your fav'rite Princess is back she's walkin' up on the scene
She has been stuck on the moon but that's no reason to fret
She's not a Nightmare no more so buckle down and get set
She's comin' gracin' her subjects she ain't leavin' no choice
She's gonna blow you all back with her Equestrian Voice
So cover all of your fears and stow away all your fright
The Lunar Princess is back to bring the nightmares tonight
She's living in the past so you~ won't last
Without the proper care
With a royal farewell and an animate spell
You won't have long~ to prepare~~~~~
Ooh~~
Ooh~~~
Now little fillies this is Nightmare Night
Your ruler Nightmare Moon is back to come and fill you with fright so hurry
Now get your goodies and fill up all your bags
Go and leave a candy offering for that big ol' hag get runnin'
And pray above that she's not comin' back
To come and take away your soul and eat you up for a snack
So run away and go hide just keep your head out of sight
The darkness is rising again cause this is Nightmare Night
She's living in the past so you~ won't last
Without the proper care
With a royal farewell and an animate spell
You won't have long~ to prepare~~~~~
Ooh
Ooh~~
Ooh~~~