The night is getting darker
And the full moon is in the sky
In the distance you hear a howl
And a blood-curdling cry
You think it's probably just the wind
But then something else happens
Something that makes you think again
There's something moving
Out through the night
You got that sickly sinking feeling
That something isn't right
You run to find a shelter
Locking the door
But behind you there's a shadow
Crawling 'cross the floor
You turn to scream
It seems a little mean
Knees are shaking, cold sweat
And your hearts are racing
Those claws, those teeth
Who's that underneath?
Is that a hedgehog?
Your eyes can't believe
He's been wolf-i-fied!
You better fly
Cause there's no one here to save you
And you can not deny
He's been wolf-i-fied!
Just say goodbye
Cause there's no place left to run to
There's no place left to hi-ide
You think you made it
Running out the back
But you better think again
Because something's on your track
You run into a corner
Turn to see who's there
Now there's almost half a dozen
That seems a bit unfair!
You turn to scream
Get something in between
Knees are shaking, cold sweat
And your hearts are racing
Those claws, those teeth
Who's that underneath?
Are those your friends there?
Your eyes can't believe
They've been wolf-i-fied!
No need to try
Cause there's no one here to save you
And you can not deny
We've been wolf-i-fied!
Just say goodbye
Cause there's no place left to run to
There's no place left to hi-ide
Wolf-i, wolf-i-fied!