You taste like sugar
Wrapped up with a pretty bow~
I'm saying "yes"~
All I hear from you is "no"~
And I wanna take you dancing~~~
But you won't move for a crowd~
And you're kinda whispering~~~
When I wanna say it loud~
Loud, loud~~~~~
Don't say you want me
When you leave~ me
I won't let go
(I won't let go~)
I will always follow
Where you lead~ me
Please say it's so
Woah~ oh wow oh
I won't let go~
You pull my heartstrings
Without knowing how to play~
I'm watching, waiting
On every word you might say~
And I wanna hold you close now~~
But you're too damn refined~
And I'm losing all control now~~
What is on your mind~
Mind~, mind~~~~~~?
Don't say you want me
When you leave~ me
I won't let go
(I won't let go~)
I will always follow
Where you lead~ me
Please say it's so
Woah~ oh wow oh
I won't let go~
You take me~
You break me~
You break~ me~
You take~ me~
You break me~
Don't say you want me
When you leave~ me
I won't let go
(I won't let go~)
I will always follow
Where you lead~ me
Please say it's so
Woah~ oh wow oh
I won't let go~