Ooh Bonnie
I've been trying to escape
From this stupid fucking phase I call love
Oh Bonnie
Won't you show me how to live?
I've been under a rock since I was a filly
Ooh~-ooh
Oh Bonnie
Do you remember who I am?
You picked me up when I was at my lowest
Oh no
Ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh-uh
Get home at seven PM
Nothing to do
Been getting fucked up at school again
Just wanna talk to you
It's been practice, practice, practice
For the recital coming up
But I'd rather be online
'Cuz I don't really give a fuck~
Ooh Bonnie
Won't you show me how to live?
I've been under a rock since I was a filly
Ooh~ooh
Oh Bonnie
Do you remember who I am?
You picked me up when I was at my lowest~~
Oh no
Oh Bonnie~
Oh Bonnie~~
Bonnie~~
Oh Bonnie~
Oh Bonnie~~
Bonnie~~
Ooh
I've been~ thinking about you since you left
You said we'd be best friends
But you're stuck in my head~
Oh won't you call me back
Secret Agent Sweetie Drops
Let's forget this whole facade
My lovely lesbian hotshot
Ooh~, please just call me back~
Oh~, oh~~
Let's just dance together~~~
It'll be alright~~~
Oh~~~~~~
Did you ever read the letters I sent?
I left them on your desk when we were young
I've felt this way for a really long time
But I was so scared, so scared~~
Am I normal? Is this feeling right?
It's hard to keep on living when I see no light
For a whilele I had asked, should I fucking~ die?
Oh who am~ I? Will I live tonight~?
I wish it were easy to tell you
The demons I face when I sleep at night
I just want to look after the soul you've let decay
If you won't love yourself let me hold~ you and stay~
I remember
I remem~ber
So let me try again
Let me live again~