Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh
Jollity forever shown
Path of joy so few have known
Sincerity and emphasis
So truly seen in happiness
With one mind, we can make, we can live
With a life, one can take, one can gi~~ve
We rejoice lending all we possess
With a voice, one can lift or depress
Jollity forever shown
Path of joy so few have known
Sincerity and emphasis
So truly seen in happiness
In happiness
In this dream, there is no~ room for spite
Still it seems, only I can deci~~de
I am lost but am free of the~ world
For outside,~ all is bleak, all is cold
Jollity forever shown
Path of joy so few have known
Sincerity and emphasis
So truly seen in happiness
Jollity forever shown
Path of joy so few have known
Sincerity and emphasis
So truly seen in happiness
In happiness
Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh Ooh
Giggle