I fear I told a little fib
About my pony past
I hope that when you hear the truth
You will not be aghast
I wasn't quite the super party pony like I claimed
The fact is that I was so shy
Nopony knew my-y name
I stumbled into Ponyville
One afternoon by chance
And found the biggest ever celebration party dance
Everything was perfect
Cheer was filling up the place
And I saw that everypony had
A smile upon their face
I vowed that day to change my life
The past I did set free
For now Cheese Sandwich was
A party pony full of glee
A super duper party pony
That's what I became
I traveled all Equestria
And all did know my name
But that never would have happened on my own
I'll tell you why
For the one who threw that party
It was you, Pinkie Pie