Are you a real Pinkie?
Well, uh… I dunno
Have you ever played a prank, like, uh, a practical joke?
Nope
Have you ever worn a silly costume?
Naahh nope…
Alright! I can see that I'm gonna have to teach you how to be Pinkies!
Fun!
We are Pinkie Pies!
Now listen closely
Here's a little lesson in Pinkery
This is going down in history
If you wanna be a Pinkie Number One
You have to chase a silly filly on the run
Just follow my moves, and sneak around
Be careful not to make a sound
Shh
Ooooh
No, don't touch that!
We are Pinkie Pies!
Fun!
Ha ha ha
Now look at these horns
That I just found
When I say go~, be ready to blow
Blow!
Blow 'em at her, not me!
Ugh, let's try something else
Now watch and learn
Here's~ the deal
She'll slip and slide on this banana peel!
Ha ha ha, gasp!
What are you doing‽
Fun!
Ba, ba-ba-badapa-ba ba, ba-ba-ba-ba ba ba ba ba
We are Pinkie Pies
Fun!
Ba, ba-ba-badapa-ba ba, ba-ba-ba-ba ba ba ba ba
SHOW THAT PINKIE PRIDE!
Fun!
Ba, ba-ba-badapa-ba ba, ba-ba-ba-ba ba ba ba ba
We are Pinkie Pies
Ba, ba-ba-biddly-ba-ba ba, ba-ba-ba-ba ba ba ba ba
We are Pinkie Pies!
FUN!