A stage could not be better~ set~
We got to write our own history~
I held tight every other soul~
Who took part in the bliss with me~
We lived it up with no looking back~
Like we'd never again see the day~
A chapter written in our lives~
That nobody can take away~
Let it be known~ that far and wide~
We got to be who we are inside~
Goodbye all doubts and fear~
Let it be known~ that in the end~~
We recalled each smile~ and tear~
We never blew away with the wind~
Let it be known that we were here
Oh~ we were here~~~
Yeah we were here~~~
This place is perfect, take it with you~
Your port in an ever raging storm~
An embrace that time can't erase~
Where returning is true to form~
This is where we can come alive~
Where enemies shake hands and heal~
Where no matter what happens outside~
These few days will always be real~
Let it be known that far and wide~
We lit a flame that never died~
Goodbye all doubts and fear~
Let it be known that in the end~~
We recalled each smile~ and tear~
We never blew away with the wind~
Let it be known that we were here
Oh~ we were here~~~
Yeah we were here~~~
Remember, remember
Remember, remember that we were here~
Echoes that won't ever fade~
Stories of nights that we would never trade~
And long after~ my fate~ calls~
Remember the laughter held in these halls~
Goodbye all doubts and fear~
Let it be known~ that in the end~~
We recalled each smile~ and tear~
We never blew away with the wind~
Let it be known~ that we were here
Oh~ we were here~~~
Yeah we were here~~~
Yeah
Remember that we were here!