The little filly was all alone
She felt the wind and she longed to follow
"Her scrawny wings were too small" they said
"And she will never ascend like other"
But she looked up
And she spread her precious golden wings
And in her heart there burned a fi-re
Then she took to the sky!
Rising...
Soaring...
Dreaming...
Burning!
You'll never hold me back the Spirit of Fi-re
I am invincible, I'm flying, and I am free!
I'm never turning back, the Spirit of Fi-re
My dreams are all I need, my passion will be the key!
Spitfire~
Another pony at school was cruel
He thought that he was the greatest flyer
"You'll never win in a race with me"
"I will defeat you just try and see~"
She felt no fear
As she marched up to the starting line
And in her eyes, there burned a fi-re
Then she took to the sky!
Rising...
Soaring...
Dreaming...
Burning!
You'll never hold me back the Spirit of Fi-re
I am invincible, I'm flying, and I am free!
I'm never turning back, the Spirit of Fi-re
My dreams are all I need, my passion will be the key!
Spitfire~
You'll never hold me back the Spirit of Fi-re
I am invincible, I'm flying, and I am free!
I'm never turning back, the Spirit of Fi-re
My dreams are all I need, my passion will be the key!
Spitfire~