For every day
I look around me
For every time I se-e you near
I thank the stars
Whose light surrounds me
I thank the earth that keeps you here
'Cause I will only follow
My tru-e heart
And I can see it clear now
Right from the-e start
Yo-u we-re My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be
My Little Pony-y
Until you shared its magic with me
You saw the change
That we all needed
You saw how good that we could be
We'll never let little things come between us
Now that we found this destiny-y
And we can stand up tall now
To any hate
'Cause best friends stick together
We love and tolerate
My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be
My Little Pony-y
Until you shared its magic with me
If one falls do-own
We all come aro-und
Yeah, you're so-o-o-o free
To be anything,
Anything that you want to be-e, yeah
My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be-e
My Little Pony-y
Until you shared its magic with me-e
My Little Po-ony
I used to wonder what friendship could be-e
My little pony-y
Until you shared its magic wi-ith me-e