The farm's been doing fi-ine since the spring began
As good as any other year
Sales are goin' steady and we're working hard~~
Nothing's really changing here
I tend your garden every morn~ing
Just the way you taught me long ago
The flowers still remind me of the song~ you used to sing
When we were out there working hours~ all a~lone
What I wouldn't give to have you back for just a day
I miss the way you'd smile when I was~ scared
All I wanna say is that I hope that I can be
The shining star that you both were to me
Applebloom's a little bigger every day
Had no idea how quick she'd grow
Lately she's been learning who she wants to be~~
Could really use her mama though
Mac sings with a choir~ every Sunday
First thing that he's done since you've been gone
Granny's slowin' down but she's still every bit as strong
As the days when we'd throw horseshoes on the~ lawn
What I wouldn't give to have you back for just a day
I miss the way you'd smile when I was~ scared
All I wanna say is that I hope that I can be
The shining star that you both were to me
I wanna hear you tell me that you're proud~ of me
I wanna feel your warmth against my fur
I try to be the adult that I know~ that I should be
But it's hard to fill the hole where you two~ were~~
What I wouldn't give to have you back for just a day
I miss the way you'd smile when I was~ scared
All I wanna say is that I hope that I can be
The shining star that you both were to me