Cold winter fast approaches as we fearfully wait
The simplest of simple creatures bound by the laws of fate
As we shivered in the gutters
Far away from home~
We lost the last vestige of hope~
Freezing and alone
A shadow came to us in our dreams with tales of better times~
The royal Princess of the Night forgave us for our crimes
And as the Solar Sister overlooked us, nocturnal we became~
We wore a darker armor, and we carried a different flame
You now belong to a greater good
And you answer to a higher call!
You are part of the best and greatest
And there is no room for failure!
You will leave behind all weakness!
You are no longer a mortal!
You are now indestructible
Soldier of the Night!
As the sunset fades away, the yellow turns to grey~
The moonlight shines across the land, a calling we obey
The purest black of shadows rise to fight a greater fight
My brothers and sisters move as one, we Soldiers of the Night
We stand at arms before our liege, each one of us just a pawn~
Now we reign supreme throughout the dark, until the light of dawn
The memories we have left behind us might cripple lesser men
But those of us brought back from nothing have risen once again
We see it in her moonlit eyes, a fury held at bay
A battle waiting in the ashes, to resume~ another day
And as we disappear into the shadows, we fill their souls with dread
We fight tonight to rule tomorrow, and a dark day lies ahead
As the sunset fades away, the yellow turns to grey~
The moonlight shines across the land, a calling we obey
The purest black of shadows rise to fight a greater fight~
My brothers and sisters move as one, we Soldiers of the Night
The times we live in now have changed, honor is long gone
And now that good and evil are shades of grey~
A cruel impasse is drawn
For all the good we have created
It doesn't make us right
But those of us who hide in darkness
See a different kind of light
As the sunset fades away, the yellow turns to grey~
The moonlight shines across the land, a calling we obey
The purest black of shadows rise to fight a greater fight
My brothers and sisters move as one, we Soldiers of the Night
The times we live in now have changed~, honor is long gone
And now that good and evil are shades of grey~
A cruel impasse is drawn
For all the good we have created
It doesn't make us right~
But those of us who hide in darkness
See a different kind of light