Today I'll shine like I've never shone before
And I will show the princess that I'm ready for more
I'll dazzle her with magic, every spell~ that I've done
And I'll prove to her I'm ready for my place in the~ sun~
Today I'll be what I've never been before
And I will take to the sky~ spread my wings and soar
There's a brand new spark up in the sky~ today
And as sure as night is dark
We are on our way~
Today I'll rise with the upper~ crust
Fancy drinks, crystal glass
Cider is a must!
Clean your hooves, it's a big day!
Hold your horses, they're okay!
Sure as stubborn ponies squabble
We are on our way~
There'll be ponies laughing, ponies dancing, having so much fun!
I cannot wait to celebrate everything with everyone
All those thousands of ponies from every place under the sun!
Thousands of ponies? Really?
Of course!
The Prince and Princess are coming back!
It's the event of the century!
Pinkie!
Maybe I'll hide in a cupboard, lock the door-
There won't be thousands of ponies there by far-
Are you sure?
I could find a little corner I could use for a day
Don't listen to Pinkie Pie
She's gone off the hay!
And as sure as the Wonderbolt flies~
We are on our way
The bumpy road to Canterlot
Flying free!
Through dirt we'll trot!
And we'll party!
Maybe not!
And sure as the moon is grey~
We're on our way