We're in this together!
Looking back~ feels so bittersweet
I'd never imagine what we started
Could mean so much to me
It might be true we've
Passed the golden~ years
Well let them say what they want
I'll politely disagree
'Cause it doesn't mean much
If you're where you wanna be
So scream if you're out there
If things just ain't fair
Alone in a nightmare
We're not going anywhere
Don't tell me it's over
That all things have to end
I think we'll live forever
'Cause we're in this together
Hey!
Tell me where do we go from here
Do we just burn up and disappear
Hey!
Will you still be there stood next to me
Like you were back in 2013
Will they remember you~
When you're dead and gone
Let them ask you where you were
Show them you've been here all along
Will you remember me
When it's been so long
Will we fade to distant memories
Will I see you at the con?
Every time I
Look back at the place we all came from
Familiar faces one by one
Seems everypony's movin' on
Every step I take
Feels like someone gets left behind
But it's their choice and that's okay
We'll keep that fire burning bright
Don't tell me it's over
That all things have to end
I think we'll live forever
'Cause we're in this together
Hey!
Tell me where do we go from here
Do we just burn up and disappear
Hey!
Will you still be there stood next to me
Like you were back in 2013
Now
On a day like today
I can honestly say
I wouldn't be standing here
If it weren't for the friendships
I made with all of you
Each one of you taught me something about friendship
And for that
I will always be grateful
Today
I consider myself
The luckiest pony in Equestria
Thank you friends
Thank you everypony
Will you remember them~
The friendship that they found
Will you know the songs and sing along
Twenty years from now
Or will you still be here
Screaming every word
I know I'm not going anywhere,
I'll die with the herd
Yeah, I'll die with the herd~~