I see me behind the door, don't know what it is for
Celestia, don't leave me
Think my dreams have gone away
Don't know just what to say
King Sombra, don't deceive me
I have tried as best I can, and I don't understand
Celestia, don't leave me
Your voice told me I should go and that is all I know
King Sombra, don't deceive me
My worst nightmare right in front of my eyes
And who knew that it was all a disguise
Somebody tell me this is a dream
A door to a world I never have seen, oh!
Losing faith with every stair I climb, I'm unaware
Celestia, don't leave me
Can't help thinking that was real and not just how I feel
King Sombra, don't deceive me
I tried so hard and got so far but in the end it doesn't ma-atter
But it's too late for me to stay, I better save the day
King Sombra, you will sha-atter!
My worst nightmare right in front of my eyes
And who knew that it was all a disguise
Somebody tell me this is a dream
A door to a world I never have seen, oh!
My worst nightmare right in front of my eyes
And who knew that it was all a disguise
Somebody tell me this is a dream
A door to a world I never have seen, oh!