You try your best but it's not quite there we got
Mic on the mic we wreck the scene got
LULZ backin' the track we're a machine causin'
Havoc and chaos you come to try and stop it when you
See just who your messin' with these boys are reppin' twenty ten
We got Glaze on the track to get this party started
The Living Tombstone remixin' he gonna put his heart in
To what he's making so step back we 'bout to share
You try your best but it's not quite there yeah
Carrot Top go beyond the Garden and
Be the queen you know that you're destined to be ya gotta
Follow your heart now that's a start to be serene you're
Glowin' and showin' the world
You're somepony that people should know and
You gotta beat the heat these haters comin' hard
Ready to break down your armies and go shatter your walls
But you know inside you're not a typical girl
You gonna show us let your story unfurl
You try your best but it's not quite there
You kick your hoof and say it's just not fair
A simple mare living simple dreams
A rumor that's not quite as it seems~
You're gonna rattle shake and bring the heat you'll show the
Haters when you sweep 'em right off their feet you're gonna
Cast out your light and cover them in your glow
The world is now your Garden give 'em love to grow
You're mother nature they hate ya nailed ya on the cross
It's all lost to me the cost to be a beacon in the dark ya see
Is your life but you know inside though they're your blight
They're never ever gonna manage to put out your light
So Carrot Top spread your wings and take to the sky
You're gonna rise in time they hurt'cha but you'll never die
Like a phoenix rise again when they strike you down
You'll change their frown turn all their worlds upside down
The second coming has begun the deed is done
The haters lookin' at'cha shakin' cause they're all about to run
But then you hold out your hoof and show 'em gentle smiles
It's worthwhile they feel they hatred leave you banished the vile
You try your best but it's not quite there
You kick your hoof and say it's just not fair~
A simple mare living simple dreams
A rumor that's not quite as it seems~
Six months have passed and everypony knows your name
They know that mane and they all know the claims
About how Carrot Top ain't a normal filly at all
She's a star in the sky and it's why the other
Ponies gonna try and drag her down but
You know you gotta try and go to stand your ground 'cause
If you don't the world will crumble right at your feet
Now go beyond the Garden girl and try to beat the heat
Carrot Top go beyond us
You're a late star time to fool us
Keep your friends close they're what drive you
To the cosmos that describes you
Carrot Top go beyond us
You're a late star time to fool us
Keep your friends close they're what drive you
To the cosmos that describes you
Brighter than tonight's sunset
Can't mistake your silhouette
Not a sound nor voice nearby
Your mane illuminates this gloomy sky~
The other ponies come and try to take ya but your
Your friends are by your side they are what make ya so ya
You stand up tall and you just give in you never
Think about yourself you selfless woman within
And then they they tie ya up and they set you a blaze through smoke and haze
You only see their brighter days are comin'
So even though you're gone you're still in their hearts and
They'll always have a piece of you you left them your Garden
Carrot Top go beyond us you're a
Late star time to fool us
Keep your friends close they're what drive you
To the cosmos that describes you
Carrot Top go beyond us
You're a late star time to fool us
Keep your friends close they're what drive you
To the cosmos that describes you