You can keep yourself~ hidden
By never telling the truth
But when your friends are~ hurting
They'll be relying on you
So won't you set yourself free
From these darkest of times~~
Truth comes out when you're~ singing
So let your sweet voice shine~~
'Cuz I believe in honesty
I believe~ in faith
In the land that we're working
In the things that we make
Honesty has beauty~
That you can't~ take away
Oh I believe in honesty~~
It's our family way
Oh if you ever get tired~
Of never doing your share~~
Of looking over your shoulder~~
Just to see who's~ there
Honesty is watching~
It makes you strong oh yeah~
Feel it in your heart~~
And you'll be singing our~ song
'Cuz I believe in honesty
I believe~ in faith
In the land that we're working
In the things that we say
Honesty has beauty~
That you can't take away
Oh I believe in honesty
It's our family way