Daytime sleeps and dreams of night
While beauty flanks your bed
White-blue stars soar skyward yearning
Love your heart misread
Night burns bright and blends with shadow
Fills your heart with gloom
Princess Luna, roamer of dreams
Steal my heart and bloom
Dance with me
Sing with me
Play with me
Fly with me
Run with me
Trot with me
Laugh with me
Steal from me
All deckhands on deck!
Swasher and blackjack!
Peel off to port tack!
Hearties go find me gold!
All deckhands on deck!
Swasher and blackjack!
Peel off to port tack!
Blimey, you got me sold!
Pirate Luna, come steal my heart made of gold
Live in my dreams, we'll fight scallywags and the mold
Scream out ahoy!
Lift up your spirits
Live on the vessel of the lunar pirate
All deckhands on deck!
Swasher and blackjack!
Peel off to port tack!
Hearties go find me gold!
All deckhands on deck!
Swasher and blackjack!
Peel off to port tack!
Blimey, you got me sold!
Pirate Luna, come steal my heart made of gold
Live in my dreams, we'll fight scallywags and the mold
Scream out ahoy!
Lift up your spirits
Live on the vessel of the lunar pirate
Pirate Luna, come steal my heart made of gold
Live in my dreams, we'll fight scallywags and the mold
Scream out ahoy!
Lift up your spirits
Live on the vessel of the lunar pirate
Regina noctis pro nobis
Lunæ lumen