She's go-ot a way of kno-owing
What's on your mi-i-i-ind
She really can't expla-ain it
So she leaves you bli-i-i-ind
Do you ever wonder why she-e
Always makes you smi-i-i-ile?
If it's impossible physically-y
It suits her sty-y-y-yle
It keeps you smilin' for a whi-i-ile
She's made of giggles and gu-umdrops
Oven mitts and outtakes
Doodles and do-onuts
Fairytales and fruitcake
Ask her yourse-elf but you'll never
Ever understa-and why-y
It's anything but a li-i-ie
Sometime-es I tend to wo-onder
How she lived befo-o-o-ore
How could o-one survive so so-omber
Maybe there's mo-o-o-ore
It feels like every morni-ing
She's wo-ound up ti-i-i-ight
She may be hard to talk to-o
But she's ne-ever shy-y-y-y
You can never ever look her in the e-eye
She's made of giggles and gu-umdrops
Oven mitts and outtakes
Doodles and do-onuts
Fairytales and fruitcake
Ask her yourse-elf but you'll never
Ever understa-and why-y-y-y-y
She's made of chaos and cu-upcakes
Lots and lots of batter
Sugar and su-unshine
Lollipops and laughter
See for yourse-elf but you'll never get it
Don't even try-y-y-y-y
It's anything but a lie
Slow motion, so fo-oreign
To somebody so hyperactively involved
Commotion, confu-usion
Talk of the to-own, she's a mystery
We'll never so-o-o-olve
We'll never solve
She's made of chaos and cu-upcakes
Lots and lots of batter
Sugar and su-unshine
Lollipops and laughter
See for yourse-elf but you'll never get it
Don't eve-en try-y-y-y-y-y-y
Giggles and gu-umdrops
Oven mitts and outtakes
Doodles and do-onuts
Fairytales and fruitcake
Ask her yourse-elf but you'll never
Ever understa-and why-y
No you'll never ever understa-and why-y-y-y-y
It's anything but a li-i-ie