Don't really know if she saw me
I won~der if I'll e~ver learn
Oh yes, I know I'll be sorry
If I~~ don't make it clear~ to her~~
The pony's got a knack for excellence
Clearly not an accident
Elegant perfection she~~ is
She's the mare who's got everything
But emptiness
But will you ever share with me?
My little fashionista can't get a break
Too many dresses~ due
And there's no esca~pin' but
Rarity
I bet you wonder if the world has its cup
Filled to the brim with~ you
And how could I blame~ them?
Will she see me
When surely I'm invisible
Will she hear me~~
If I don't make a sound at all
Why am I fighting a losing bat~tle?
And why from the lower ground~~?
Well they told me
My heart would carry me around
So will you ever share with me?
My little fashionista can't get a break
Too many dresses~ due
And there's no esca~pin' but
Rarity
I bet you wonder if the world has its cup
Filled to the brim with~ you
And how could I blame~ them?