We're no strangers to love~~
You know the rules~, and so~ do~ I
A full commitment's what I'm thinking of~
You wouldn't get this from any other gal
I just wanna tell you how I'm fe-eling
Gotta make you understand
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you do-own
Never gonna run around~ and desert you
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie~~
And hurt you
We've known each other~
For so long~
Your heart's been aching but
You're too shy to say it
Inside we both know what's been going on~
We know the game and we're
Gonna play it
And if you ask me how I'm fe-eling
Don't tell me you're too blind to see
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down~
Never gonna run around~ and desert you
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie~~
And hurt you
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down~
Never gonna run around~ and desert you
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie~~
And hurt you