In the rising dawn
Just another da-ay to bear
Don't know whe-ere my life has go-one
Waiting on an answered prayer
Hiding fro-om your face~
You're breaking through my e-endless youth
Telling me my life's a waste
My world is crumbling i-in the truth
Flying never felt so low
All the thi-ings that we~ have do-one
Though I try I never know
What you want me to beco-ome
And I'll fly forever
Get nervous, get nervous
It does~n't, it does~n't
Um, ma'am, better be harder, better be fast
Better be shining free
And I'll fly forever
Get nervous, get nervous
It does~n't, it does~n't
Um, ma'am, better be harder, better be fast
Better be shining free
And I'll know never to be you
Every night I lie awake
Facing fears I'm hiding deep inside
Every word I heard you say
Every memory louder than the lies
Nowhere left for me to go
When the dreams~ I seek are~ dead~ and gone
Though I try~ I'll never know
What you want me to~ beco-ome
I don't want second
Get nervous, get nervous
Better be harder, better be fast
Better be pushing until I fly
Until I fly
Who am I?
I'll journey till~ I fi-ind a light
Yeah I'll get the-ere one da-ay~~~~~~~~~~
Cause I fly a~way
From the world I knew
Cause my heart it to-old me to
Now I'm on my own
Who knows~ what~ I could become?
In the ai-ir I see it
The truth, yeah I believe it
Doesn't matter what we've do~ne
Only what~ we can beco-ome
Oh wa-a-aoh woah-aoh woah-oh singin'
Oh wa~oh woah-oh oh
With my friends~ I'm not alone
Now I know~ what~ I'll become~~~~~~
With my friends I'm no-ot alo~one
Now I~ know~ what I'll beco-ome