Fo-or I oh so love the groom
All my-y-y thoughts he does consume
Oh, Shining A-armo-o-or
I'll be there very soon
I have never seen a pony quite like you
What they don't know is that she's a changeling
She's got a parasitic sty-yle and unfeeling intentions
Mi Amore Cadenza
This is all my fault
Whatever are you talking about?
What wouldn't Twi-ilight want me to know anything about?
We-we-well there's a new regime now
Fo-or I oh so love the groom
All my-y-y thoughts he does consume
Oh, Shining A-armo-o-or
I'll be there very soon
Fo-or I oh so love the groom
All my-y-y thoughts he does consume
Oh, Shining A-armo-o-or
I'll be there very soon
Cadance had the ideal life
Gave her all to her kni-ight
You broke her and let the pieces fall
And so you staged the perfect crime
You ruin everyone you mimic
This day is going to be perfect
This is all my fault
Whatever are you talking about?
What wouldn't Twi-ilight want me to know anything about?
We-we-well there's a new regime now
Fo-or I oh so love the groom
All my-y-y thoughts he does consume
Oh, Shining A-armo-o-or
I'll be there very soon
And you can't feel the pain yo-u bring
Heartless changeling
Cause you're not a part of this affair
But Twilight is the brightest bulb
That's her brother that you ho-old
She won't go down without a fight
We-we-well there's a new regime now
Fo-or I oh so love the groom
All my-y-y thoughts he does consume
Oh, Shining A-armo-o-or
I'll be there very soon