The darkness within the trees~
The monsters from deep unknown~
My friends all are telling me~
I shouldn't go
Don't go into the Everfree
Don't go into the Everfree~~
Don't go into the Everfree~
And I mean it when I say~
The forest is no place~
For ponies to go play~
Alone~
There's evil deep inside~
And no place left to hide~
No one can hear you cry~
At all~
Even though it's mysterious
And I know everypony is curious
It's not worth it to sacrifice
Going into the forest devoid of light
Constant darkness and strange events
All the magic and forces are quite intense
Lots of weird things you'd never see but
Don't get lost~, in the Everfree~
The darkness within the trees~
The monsters from deep un known~
My friends all are telling me~
I shouldn't go~~~~
Don't go into the Everfree
Don't go into the Everfree~~
Don't go into the Everfree~
The darkness within the trees~
The monsters from deep unknown~
My friends all are telling me~
I shouldn't go
Don't go into the Everfree
Don't go into the Everfree~~
Don't go into the Everfree~
Don't go into the Everfree
Don't go into the Everfree~~
Don't go into the Everfree~