I've seen enough here, to know I don't belong
My imagination, again has lead me on
This stubborn aching, has a mi~nd of its own
I've left, but I won't tell you whe~re I've go~ne
I've never known that, the world could be so~ mean
I'll never go back, to who I used to be~
A steady runway, is all that I would need
To reason with myself behi~nd the sce~nes
Is it me...
Is it me, or can you see through my~ walls
As if the~y'd ne~ver shown?
Could it be...
Could it be~, all because of my~ lies?
I've broken my~ own bones
No more throwing stones
I could have sworn I, I had a life befo~re
My short attention, had wanted something more
I can't erase it, I know I won't forge~t
But at least I learned my lesso~n i~n the end
Oh, winter bree~zes, were never gone so fast
I~t's straight ahea~d now, and no more looking back
Like separation, letting go~ of the pa~st
And trying to rebuild my house of glass
Is it me...
Is it me, or can you see through my~ walls
As if the~y'd ne~ver shown?
Could it be...
Could it be~, all because of my~ lies?
I've broken my~ own bones
Is it me...
Is it me, or can you see throu~gh my~ walls
As if the~y'd ne~ver shown?
Could it be...
Could it be~, all because of my lies?
I've broken my~ own bones
My own bo~~nes
No mo~re throwing stones