A young magician
With strong ambition
She's dedicated
Underrated
But she pla-ans to change
She met her idol
Talked for a while
She learned his tri-ick
She was pi-icked
To go out on stage
Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-oo-ooh
She got caught up in the fame
Proudly shouting out her name
Took her ye-ears, now she finally had a crowd to entertain
Hooves were stomping on the floor
Screaming, shouting for encore
Trixie got her attention and desired for more
Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-oo-ooh
A month of touring
Her shows were boring
Without a na-ame
Dipped in fa-ame
Not a soul would care
Her constant fading
Was irritating
This false direction
Of attention
Just felt so unfair
Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-oo-ooh
Then she got to Ponyville
Lying nearly got her killed
She was showed up by a mage who greatly triumphed her in skill
Left with nothing but a name
Fueled with hatred by her shame
She destroyed her reputation and then everything else
Ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-ooo-oo-ooh