Button's~ Mom has got it goin' on
Button can I come o~ver
After school~ ol-ol-ol-ol?
After school
We can play around
In your gaming~ room~ oo-oo-oo-om
Gaming~ room
Did your mom get back
From her Canterlot trip?~~
Canterlot trip
Is she there or is she trying to
Give me the slip~ i-i-i-ip?
Give me the slip
You know I'm not the little colt
That I used to be
I'm all~ grown~ up
I'm a stallion can't you see!
Button's Mom has got it goin' on
She's all that I want
And I've waited for so~ long~
Button can't you see
You're just not the colt for me!~~
I know it might be wrong~ but
I'm in love with Button's Mom
Button's~ Mom has got it goin' on
Button do you remem~ber
When we gamed all~ night?~~
Gamed all night
Your mom came in
Just to turn out the li-~i-i-i-ight
Turn out the light
I could tell she liked me
From the way she~ stared~~
The way she stared
And the way she said
"You missed a mob over there~ e-e-e-ere"
Mob over there
And I know~~ that you think it's just a fantasy
But since your dad ain't home
Your mom could use a guy like me!~
Button's Mom has got it goin' on
She's all that I want
And I've waited for so~ long~
Button can't you see
That she's just the mare for me!~~
I know it might be wrong~ but
I'm in love with Button's Mom
She's got it goin' on
Waitin' and waitin'
I know it might be wrong~~~
But I'm in love with
Yeah I'm in love with
No wait a minute
I know it might be wrong~ but
I'm in love with Button's Mom