If you wanna be the life of the party
But you're feeling just a little uptight
Call the doctor, beg and plead
"Doctor, tell me what I need"
Try to put a little cheese in your knees!
Just let yourself go floppy
For now this is your chance
Pretend you have no bones
and do the rubber chicken dance!
Hit it, Boneless!
'Cause I like to make you smile, smile, smile
Yes I do
It fills my heart with sunshine all the while
Yes it does
'Cause all I really need's a smile, smile, smile
From these happy friends of mine
What do you mean?
I have no idea what you're talking about
Why should you compromise?
Try this one on for size
'Cause nothing quite says cheer
Like the ringing in your ear
Of the Cheese Supreme Cannonball Surprise!