I'll be searching da-ay and night
The big old sun, it sure is bright
But it's ha-ard to keep i-it burning without yo-ou
And when the sun is o-out of si-ight
The moon will be my guiding light
But it's ha-ard to keep i-it turning without yo-ou
It's hard to keep i-it turning without you
Summer, winter, spri-ing and fall
Seasons move around us all
But it's ha-ard to keep 'em rolling without yo-ou
Seconds keep on passing by
The numbers tell us how and why
But time will never sta-and still without yo-ou
The time will never sta-and still without you
Guess who I've been thi-inking o-of
My little heart is full of love
But it's ha-ard to keep it beating without yo-ou
It's hard to keep it beating without you