I hear you're trying to call to me
You wanna be free
My broken and scarred destiny~
As seen by~ your own em~pathy
Ran away from the life I have known~
Got this feeling in my bones
The exile~ of this forsaken race~
There's something we've got the trace~
Open your eyes to~ a whole new dimension
Of a world you've never seen
We assume control of a city
Of self pity when The Last Tempest
Takes control~~~~
Takes control~~~~~~~~
Takes control~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
I was just a little girl~
Wanting to play with my friends
Misfortune played a role~
In my everlasting toll~
I had hoped for a childhood
And everlasting friend~ship
They always predicted my path
They will face for my wrath
Open your eyes to a whole new dimension
Of a world you've~ never seen
We assume control of a city
Of self pity when The Last Tempest
Takes control~~~
Takes control~~~~
Takes control~~~~~~~~
Takes control~~~~~~