I've been trying to tell ya
Why I am the way I am
See I'm not like you no
Something you must understand
See I come from a place where we must embrace
The madness that we own~
And I try to be good but the neighborhood
Just ain't too much like home~~
In the Gryphon City no it ain't pretty
Nobody said it was supposed to be
We're all conceited and everyone's a cheater
Call it a natural ability~
In the Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Failure after failure
Far away from what I know
Rules and regulations
Planted with no room to grow
See there comes a time when it seems a crime
To live in harmo~ny~
And I try to be good but the neighborhood
Just ain't the place for me~~
In the Gryphon City no it ain't pretty
Nobody said it was supposed to be
We're all conceited and everyone's a cheater
Call it a natural ability~
In the Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Ponyville is nice for most
But it seems kind of comatose
Why don't you wake up and see
It's just the way I am~?
In the Gryphon City no it ain't pretty
Nobody said it was supposed to be
We're all conceited and everyone's a cheater
Call it a natural ability~
In the Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Gryphon City, Gryphon City
Gryphon City, Gryphon City~~