From the snow-swept mountain tops
To the emerald green fields
Across the sea and sky, that wondrous light
Has touched us all
And as the night begins to fade
And the moon hangs low
We wake to see the rise of her
Celestial glow
Woah
Raise the sun
Every pony and parasprite
Every dragon and bird
Knows that without her light, her loving warmth
We'd ne ver live
Those cowards hide in shadows
Sheathed by the night
We fight the darkness, our swords
Raised for the light
Woah
Raise the sun
Through out all of Equestria
The Solar Empire endures
Every colt and mare, we stand at arms
Ten million strong
You best stray from evil
And stay in the light
Or be lost to darkness like tears
Shed in the night
Woah
Raise the sun
We shall never surrender
We shall never let the darkness impede
We shall stand strong for all eternity
And spread her radiance and love
MOVE OUT!