I can't belie-eve that I thought it'd be easy
Well I guess that no~-one's perfe-ect
I was decei-ieved by a thing we call dreamin'
'Cause I thought I co-ouldn't hurt i-it
Now look at me-e, it's so easy to se-ee
Something's hi-idin' what I asked fo-or
It's been ye-ears now
And I'm still seekin' it o-out
Ma-aybe I'm~ only~ stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-a-bo-ove
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, or maybe all I need is love
Ooh yeah, wo-o-oah
All I need is lo-ove
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh
Ooh, wo-o-oah
Ooh, all I ne-eed is
Once aga-ain, I can feel myself fadin'
But I see a ne-ew life being co-olored in
I can te-ell that my heart is done achin'
But I wonder if I've gained ano-other skin
I can't stop this transformation
An odd sensation's takin' me fo-or a~ ride
All the way ba-ack through my~ mi-ind
Ma-aybe I'm~ only~ stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-a-bo-ove
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, or maybe all I~ need is lo-ove
Ooh ye-eah, woah-oh, oh-oh
Ooh, all I ne-eed is
Lo-o-o-ove
Oh, ye-e-e-e-eah
Oh, ah-ah-ah-ah
All I~ ne-eed is
Lo-ove
Ma-aybe I'm~ only~ stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-a-bo-ove
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, or maybe all I~ need is
Lo-ove