A flash of colour and she's gone no one can hope to pursue
A flank of red and white and yellow and cerulean blue
And making rainbows awesome since October two thousand ten
Another day a rush of wind and she'll be at it again
Those airborne virtuosics are the stuff of legends and more
The name is Rainbow Dash and I suspect you've heard it before
Now if you come with me you'll find her where she takes her repose
You won't forget her quickly once you see her as she well knows
Rainbow Dash fly
Rainbow Dash fly fly
If ever you're in need of help she will show up with a smile
And indescribable velocity impeccable style
Agility in spades and pegasine charisma to match
And when you're falling you can count on her to be there to catch
Don't be alarmed if she does not appear as soon as you shout
You know she probably just stopped to give some autographs out
To call her narcissistic is an understatement and yet
She's just that good it's not surprising that it goes to her head
Rainbow Dash fly
Rainbow Dash fly fly
Rainbow Dash is best pony
When the world seems everfree
Coloured winds blow through my mind
Everything is left behind
Now Rainbow Dash I think you could do worse than listen to me
Though you're spectacular it's probable your friends would agree
Your self aggrandising demeanour is ungracious and cruel
As if you're insecure and compensating don't be a fool
You know you'll never be a Wonderbolt until you admit
You need to lift your game and act as if you really want it
Still busy napping when you could be out perfecting your art
So much potential
Come on Rainbow Dash you're breaking my heart
Rainbow Dash fly
Rainbow Dash fly fly
Rainbow Dash fly~
Rainbow Dash fly