Nightmare Moon sealed away in lunar prison
Life will go on in the kingdom below
All is set right in the world for a season
'Til her release when this story is closed
The stars will aid in her escape
Return to where the battle raged
The elements will wash away
The darkness and the pain
My little ponies the horror has ended
Luna will pay for the crime she has done
Don’t let her sins fill your mind up with hatred
Forgiveness is all I can ask of you now
For the future is bright
Golden age within sight
If you let love lead the way
Now the sunrise lifts us up from the dark~
The dawn bringing light, bringing hope
We will rebuild for our spirit is strong
And Harmony will be restored~
Listen now my children
For the meaning of her fall
A heart that’s left abandoned
Causes sadness in us all
So love your fellow ponies
Show a kindness unrestrained
And Harmony will follow you for all~ of your days~
Now the sunrise lifts us up from the dark~
The dawn bringing light, bringing hope
We will rebuild for our spirit is strong
And Harmony will be restored~