I'm sitting here in the sunshine
This place is not mine
And all is not fine
Like where is all my corruption?
I need destruction
To make me feel okay
Did I get lost along the way
Playing nice like they wanted me to be?
No, I will not smile to make your day
I just wanna cause a little entropy
You tried so hard
To make a hero out of me
But there are some rules I don't obey
And I just wanna cause a little entropy
You tried so hard
To take the discord outta me
But I'm not generic in that way
And I just wanna cause a little entropy
Well, I've got no good intention~
The fourth dimension
Is my own mansion
It's all messed up, I don't care
'cause what fun is there
In ever making sense?
Did I get lost along the way
Lose my mind for a new identity?
I quite enjoy ruin~ing your day
And I just wanna cause a little entropy
You tried so hard to make a hero outta me
But there are some rules I don't obey
And I just wanna cause a little chaos
And entropy
You tried so hard
To take the discord outta me
But I'm not generic in that way
And I just wanna cause a little entropy
I just want to cause a little entropy
This old heart was never warm
Silly ponies can't reform
What was already so real
So you can try to change my ways
For the rest of all your days
But I can't change the way I feel
That was really cheesy
Did I get lost along the way
Lose my mind for a new identity?
I quite enjoy ruin~ing your day
And I just wanna cause a little entropy
You tried so hard to make a hero outta me
But there are some rules I don't obey
And I just wanna cause a little-
Yeah yeah~~~~~
I'm causing all the entropy entropy yeah
You tried so hard
To take the discord outta me
Guess what I wasn't born that way
And I just wanna cause a little entropy