Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything is certainly fine
There's the mayor en route to her office
There's the sofa clerk selling some quills
My Ponyville is so gentle and still
Can things ever go wrong?
I don't think that the-ey will
Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi~-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything is certainly
Fine
There's the mayor en route to her office
My Ponyville is so gentle and still
Yes! Everything's gonna be just fine
Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything is certainly
Fine
Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
'Cause everything is certain-
Life in Equestria shimmers
Life in Equestria shi-i-ines
And I know for absolute certain
It's fine
Something tells me everything is not going to be fine