Aah ah ah aaah aaah
Things just ain't the same for Sunset
Been just a bum fest, haven't had any fun yet
Her friendship testing has been done yet
She made a slum bet, ended up in a rock pit
Its hard shit, her destiny's not met.
A hot mess, told herself that she got this
But not since Tia shoved away all of her nonsense
She couldn't stop this in the end she turned powerless
She raised hell with both of her fists cocked
Yet was worthy of jail with both of her wrists locked
Twist cops who'd miss shots, students resist not
This wild ride didn't have any pit stops
Tick-tock went the clock, a years passing
Today's past means no forgiveness from THAT thing
Shimmer thought it was the end of her world
Until she met up with these three new girls
Everywhere Shimmer goes
Ain't the same as before
There are people she knows
They don't want her no more
Then comes Adagio
Sonata and her taco
Aria will take control
They'll welcome you to the show
Old Starswirl works in mysterious ways
Banishing the sirens to this infurious place
Starving for green fumes it's a serious case
Til they see the Rainbooms with a curious face
"This world don't have Equestrian magic Adagio"
But does she know what that really is? Prolly so
Really tho, they preach of competition and fame
They say they we don't really have to be one in the same
The battle of the bands equals power in your hands
You think you'll take control from the adoration of fans?
More insane than Lyra's admiration of hands
Friendship will be the key to your laceration of plans
The admiration for jamming will keep everyone standing and dancing
Spell breaks with rainbow enhancing
No Hanson telling them to take a seat over there
Except the trio with the tripped out hair
Everywhere Shimmer goes
Ain't the same as before
There are people she knows
They don't want her no more
Then comes Adagio
Sonata and her taco
Aria will take control
They'll welcome you to the show
We heard you want to get together
We heard you want to rock this school
We've thought of something that is better
Something that changes all the rules
How the mighty have fallen without their rad bling
Their dazzling talents turned into babbling
Sights on a world tour they'll have to be cancelling
Never knew Horse Jesus would be the one they'd be battling
It's a sad thing all they've been doing was hassling
These hafflings, these sea pony hatchlings
They say to make an omelette you gotta break a couple eggs
Yet they're thrown in their faces and now they scrambling
So much for the ol' razzle dazzle
These damsels will have to find a brand new angle
The road they traveled left em in mangles
A strange gamble they thought they could handle
They didn't know they would fall so how can ends meet
How can they get off street and back up on their feet
It's such a trip to be working for tips
So you better get to swaying them hips
Everywhere Shimmer goes
Ain't the same as before
There are people she knows
They don't want her no more
Then comes Adagio
Sonata and her taco
Aria will take control
They'll welcome you to the show
Aah ah ah aaah aaah