Yahoo!
Raise this barn
One, two, three, four
Together we can raise this barn
Up, up, up, go the beams
Hammer those joints,
Work in teams
Turn 'em round quick by the right elbow
Grab a new partner
Here we go
Come on, Apple family
Let's get to it! Whoo-hoo!
Raise this barn
One, two, three, four
Together we can raise this barn
Finish the frame
Recycling wood
Working hard, you're doing good
Turn 'em round quick by the right elbow
Grab a new partner
Here we go
Yeah!
Whoo-whee!
Raise this ba-arn
Raise this barn
One, two, three, four
Together we can raise this barn
Slats of wood come off the ground
Hold 'em up and nail 'em down
Turn 'em round quick by the left elbow
Grab a new partner
Here we go
Come on, Apples!
Get her done!
Look at us, we're family
Working together thankfully
We Apples we are proud to say
Stick together the pony way
Bow to your partner, circle right
Get down if you're scared of heights
Forward, back and twirl around
The barn's gonna be the best in town
Yeah!
Yee-haw! Attagirl!
All right! Let's get to it!
Raise this barn
One, two, three, four
Together we can raise this barn
Take your brushes
Young and old
Together paint it bright and bold
Turn 'em round quick by the left elbow
Grab a new partner
Here we go
We raised this barn
Yes, we did
Together we sure raised this barn,
Yes we-e did
Being together counts the most
We all came here from coast to coast
All we need to strive to be
Is part of the Apple family
Yeah!