You would not believe your eyes
If ten million Fluttershys
Flew in the room
As I fell asleep
Cause they'd fill the open air
And their squeaking everywhere
would be so~ cute
That I would just stand and smile
I'd like to make myself believe
Equestria's~
kind po~ny
Would come to me
When I'm feeling tired
And snuggle me to sleep
Cause ponies have invaded
All my dreams
Cause into my room they'd fly
Those ten thousand pegasi
As they sung me lullabies to sleep
"Time to lay your sleepy head,
Hush now, time to go to bed"
I'd slumber then,
Snug under my warm bedspread
I'd like to make myself believe
Equestria's~
Kind po~ny
Would come to me
when I'm feeling tired
And snuggle me to sleep
Cause ponies have invaded
All my dreams
When I fall asleep
Don't close my browser for a bit
Cause I need another pony hit
Why can't I stop with one more peek
It's 5 AM and I need to sleep
To ten million Fluttershys
I'm weird cause I hate goodbyes
I got misty eyes
As they said farewell
But I'll know where several hide
When my dreams get ponified
Cause I saved a few
And into my room they'll glide
I'd like to make myself believe
Equestria's~
kind po~ny
Would come to me
When I'm feeling tired
And snuggle me to sleep
Cause ponies have
invaded all my dreams
I'd like to make myself believe
Equestria's~
kind po~ny
Would come to me
When I'm feeling tired
And snuggle me to sleep
Cause ponies have
invaded all my dreams
When I fall asleep
I'd like to make myself believe
Equestria's~
Kind po~ny
would come to me
when I'm feeling tired
And snuggle me~~ to sleep
'Cause I'm obsessed
with ponies, so it seems