Na na, na na na na
Na na na, na, na na na na na
With every step that I take
I'm movin' on
Brush the dirt off my shoulder
Yeah I'm movin' on
Rainbow Dash in my hand
Backpack on the back, packed, ready to attack
At a moment's call
It's go time, don't drop the ball
You look back
Might as well be turned to salt
Don't be shy, just dash and fly high
With a sparkle in your eye
Yeah, keep movin' on
From when you pop right outta the womb
And right in the tomb
You think you have time to figure out
What you're destined to do
You're guessing your moves
Yet at the same time
You're wasting your days and nights
Downing the booze
Light up parties with your dazzling moves
You're out with your crew
Going out on the town
'cause that's what they do
Wreaking havoc all around
Neighbors clamoring too
But your family and friends
All frowning at you
With every step that I take
I'm movin' on
Brush the dirt off my shoulder
Yeah I'm movin' on
Rainbow Dash in my hand
Backpack on the back, packed, ready to attack
At a moment's call
It's go time, don't drop the ball
You look back
Might as well be turned to salt
Don't be shy, just dash and fly high
With a sparkle in your eye
Yeah, keep movin' on
Keep movin'
Keep moving on
Keep movin
Keep movin'
Keep moving on
You're ballin' you're cause toppin' out your game
But when they call your name
You're staggering and fallin' over
They're all ashamed
The fame game that you played
Has made ya act insane
You're taking no blame
You're not stoppin'
You're not droppin' again
You start poppin' at claims
And keep on actin' the fool
And walkin' n' struttin' around
Talkin' down at your crew
The only few keepin' you from feelin' lonely and blue
Yet people lookin' atcha thinkin'
"Damn! It's good to be you"
And at the same time
You don't know what the hell you should be bringing
You start swinging
And feelin' that you've only been singin'
For all the wrong reasons
People keep on tellin' you, "STOP!
If you keep goin' you'll DROP
Never knowin' watcha GOT"
But you're too hot-headed
To see just what you're doin' wrong
You sing your song
You're thinkin' that you're cruisin' along
But now your friends are gone
There's nothin' left for you to hold on
You gotta be strong
Now pick up
It's time to move on
With every step that I take
I'm movin' on
Brush the dirt off my shoulder
Yeah I'm movin' on
Rainbow Dash in my hand
Backpack on the back, packed, ready to attack
At a moment's call
It's go time, don't drop the ball
You look back
Might as well be turned to salt
Don't be shy, just dash and fly high
With a sparkle in your eye
Yeah, keep movin' on
With every step that I take
I'm movin' on
Brush the dirt off my shoulder
Yeah I'm movin' on
Rainbow Dash in my hand
Backpack on the back, packed, ready to attack
At a moment's call
It's go time, don't drop the ball
You look back
Might as well be turned to salt
Don't be shy, just dash and fly high
With a sparkle in your eye
Yeah, keep movin' on
Keep moving on
Keep movin', keep movin', keep moving on