It's so complicated
He's evil, let's face it
But I know he'll reform
Just give him the chance
Now if you wanna be kind, it'll take some steps so
Take a seat and I'll explain the rest
Just be polite, don't bring the worst and- um, well,
You gotta pay attention first...
There's a way to show kindness and trust
Without playing those tricks and rain chaos on us
No need for those insults, just give it a try
Oh, there's gotta be some kind of compassion inside!
La la la la la, aa-aa-aa-aa-ahh
Though it's hard to make it there,
Don't hide you care
I know you'll be fine
Aa-aa-aa-aaahh, la la la la la
Use your magic for the best,
And see the rest
Believe in you in no time!
Thank you Discord for showing me
That sweetest side that I can now see
Keeping our promise all the more
'Cause that's what friends are for!
It's so complicated
He's evil, let's face it
But I know he'll reform
Just give him the chance
So let out that kindness
Don't forget where your heart is
And it's not bad! Understand
The friendship we have!