If you threw a party~~
And invited everyone you knew~~~
You would see the biggest gift would be from me
And the card attached would say
I count on you and you count on me
It's as easy as 1-2-3
And we're connected eternally
We dance around by the firelight
And catch the stars falling from the sky
Tell your secrets and I'll tell you mine
Out of seven billion people in the world
Can't believe that I found you
Hey! Hey!
I know you've got my back and I got yours
Call on me and I'll remind you
Yeah, you're da best!
And if you threw a party~~
And invited everyone you knew~~~
You would see the biggest gift would be from me
And the card attached would say
Thank you for being a friend
A friend, a friend, a~~~~ friend
You understand without saying a word
Your heart is gold, but you put me first
And you help me reach for what I deserve
Out of seven billion people in the world
Can't believe that I found you
Hey! Hey!
And just in case you're feeling insecure
Call on me and I'll remind you
I will remind you!
And if you threw a party~~
And invited everyone you knew~~~
You would see the biggest gift would be from me
And the card attached would say
Thank you for being a friend
A friend, a friend, a~~~~ friend
So c'mon, call anyone over
They'll tell you the same thing I told ya
We'll always be shoulder to shoulder
I gotcha, I gotcha
So c'mon, call anyone over
They'll tell you the same thing I told ya
We'll always be shoulder to shoulder
I gotcha, I gotcha
And if you threw a party~~
And invited everyone you knew~~~
You would see the biggest gift would be from me
And the card attached would say
Thank you for being a friend
A friend, a friend, a~~~~ friend