Almost heaven, West Virginia
Blue Ridge Mountains, Shenandoah River
Life is old there, older than the trees
Younger than the mountains, rolling like a breeze
Country roads, take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia,oh mountain mama-a-a
Take me home, country roads
All my memories gather 'round her
Miner's la~-ady, stranger to blue water
Dark and dusty, painted on the sky
Misty taste of moonshine, teardrop in my eye
Country roads, take me home
To the place I belong
West Virginia,oh mountain mama
Oh take me home, country roads
I hear her voice in the mornin' hour, she calls me
The radio reminds me of my home far away
Drivin' down the road, I get a feelin'
That I should've been home yesterday
Yesterday
Country roads, take me home
To the place
I belong oh! West Virginia
Oh mountain mama-a-a
Oh take me home, country roads