I can't belie-eve that I thought it'd be easy
I guess no one's perfe-ect
I was dece-eived by a thing we call dreamin'
'Cause I thought I co-ouldn't hurt i-it
Now look at me-e, it's so easy to see-ee
Something's hi-idin' what I asked fo-or
It's been ye-ears no-ow
And I'm still seekin' it o-out
Ma-aybe I'm~ only-y stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-above
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Whoa-oh-oh-oh–oh-oh-oh-oh
Or maybe all I need is love
Ooh, ye-e-e-eah
Oh-oh wo-oah, o-o-o-oh
Whoa-oh wo-o-oah
All I ne-eed is lo-o-o-o-ove
Once aga-ain, I can feel myself fadin'
But I see a ne-ew life being co-o-lo-oured in
I can te-ell that my heart is done achin'
But I wonder if I've gained ano~ther skin
I can't stop this transformation
An odd sensation's takin' me fo-or a~ ride
All~ the way ba-ack through my-y mind~
Ma-aybe I'm~ only-y stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-above
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
Or maybe all I need is love
Ooh, yeah, ye-eah
Ooh, all I ne-eed is lo-o-ove
Oh, ye-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-e-eah
Ooh, all I need is
Love
Ma-aybe I'm~ only-y stuck
O-on my o-own cloud a-above
Maybe it's okay
Or maybe I'm insane
Maybe it's meant to be so-o tough
Whoa-oh-oh-oh–oh-oh
Or maybe all I ne-eed is
Love