W~atching you~
Fl~ying hi~gher~
Gone in a flash
Like a multi-colored fire
I only wish I could fly besi~de you
Some~day
I'll be up~ there~
Just like you
Dashing through the air
I know one day my dreams will co~me true
Oh how I wish I could be soaring through the sky
If only I could stand upon the clouds up high
If only I could be just li~ke you
Someday I'll be flying abo~ve the world
One day I'll be more than just an ordinary girl
'Cuz I can be whate~ver I~ choo~se
I wanna be just li~ke you
O~ne~ day
I'll learn all~ your~
Daring tricks
And you'll see what I have in store
Someday I'll fly just as high a~s you
Until then
I'll be try~ing~
I'll never give up
Until I'm~ flying
I'll be watching every little thing you~ do~
Oh how I wish I could be soaring through the sky
If only I could stand upon the clouds up high
If only I could be just li~ke you
Someday I'll be flying abo~ve the world
One day I'll be more than just an ordinary girl
'Cuz I can be whate~ver I~ choo~se
I wanna be just li~ke you
Someday I'll be
Just li~ke-
I wanna be
Just li~ke you
Just like you
Oh how I wish I could be soaring through the sky
If only I could stand upon the clouds up high
If only I could be just li~ke you
Someday I'll be flying abo~ve the world
One day I'll be more than just an ordinary girl
'Cuz I can be whate~ver I~ choo~se
I wanna be just li~ke you