Oh oh oh oh
Oh oh
Lights fade out in this crystal hole
I can't see you from down below
I can't do this without you
The green haze hides me from brighter days
All I'm seeing are shades of grey
I can't do this without you
The shield has crumbled, the fight begun
The sky is buzzing, I'll never run
My Cadence, my love song
The stars are shining for you alone
I know I can't win
My Cadence, my love song
Love's in bloom everywhere you go
I know I can't win
Without you by~ my side
Oh oh oh oh
Oh oh
Best friends even since we were young
I should have known, can't believe I was wrong
I need you here by my side
I've loved you since the day we met
I know your heart wouldn't stray from me yet
I~ need you here by my side~~~
The queen has risen, the throne undone
Shining Armor you must hold on
My Cadence, my love song
These stars are shining for you alone
I know I can't win
My Cadence, my love song
Love's in bloom everywhere you go
I know I can't win
Without you by~ myside
I won't give up and I will not die
I will stay strong and I will fight
Till you're here by my side
My Cadence, my love song
These stars are shining for you alone
I know I can't win
My Cadence, my love song
Love's in bloom everywhere you go
I know I can't win
Without you by~ my side
Oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh
Oh oh