Food, store, we, I, I, win, win
I, win, win, do look, down
Cold or, cold or, cold, win, win
We, Food, we, we, I, I, win, win
I, win, win,
Do look, down, cold or
Just fine, hint, hint
Food, store, we, I, I, win, win
I, win, win
Do look, down, cold or
Cold or, cold, win, win
We, food, we, we, I, I, win, win
I, win, win,
Do look, down, cold or
Just fine, hint, hint
Food, store, we, I,I
I win, win, do look, down
Cold or, cold or, mean, -come
We, food, we, we
I, I, I win, win
Do look, down
Cold or, just fine, mean, -come
Food, store, we, I, I, win, win
I, win, win
Do look, down
Cold or, cold or, mean, -come
We, food, we, we
I, I, win, win
I, win win, do look, down
Cold or, just fine, mean, -come
Plant, our, care, seeds, sunshine
Colorful flowers
So much to do, -wers, ti-ny, seeds
Plant,Plant, our, care, with the
Colorful flowers,
Task, the ground
Sunshine, celery stalks
Plant, our, care, seeds, sunshine
Colorful flowers
So much to do, -wers
Tiny, seeds~
Plant, plant, our, care, with the
Colorful flowers
Task, the ground
Sunshine, celery stalks
Food, store
We, I, I, I win, win
Do look, down, cold
Or, cold or, mean, -come
We, food, we, we
I, I, I win, win
Do look, down, cold or
Just fine, mean, -come
Plant, our, care, seeds
Sunshine, colorful flowers
So much to do, -wers, tiny seeds~
Plant, plant, our, care, with the
Colorful flowers
Task, the ground
Sunshine, celery stalks
Plant, our, care, seeds
Sunshine, colorful flowers
So much to do, -wers, tiny seeds~
Plant, plant, our, care, with the
Colorful flowers
Task, the ground
Sunshine, celery stalks