These year stricken pa-ages
Are an old memory
And I've been here fo-or a-ages
And always will be
We'll never retu-u-u-urn to
The world the wa-ay it was
I'll never return to my friends up above
Through this life of adventures
Short lived fairytales
I've seen your de-epa-a-a-arture
But your faces rema-ain
Inside of my he-e-e-e-ad
'Til it's all said and done
You never betra-ayed me, my friends up above
The-ere's so many diff'rent e-e-eyes
They wander to and fro
But how can I be fi-i-ine
If none of them are yours
Now it's time to depart and
We say our goodbye-es
We've all come so fa-ar
Everyone has their ti-ime
But I'll see you in the stars tonight
Look at what it's become
I should not have doubted my friends up above