As dawn shines on us every morn'
The fire of friendship is reborn
And all the fri-endships we have made
We cherish in every way
Loyalty binds us and makes us strong
Honesty shows that we belong
And kindness shared will unite us through each day
The fire of friendship lives in our hearts
As long as it burns, we cannot drift apart
Though quarrels arise, their numbers are few
Laughter and singing will see us through
We are a circle of pony-y friends
A circle of friends
We'll be to the very end
Winter brings all its cold and storm
The glow in our hearts keeps us warm
The friends we now call our family
Will a-always see us through
Loyalty binds us and makes us strong
Honesty shows that we belong
And kindness shared will unite us through each day
The fire of friendship lives in our hearts
As long as it burns, we cannot drift apart
Though quarrels arise, their numbers are few
Laughter and singing will see us through
We are a circle of pony-y friends
A circle of friends
We'll be to the very end