Got my sword with Sharpness two
Look that Zombie's got one too~ What?!
Out of bread what do I do?
I'm low on hearts this is my doom~
I don't even have a tool
Come on Button play it cool
Though I'm here to fight for you
I'm biting more than I can chew~
My life flash~es by through that
End~er eye I'm scared~ oh well
And I'm pret~ty sure there's a
Big Creeper right there~ Oh dang
Don't~ mine at night
I know you're lookin' at that cave
And you're feelin' kinda brave
Go to bed you'll be alright
Don't~ mine at night
Don't go deeper make a change
Get that gold and get away
Zombies wanna' eat our brains
Don't mine at night
I'll fight away the skeletons
While you're looking for diamonds
They're getting closer better run
Don't mine at night
No this won't be our final day
Take my hoof we'll find a way-ay a-woah~
Don't~ mine at night
I turn a sec' you're getting shot
Then you jump through a portal Well why not?
When I think it can't get worse
An Ender herd shows up of course~
Now you say you need glowstone
And want to mine it on your own
Then to save you from the lava
I fell in I should have known~
This is the~ last time I try to
Be your light I failed~ so bad
I lost all~ my stuff it was
Really tough that's it~ Rage Quit!
Don't~ mine at night
I know you're lookin' at that cave
And you're feelin' kinda brave
Go to bed you'll be alright
Don't~ mine at night
Don't go deeper make a change
Get that gold and get away
Zombies wanna' eat your brains
Don't mine at night
Please don't get caught by skeletons
While you're looking for diamonds
They're getting closer better run
Don't mine at night
No this won't be your final day
Hold on tight I'm on my way-ay a-woah~
Don't~ mine at night