If I'm a diamond then why do I feel so rough?
I'm as strong as a stone, even that's not enough
There's something jagged in me
And I've ma-ade such mistakes
I thought that diamonds were hard
Tho-ugh I feel I could break
Would you beli-eve
That I've always wished
I could be somepo-ony else?
Yet I can't se-e-e
What I need to do
To be the pony I wanna be
I've been told my who-ole life
What to do-o, what to say
Nopony showed me that the-ere
Might be some better way
And now I feel like I'm-m lost
I don't kno-o-ow what to do
The ground is sinking awa-ay
I'm about to fall through
Would you beli-eve
That I-I've always wished
I could be someponyelse?
Yet I can't se-e-e
What I-I need to do
To be the pony I wanna be
I know you were worried
For a second there, weren't you?
Hah! Well, I think it's all gonna work out just fine
Mister President
We'll build that playground fo-or all of u-us to enjoy
So full of games, there's eno-ugh fo-or each girl and boy
I wanna help and do-o everythi-ing that I can
I'm here to show you what cha-anged, listen up, here's the plan!
Bring it in! That's right, keep it coming!
Hey there, you with the amazing strength!
Can you help them move that merry-go-round across the lawn?
Thank you so much!
And you, with the super teeth
We need you to help with that teeter-totter
You've got it, that's the spirit!
There's so much I can do-o to help everypony else
I see the light that shines in me
I know I can be my better self
I can free the pa-ast
'Cause now the future's bright for me
My cutie mark has set me free
To do what's right
And be the pony I wanna be