I’m your stallion in shining amour, my name implies it
Far from famous, but in bliss, I live, my dreams define it
Little nerdy but all too study till you arrived
Knocked me down, filly, I've got stars in my e~yes
She's the top mare in town
High class and wearing the crown
Fair princess, got me speechless
There ain’t no class that can teach this
She’s got my heart tied in knots
I swear that ready or not
She’ll know my name
I just hope somehow that you feel the sa~me
Cause’ when you’re here, I don’t know what to do
My hopes are fly~ing high
And when you’re near, I don’t know what to do
When you look my~ wa~~y
And I know, that you are out of my league
But you stole my~ heart and gave it away
I know this isn’t right but these feelings I have won’t go away
Go away
Royal Princess with royal duties, a royal pain and
Everypony, for my hoof, in marriage they campaign and
I had no idea if my prince I could choose
Until my heart stopped, when I looked at you~
But I have checked all the cha~rts
No way I’m throwing my da~rts
This stallion’s the perfect one
My shining second to none
He is so precious you kno~w
Whenever he says “Hello!”
My special somepony
I’m hoping that you might agree~ ~~~
When you’re here, I don’t know what to do
My hopes are fly~ing high
And when you’re near, I don’t know what to do
When you look my~ wa~~y
And I know
That you are out of my league
But you stole
My~ heart and
Gave it away
I know this isn’t right but these feelings I have won’t go away
Go away
And it won’t go~ away
I’m on top of the world, singing out my love fo~r you
And I don’t want it to go~ away
Got a passion to go the distance all fo~r you
And everypony’s saying we~ are crazy
But I’d do it all a~gain
If it means I can be there by your si~de
And be there till the~ end!