Ah~~~~~
I've kicked dragons in the face
I've won death in the race
I clear skies in ten seconds flat
I bet you can't beat that
I fly faster than the sound
I'll beat my foes to the ground
I'm the strongest thing around
I'd kick the shit out of hell hound
Like a flaming arrow
Flying over castle walls
Burning down my enemies~
Leading my friends to victo~ry
I'm faster than a lightning
Soaring through the sky
Louder than the thunder
Roaring in the night~
Stronger than a hurricane
In all its might
Prouder than a lion
I'm ready to fight
Faster
Louder
Stronger
Prouder
Oh!
I'm a savior from the skies
Hero with no disguise
Brighter than the thousands suns
I'll be there with blazing guns
I am your turbolover
It takes days to recover
Being cool is my destiny
Kneel before my supremacy
Like armor piercing bullet
Going through the six inch~ steel
Destroying my enemies' guard
Leading my friends to victo~ry
I'm faster than a lightning
Soaring through the sky
Louder than the thunder
Roaring in the night~
Stronger than a hurricane
In all its might
Prouder than a lion
I'm ready to fight
Ah ah~ ah
Faster than a lightning
Soaring through the sky
Louder than the thunder
Roaring in the night
Stronger than a hurricane
In all its might
Prouder than a lion
She's ready to fight
I'm faster than a lightning
Soaring through the sky
Louder than the thunder
Roaring in the night~
Stronger than a hurricane
In all its might
Prouder than a lion
I'm ready to fight
Soaring in the sky
Roaring in the night
In all its might
I'm ready to fight
Ah ah
Ah oh
Come on!