Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-hoh-oh, whoa-hoh-oh
Moments pass like photographs
Like pages filled with our own pasts
You're the happy ending to thi-is tale
And now I ca-an't fail
I'm reckless without a plan
You know that I'm no superman
But I can keep you safe if you ho-old on
I know this can't be wrong
Can't do this without you
Together we can make it through
These roads around
The battleground
Chapters closed, on a new start
We're getting to my favorite part
'Cuz you're the only one
Who can tame my-y dra-agonheart
Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-hoh-oh, whoa-hoh-oh
Despite my strong desire
You sometimes feel my breath of fire
It doesn't mean I'm angry, just co-onfused
I don't know how to choose
Between my bitterness
And the ending that comes after this
I know I want you, though it's hard to change
So let's just turn the page
Can't do this without you
Together we can make it through
These roads around
The battleground
Chapters closed, on a new start
We're getting to my favorite part
'Cuz you're the only one
Who can tame my-y dra-agonheart
Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-hoh-oh, whoa-hoh-oh
Never feel like you are alone
In the midst of the fire, we found home
It's our happy ending
And no one's gonna stop us now
I'm a beast with a heart that's frozen
But with you, now my eyes are open
I see the struggles coming
But we will strike them down somehow
You're the savio-or of
My ability to love
I found the will to change i-n you
Though I'm still ashamed
Of how I start the flames
You accept me fo-or what's true
Can't do this without you
Together we can make it through
These roads around
The battleground
Chapters closed, on a new start
We're getting to my favorite part
'Cuz you're the only one
Who can tame my-y dra-agonheart
Can't do this without you
Together we can make it through
These roads around
The battleground
Chapters closed, on a new start
We're getting to my favorite part
'Cuz you're the only one
Who can tame my-y dra-agon-
heart~~~~~~!
Whoa-oh-oh, whoa-oh-oh
Whoa-hoh-oh, whoa-hoh-oh