She looks outsi-ide her wi-indow at the rising sun
And she also looks at the same ti-ime at her beloved one
Dinky's sorting out the mail for her in such a thoughtful wa-ay
She saddles up her ba-ags and
Peeks through the looking glass
And hears her daughter say
"Hey Mommy, can you se-ee how good you look today?
Your right eye has a sparkle, and the left one wants to play
Your mane looks extra shiny and your feathers extra so-oft
Your cutie mark reminds me that our love will never pop!"
Oh-oh-oh, Ditzy Doo~!
All the world's in love with you
It's like you're a fresh baked muffi-in
And the-e rest of us a-are you
Oh-oh-oh, De-er-py~
Te-ell me, can those bright eyes see?
You make living happie-er for everypo-ony
She takes off down the ro-oad, in
Search of the day's first ho-ome and
Although it takes a mo-oment, she spots the boutique
A white mare canters o-out and
Her lips rise from a po-out when
She cannot help but shout "Hello!" to that gray streak
Then in the ma-ar-ket-pla-ace where
Every eye knows her fa-ace, she's
Greeted by the-eir good grace, and
She-e has none to spare
A farm mare selling apples
Tosses our friend a ha-atful
It's more than she can grapple,
But she tha-anks the mare
Though she's a little wo-onky,
Each pony a-and each do-onkey
Together and all o-on key
Sing her a song
Oh-oh-oh, Ditzy Doo~!
All the world's in love with you
It's like you're a fresh baked muffi-in
And the-e rest of us a-are you
Oh-oh-oh, De-er-py~
Tell me, can those bright eyes see?
You make living happie-er for everypo-ony
Oh-oh-oh, Ditzy Doo~!
All the world's in love with you
It's like you're a fresh baked muffi-in
And the-e rest of us a-are you
Oh-oh-oh, De-er-py~
Tell me, can those bright eyes see?
You make living happie-er for everypo-ony
Oh-oh-oh, Ditzy Doo~!
All the world's in love with you
It's like you're a fresh baked muffi-in
And the-e rest of us a-are you
Oh-oh-oh, De-er-py~
Tell me, can those bright eyes see?
You make living happie-er for everypo-ony
Oh, you make living happie-er for everypo-ony
Oh, you make living happie-er for everypo-o-o-ony