Yeah I own this beat
You can call me the king or the ruler
Felon on bass, getting hoarse at the mic
We're getting twenty percent cooler
We had a great day out
Calling my name like Ferris Bueller
It's time to wrap this up
We're getting twenty percent cooler
Seven colors in your hair
Get your boots on dear 'cause we're going out there
Don't care 'bout the dress code
Put it on, let's go
Girls go wild 'cause we're going al fresco
Ha!
No need to perform
Hands on our bodies gonna keep our skills warm
We need social reform 'cause we're just so criminal
Linguist subliminal, damages minimal
Top percentile, largest fraction
Massive attraction, girl-on-girl action
Stop that, I'm gonna need a redaction
Drop that, you already got your reaction
Me? I'm gonna keep on smiling
You? You're gonna need restyling
I got the quote back
From the jeweler
You're getting twenty percent cooler
Yeah I own this beat
You can call me the king or the ruler
Felon on bass, getting hoarse at the mic
We're getting twenty percent cooler
We had a great day out
Calling my name like Ferris Bueller
It's time to wrap this up
We're getting twenty percent cooler
Shhh
Reduce that treble
There's an eight or a nine who think they're on my level
Like a rebel in a bunker getting shelled with a mortar
Bump up and down 'cause I think you oughta
Place your hand on my thigh
Don't be coy, I can hear you sigh
Grinding your hips, I'll be flashing my pink
And in ten seconds flat you'll be back with a drink
Wooo!
Bring out the Bacardi
Twilight Sparkle, up in the party
Tap that, like a phone in the cold war
Room on the third floor, knocking at my front door
Me? I'm kind of a rarity
You? Work that dexterity
Lean back now, here's what I meant
Getting cooler by twenty percent
Yeah I own this beat
You can call me the king or the ruler
Felon on bass, getting hoarse at the mic
We're getting twenty percent cooler
We had a great day out
Calling my name like Ferris Bueller
It's time to wrap this up
We're getting twenty percent cooler
Yeah I own this beat
You can call me the king or the ruler
Felon on bass, getting hoarse at the mic
We're getting twenty percent cooler
We had a great day out
Calling my name like Ferris Bueller
It's time to wrap this up
We're getting twenty percent cooler!