This day is going to be perfect
The kind of day of which I've dreamed since I was small
Everypony will gather 'round
Say I look lovely in my gown
What they don't know is that I have fooled them all
This day was going to be perfect
The kind of day of which I've dreamed since I was small
But instead of having cake
With all my friends to celebrate
My wedding bells, they may not ring for me at all
I could care less about the dress
I won't partake in any cake
Vows? Well I'll be lying when I say
That through any kind of weather
I'll want us to be together
The truth is I don't care for him at all
No, I do not love the groom
In my heart, there is no room
But I still want him to be all mine
We must escape before it's too late
Find a way to save the day
Hope? I'd be lying if I say~~~
That I don't fear that I may lose him
To one who wants to use him
Not care for, love, and cherish him each day
For I oh so love the groom
All my thoughts, he does consume
Oh, Shining Armor, I'll be there very soon
Finally, the moment has arrived
For me to be one lucky bride
Oh, the wedding we won't make
He'll end up marrying a fake
Shining Armor will be
Mine
All mine