Three minutes and dawn will arise~ again~
Three minutes and a blessing will shine~ on me
Three minutes and a blessing will shine~—
Filling me with song and wisdom and joy
'Cause I'll stay close~ to you
Without fear~ that you might forget~~
Oasis in my eyes~, an an~chor kee~ping~ me sane
"And you'll prove to me that I am made to be—"
"And you'll prove to me that I am made to be loved~"
I pray this story won't be ending in pain
'Cause I can't reach for you my dear
As these~ wings are stuck here~~
—stuck here~~
Warm~ breeze after warm~ breeze I try
And seize one of all these moments slipping by~~
And I'll try and I'll try and I'll try and I'll try and I'll try
And I'll try and I'll try and I'll try and I'll—
Seizing us before you'll fade~ into me~mories
Saving you before I'll fade into my dreams
And as your Angel, I~ know
This holy river will fore~ver flow~~~
River will fore~ver flow~
Hold on, my dear
Cause I will run, run, run to save you in the mor~—
I will run, run, run to save you in the mor~ning~
Oasis in my eyes~, an an~chor kee~ping~ me sane
"And you'll prove to me that I am made to be—"
"And you'll prove to me that I am made to be loved~"
I pray this story won't be ending in pain
—won't be ending in pain
'Cause I won't reach for you my dear
As these~ wings are stuck here~~