There's something about that magic~ girl
That brings a full stop to the whole~ world
When I look in her eyes
And suddenly nothing matters
Inspiring me to face my~ fears
Her magical spark brings me to~ tears
All these years
of me watching this show for little girls
Everyday~ I look and~ try
One day we'll~ see eye to eye
I'll break the fourth wall just for you
Reality can't hold us through
This chick means the whole world to me~
I just want everyone to see
I'd give it my all
Just~ to see her smile smile smile~
These people they can boo me~
This hate will never phase me
'Cause the look in those eyes
Makes this hell here all worthwhile~
Twilight Sparkle you're my reason to live
No other girl out there can com~pare
Believe me I've looked just every~where
And I swear
From the bottom of my heart I mean this
Your eyes are a beacon shining~ bright
Your hair in the wind bringing to~ light
All the feels
It's too bad for me you don't even exist
Everyday~ I look and~ try
One day we'll~ see eye to eye
I'll break the fourth wall just for you
Reality can't hold us through
This chick means the whole world to me~
I just want everyone to see
I'd give it my~ all
Just~ to see her smile smile smile~
These people they can boo me~
This hate will never phase me
'Cause the look in those eyes
Makes this hell here all worthwhile~
Twilight Sparkle you're my reason to live
I dream of lying under the stars~
next to you~
With all this knowledge ain't there
Someone there worth~ sharing to?
And it hurts I'll never tell you~ this
It hurts I'll never feel your face
Three simple words~ to tell you that I~ love~ you~
There's something about that magic~ girl
That brings a full stop to the whole~ world
When I look in her eyes
And suddenly nothing matters
Go!
Everyday~ I look and try
One day we'll~ see eye to eye
I'll break the fourth wall just for you
Reality can't hold us through
This chick means the whole world to me~
I just want everyone to see
I'd give it my all
Just~ to see her smile smile smile~
These people they can boo me~
This hate will never phase me
'Cause the look in those eyes
Makes this hell here all worthwhile~
And though it seems impossible~
There's no harm hoping one day
That the girl of my dreams sees~
Beyond the lighted stage~
Till' then I'll hold you close~
And I wrote this song to show you
That I'm giving you my word
I just hope I'll make you proud~
And I'll keep on saying
Twilight Sparkle you're my reason to live