Chapter one I am starting
my adventure feeling strong
Explored the ocean then I found a chest
Uhohuhoh
Chapter two found out a deadly maze
I had to venture through
I almost died, need to take a rest
Stories~ are made to be eternal
but I could be wrong
Oh it's so easy to forget~
And it ends~ once the adventure is o~ver
Only the stories to remember~
Chapter three almost dying
in the blazing desert heat
But I still got the golden~ thread
Uhohuhoh
Chapter four I just escaped
an ancient tomb of doom
Yeah I think I deserve a~ rest
Stories~ are made to be eternal
but I could be wrong
Oh it's so easy to forget~
And it ends~~ once the adventure is o~ver
Only the story to remember~
Pa pararara papapapara
pararara Papapapara
pa ra~rara
pa rapapapara rarara
Stories~ are made to be eternal
but I could be wrong
Oh it's so easy to forget~
And it ends~~ once the adventure is o~ver
Only the story to remember~
Stories~ are made to be eternal
but I could be wrong
Oh it's so easy to forget~
And it ends~~ once the adventure is o~ver
Only the story to remember~
Pa papapara pararara
pa papapara pararara
Pa papapara para~rara
pa rapapapara pararara
Pa papapara pararara
pa papapara pararara
pa papapara para~rara
pa rapapapara parara ra