Mmmm…~~~~~
See that weight on your wings?
So no one should feel~ it
Yeah, you've got bigger dreams
So keep on believ~ing~
Don't let your cuts bleed into grey~
We've got each other and chances to take~~~
Yeah, you've got bigger dreams
So keep on believ~ing~
I'll chase the sky with you
I'll chase the night with you~
I'll chase the light with you
You wanna fly? I'll chase the sky
Woah oh oh oh, woah oh
If you wanna fly
I'll chase the sky
Anything in your heart
Is more than worth keep~ing
Mmm~, as you follow the stars
That's what you're need~ing~
Just say the word
And ba~by, you'll run~
I'll find a way to go beyond the sun~~
As you follow the stars
That's what you're need~~ing yeah~~!
I'll chase the sky with you
I'll chase the night with you~
I'll chase the light with you
You wanna fly? I'll chase the sky
Woah oh oh oh, woah oh
Woah oh oh oh, woah oh uh
Woah oh oh oh, woah
If you wanna fly
I'll chase the sky
I'll chase, I'll chase it all with you~
I'll run, I'll run, to the world with you~
I'll chase the sky with you
I'll chase the night with you~~
I'll chase the light with you
You wanna~ fly? I'll chase the sky
I'll chase the sky with you
I'll chase the night with you
I'll chase the light with you
You wanna fly? I'll chase the sky
Woah oh oh oh, woah
Woah oh oh oh, oh
Woah oh oh oh, woah~
If you wanna fly
I'll chase the sky