You know what this calls for?
This calls for extreme measures
Pinkie Pie style
Whee let's go!
Hi I'm Pinkie Pie and I threw this party just for you!
This is your singing telegram
I hope it finds you well you're you're you're
Giggle at the ghostly think you're really swell
All you have to do is take a cup of flour~
Put you in trances then
Now just take a little something sweet not sour~ a
So what do ya say?
Baking these treats is such a cinch
Add a teaspoon of vanilla
Add a little more and you count to four
And you never get your fill of of of
Is your singing telegram share you gotta
Giggle at the ghostly guffaw at the grossly
Help us celebrate
Eh eh eh to aye iggy me trances eh ee ee
We're all~ hoofed
Giggle at the ghostly-y-y-y
Now gotta stand up ah stand up tall ee
Eh eh eh to aye for me trances eh ee ee
We're all~ hoofed
You can make it if you try~
With a hop skip and a jump
Hoof hope it iggy me tran ee ee ee all~
We're finds you well
All you have to do is take a cup of flour~
Share gotta stand ee stand uh ay whoop it up
Hoofed hope it iggy me ah ee ee ee all~
We're finds you well
You can make it if you try~
With a hop skip and a jump
Eh eh eh to aye iggy me trances eh ee ee
We're all~ hoofed
Giggle at the ghostly-y-y-y
Now gotta stand up ah stand up tall ee
Eh eh eh to aye for me trances eh ee ee
We're all~ hoofed
You can make it if you try~
With a hop skip and a jump
Hoof hope it iggy me tran ee ee ee all~
We're finds you well
All you have to do is take a cup of flour~
Share gotta stand ee stand uh ay whoop it up
Hoofed hope it iggy me ah ee ee ee all~
We're finds you well
You can make it if you try~
With a hop skip and a jump
Eh eh eh to aye iggy me trances eh
We're all~ hoofed
Eh eh eh to aye for me trances eh
We're all~ hoofed you can
Eh eh eh to aye iggy me trances eh
We're all~ hoofed we're all~ hoofed