Pony Rock!
Yeah!
Woo!
Let's go!
Scratch and Neon's in the club tonight
Oh~ yeah we're gonna have a good~ time
So grab some pony don't be shy
It's our job to make you feel al~right
Let's raise the roof tonight's the night
We're gonna' party till the morning~ light
The house is hot the beat is tight
We just wanna' see you shake it!
The name's Neon Lights and I wanna' see you shake it I'm
the host of this party and I'm glad you could make it
I've got the music that booms show me what you've got
Now do your thing girls and flaunt that plot
On the dance floor is where we're living
You keep moving to the beat and the beat I'll keep delivering
Now that's a promise we're gonna' commit
Hey Vinyl Scratch! Spin that= at= at= at
Ayo what's up? I'm the other half half of this duo
Got my bass cannon set to ma= ma= max it's gonna' blow
It's Pony Rock!
Yeah so get them tails a= bouncing and get them
Hooves up in the air 'cause we are announcing it is!
Scratch and Neon's in the club tonight
Oh~ yeah we're gonna have a good~ time
So grab some pony don't be shy
It's our job to make you feel al~right
Let's raise the roof tonight's the night
We're gonna' party till the morning~ light
The house is hot the beat is tight
We just wanna' see you shake it!
Everyday I'm partying!
Pu= pu= pu= pu= put the lights on me
It's time for the only true party pony
It's Pinkie Pie here and I know you all missed me
But hey wait! There's room for three
Let's get some balloons!
Let's turn up the bass!
Gummy's here with me!
Now it's a party!
Get up get down
Put your hooves up to the sound
Jump up stomp down
Every pony hit the ground
Get up get down
Put your hooves up to the sound
Jump up stomp down
Every pony hit the ground
Get up get down
Put your hooves up to the sound
Put your hooves up put your hooves up
Everypony's in the club tonight
We're gonna' keep on having a good~ time
We got some help from Pinkie Pie
With Vinyl Scratch and Neon-on-on Lights
Woah~~~
Everyday we're par-partying!
Put your hooves up put your hooves up