Wind blows~ across this wasteland
No~ one here~ to~ see
I~ stand here by~ my~self
Except when you're~ with me
Days and days~~ go by~
Un~der the bur~ning~~ sky~
No matter how~~ we cry~~
Never can we~ answer why
Just keep on walking~, and don't~ look back
Just~ keep your eyes forward and~ stay~ on track
We'll find a way out~ of~ this mess~~, I pray
As~~ long as the spirits guide~ our~ way
Dusk falls~, howls in the dark
Evil comes out to~~ play
Disappear within our~ caves
As prey, we hide~ a~way
Days and days~~ go by~
As the months drag on
Un~der the bur~ning~~ sky~
Our old life is gone
No matter how~~ we try~~
Destinies are drawn
With the ri~sing of free~zing dawn~
Of freezing dawn~
Just keep on walking~, and don't~ look back
Just keep on walking~, and don't look back
Just~ keep your eyes forward and~ stay~ on track
Just keep your eyes forward and stay on track
We'll find a way out~ of~ this mess~~, I pray
We'll find a way out of this mess, I pray
As~~ long as the spirits guide~ our~ way
As long as the spirits guide our way
Just keep on walking~, and don't~ look back
Just keep on walking~, and don't look back
Just~ keep your eyes forward and~ stay~ on track
Just keep your eyes forward and stay on track
We'll find a way out~ of~ this mess~~, I pray
We'll find a way out of this mess, I pray
As~~ long as the spirits guide~ our~ way
As long as the spirits guide our way