Day one
War's begun
Come on Johnny get your gun
At fruit camp we learn to shoot
Boy, my helmet sure looks cute
March out, rendezvous
Hey, I'm speakin' fancy too!
Agent Orange? Just wait and see
Apple tanks are all we need!
Come on, now!
We're just gettin' started!
Day two
Lots to do
Rarity is workin' too
War is like an Apple Farm
Raze that field and raise this barn!
So far
It's a breeze~
Some civilian casualties
Hit your mark, a fatal blow
Grab your partner, do-si-do!
Yee hoo!
Play it, son!
Draft horse
No remorse~
Alpha, bravo, charley-horse
Family bondin', sellin' bonds
Signin' treaties, singin' songs
Take off!
Bombs away~!
In my plastic aeroplane
Hope my backup gets here soon
Hey, it's Twilight Sparkle's Balloon!
Day three
Out at sea~
In my apple submarine
In the silence, spendin' time
Ruminatin' on my crimes
Wake up
Not done yet~
Battle time, all hands on deck
We can sink their battleship
Burn them to a Honeycrisp
White flag?
We're not done~
Got those cowards on the run
Round 'em up, no need to stall
Take no prisoners, kill them all!
Get along, little doggies!
How do ya like them apples?
Day four
Won the war~
Loyal to my apple corps
Ponyville gives amnesty
Red delicious victory
Warhorse
Proud to be~
Freedom isn't Everfree
Hung my ribbons at the door
That's how Apples won the war