I face the brand new day~
Head clear and smiling face
Don't question who~ I am
The sun it warms my skin~
And a fresh start begins
A future bright~ and tall
Sure they might think I'm crazy
For staying in this old and dried up town
But I know they need me so
So how can I just go
My place is right here wait~ing
Right here where I am
Oh ooh oh ooh oh~
Oh ooh oh ooh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh
All these smiling faces
All these worn down places
Don't judge me they~ don't
Tell me who to be~
No frilly expectations
No lies no false pretences
This is where I can be so honestly
Just honest me~~~
There's some I've met around~
Who try to hold me down
There's hate within their hearts
No matter what it takes~
I'll never bend or break
I will stay proud~ and strong
I won't wear the mask they've made
No I will not be swayed
By those who say "no"
Their words won't leave a scar
They don't change who you are
My place is right here wait~ing
Right here where I am
Oh ooh oh ooh oh~
Oh ooh oh ooh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh
All these smiling faces
All these worn down places
Don't judge me they~ don't
Tell me who to be~
No frilly expectations
No lies no false pretences
This is where I can be so honestly
Just honest me~~~
All these smiling faces
All these worn down places
Don't judge me they~ don't
Tell me who to be~
No frilly expectations
No lies no false pretences
This is where I can be so honestly
Just honest me~~~