Ahh
Scoota~~loo
Don't you cry
We'll get by
I - I need you~ too
More than I knew
Before I met you
Scoota~~loo
Don't you fear
I am~ near
My world was~~ grey
But we found a way
A brand new~ day
I'll be there by your side
Remember that you're not a~lone
You'll always have a place to call~ home
When I'm with~ you
Never too far away
Don't forget that all it takes
Is to call on my~ name
And I'll be - I'll be right next to you
Scoota~~loo
Don't you see
We're a~ team
We'll chase the~ sun
Just for our~ fun
And when we're~ done
I'll be there by your side
Remember that you're not a~lone
You'll always have a place to call~ home
When I'm with~ you
Never too far away
Don't forget that all it takes
Is to call on my~ name
And I'll be - I'll be right next to you
I'll be right next~~ to you