Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum Yum Breakfast Burrito
Yum Yum Breakfast Burri-i-ito
Breakfast Burrito
You're hot and you're yummy
You fill up my tummy with hugs
Breakfast burrito
You're easy to eat
When I'm driving a car or a bus
Breakfast burrito
Every time that you're gone
I get sad and don't know what to do
Breakfast burrito
I'm in love I'm in love
I'm in love, I'm in lo-ove with you
Yum Yum Breakfast Burrito
Yum Yum Breakfast Burri-i-ito
Oh you're so much better
Than a regular burrito
They should call a regular burrito a nighttime
Breakfast burri-ito!
Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum
Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum
Breakfast burrito
You're fueling my dreams
With your morning time beans, a-alright
Breakfast burrito
When I'm lying in bed
Well I think about you a-all night
Breakfast burrito
There's a sparkling rainbow-y smile
In every bite I-I chew
Breakfast burrito
I'm in love I'm in love oh I'm still
In lo-ove with you
Yum Yum Breakfast Burrito
Yum Yum Breakfast Burri-i-ito
Yum Yum Yum Yum