Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
First, we thought that Babs
Was so really, really sweet
A new friend to have
Then it seemed like such a treat
But then, we found the truth;
She's just a bully from the east
She went from Babs, yeah,
To a bully and a beast
Everywhere we turn, she's just a step ahead
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, what we gonna do?
Got a bully on our tail
Gotta hide, we gotta bail
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, if she's after you
Gotta run, we gotta flee
Gotta hurry, don't you see?
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, she's just a bad, bad seed
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Hidin' from a bully,
We know it isn't right
But the Cutie Mark Crusaders,
We aren't lookin' for a fight
Oh, she'll go home soon,
And then we'll have some peace again
But for now, we're staying out of her way 'til then
Everywhere we turn, she's just a step ahead
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, what we gonna do?
Got a bully on our tail
Gotta hide, we gotta bail
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, if she's after you
Gotta run, we gotta flee
Gotta hurry, don't you see?
Why so mean? Why so crude?
Why so angry? Why so rude?
Can't you be nice? Can't we be friends?
Isn't it sad is this how it all ends?
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, she's just a bad, bad
Babs Seed, Babs Seed, she's just a bad, bad seed