Crystal Prep students are super athletic
Super smart, and super motivated
But there's one thing they aren't
They aren't Wondercolts
We've fought magic more than once
And come out on top
Oh oh
There's other schools, but none can make those claims~
Na, na-na-na-na, oh
Together we are Canterlot
Come and cheer our name
Oh oh
This will be our year to win these games
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
And now our time has finally arrived
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
And you know, at the end of the day, it is we who survive
Hey!
We're not the school we were before
Before!
Yeah, we're different now
Oh oh
We overcame the obstacles we faced
Overcame the obstacles we faced
We're Canterlot united
Unite!
We'll never bow~~
Oh oh
So get ready to see us in first place
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
Three! Two! One! Go!
And now our time has finally arrived
Our time is now!
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
Oh oh
And you know, at the end of the day, it is we~ who survive
At the end of the day, it is we~ who survive
Na, na, na-na-na-na~
Wondercolts united together
Wondercolts united forever
We'll always be Wondercolts forever
Na, na, na-na-na-na~
Wondercolts united together
And now our time has finally arrived
Na, na, na-na-na-na~
Wondercolts united forever
'Cause we believe in the magic of friendship
Na, na, na-na-na-na~
Wondercolts united together
And you know, at the end of the day, it is we~ who survive
At the end of the day, it is we~ who survive
At the end of the day, it is we~ who survive!