You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
And I captivate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~
You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
See me dominate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~
You think you've got what it takes
To go toe to toe?
I've got more moves
Than you'll ever know
I own the stage
I'm all the rage
You're from the past
I'm from the Space Age
Come on, you're just making noise~
Listen how my music destroys
Anything you throw at me
I'm gonna throw back, just wait and see~
You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
And I captivate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~~
You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
See me dominate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~
I'm here to take you down a peg
Oh, whoa, oh whoa oh whoa oh oh
By the time I'm done, you're gonna beg
To be in my band - Application rejected!
Don't look so sad and so dejected
Don't mean to brag, don't mean to boast
But I'm a six-course meal and you're just burnt toast
Think I'm gonna ever give up?
No, never, ever, ever, ever!
Come on, you're just making noise~
Listen how my music destroys
Anything you throw at me
I'm gonna throw back, just wait and see~
You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
And I captivate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~
You better believe
I've got tricks up my sleeve
See me dominate
'Cause I'm powerful and great~~