Once upon a time
In a faraway land
There was a mighty hero
Glorious and brave
His breathe is flame
And his skin is steel
All your diamonds and rubies would be eaten by him
He rides the alicorn
When the lightning strikes
Even small could be the greatest hero of the world
Spike, the Dragon Lord!
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord~!
The elders foretold
That the day should come
When the hero will raise to save the Crystal Heart
All the enemies, beware
When you see his spikes
You'd better run
You have no chance to survive~
He rides the alicorn
When the lightning strikes
Even small could be the greatest hero of the world
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord!
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord~!
Spike, the dragon lord
And someone may ask "How could the dragonlord
Have no weakness at all?"
While his breathe is flame
And his skin is steel
His heart is no longer belong to him
Although every filly lays down at his feet
Afore the only mare he would bow his knee
But he's got no time to lose
His bushido calls
He must fight the other dragons
To be the only dragonlord~
We call for the heaven
We call for our Lord
We'll be thankful forever
For his mighty sword
We call for his wisdom
We pray for his health
Even little dragon
Could be a King
Spike, the Dragon Lord
He rides the alicorn
When the lightning strikes~
Even small could be the greatest hero of the world
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord!
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord~!
Spike, the Dragon Lord
He rides the alicorn
When the lightning strikes
Even small could be the greatest hero of the world
Spike, the Dra~gon Lord!