[Trumpet noises]
[More trumpet noises]
Sister
Why hast thou made such noise~
Thou needth an instructor~~
Alas, thou has brought shame to the kingdom
So now go moon 1000 years bye bye banish time~
Sry k thx
Sister
Thou art such a~ dick~~
Thou art only jealous thy musical talent
We could totally taketh thou 1v1
Cometh at me bro
[Twilight reading a book on how to cook dragons]
[Realizes Spike is a dragon]
[Shopping list]
[Attempts to subdue target]
[Letter from Celestia] Go to Ponyville. Kthx. pc
Damn it
Twilight: CHANGELING ATTACK!
Twilight: Spike! Do the fire breath SWOOSH thing!
...
Twilight: You're fired.
I am on a mountain
Why am I on a mountain
I am cold. Somepony get me down
Or at least bring me a coat
And mittens
Oh crap, Luna is back
THOU HAST RETURNTH
BEHOLD THY RIGHT LEG
AND TRUMPET ARMY
We be pirates now
Give us your booty (lol booty)
[Threatening trumpet sounds]
We have learned of our misguided ways and wish to atone for our past misdeeds.
Allow us but a chance to showth thou that we have become humbled, just and kind.
Our soul hath been cleansed by the shining light of the moon and wishes for nothing
else then to walk the land once again under the fair golden light of our sister.
We, too, could become the best of companions and walk together, side by side.
I ask for thou to open thy heart and giveth mercy.
tldr;
f&$#
[Adorable cannon sound]
glomp
NMM: I smell tacos
[plbbt]
[POP]
Luna: Now I want tacos