The road before you~ calls for~ might~
It feeds on pain~~~
No mercy shall receive
The souls who foolishly seek fame~
Come down now, from your pipe dream
This is nothing more than desiccated fantasy
You want to fly, but you don't know~~~
It's too high~~~~~~~~~~~~
You're a little girl
With a little mind~
You'll stay in line
You're a little girl
It's a bigger world~
You've got loads of time
Before you make the climb~
You're dead in the water
No soldier, no saint, is my daughter
There's no way you'll be a~ble to shine~~~~~~~~
Are you mean, are you strong, are you wild~?
Do you push like a heavy machine~~ yeah~?
'Cause the road is long
Through the water and wind and the fire~
But if you're so bold~
Then you go and you make me believe~~ yeah~~
Had enough of you and your little cage~
I don't wanna stay
I won't o~bey~
I'm a little girl
Taking on the world~
You stay out of my way
'cause I'm not here to play~
You think that you know me
That I'm weak, like I'm glass
That needs holding
Well I'll end your delusion today~~~
'Cause I'm mean, and I'm strong, and I'm wild~~
And I push like a heavy machine~ yeah~~~~
'Cause the road is long
Through the water and wind and the fire~~
And I'm so bold
That I'll go and I'll make you believe~ yeah~~~
'Cause I'm mean, and I'm strong, and I'm wild~
And I push like a heavy machine~~ yeah~~~
'Cause the road is long
Through the water and wind and the fire~~
And I'm so bold
That I'll go and I'll make you believe~~ yeah~~
'Cause I'm mean, and I'm strong, and I'm wild~~
And I push like a heavy machine~~ yeah~~
'Cause the road is long
Through the water and wind and the fire~
And I'm so bold
That I'll go and I'll make you believe~~ yeah~~