Oh, through the divide I think I've heard a whisper
But was it really you, or just the breeze
Oh, in every shadow I'll search endlessly for
A sacred sign that proves you true, so far from me
Can you feel~ me?
Can you feel me…~
'Cause I~ can feel you
Oh, the gate is waiting in the land between us
And if you only knew, it's where you'd be
Oh, it's been hidden by the dreamy darkness
One day I know you'll pull me through
Can you feel me?
Think of all the lives~ you might have lived and
All the hope you might have gi~ven
If the stars were turned
Another way
Can you feel me?
Oh, can you feel me…
Ah~
Oh, the gate is waiting in the land between us
And if you only knew, it's where you'd be
Oh, it's been hidden by the dreamy darkness
One day I know you'll pull me through
Can you feel me?
Oh~, through the divide I think I've heard a whisper
But was it really you, or just the breeze
Oh~, in every shadow I'll search endlessly for
A sacred sign that proves you true, so far from me