Beyond the fields of grass~
She left her tattered past~
Fell into a tangled heap~
Skyward all her thoughts did leap~
Celestia~ didn't shine today~
All our skies are dark and grey~
She wonders how she lost her way~
But now there is no way~ left to lose
Out past~ the setting sun~~
Way out where~ the moon~ becomes~~
An ancient dream~ of stars divine
Imprisoned her by~ their design~
What force hid~ the warmth that flowed
Chilled her step on every road
Though these are~ the seeds she sowed~
Can she find her way back? Luna's ruse~
Way out~ here~
I rest a dreamless sleep
In the walls
Compressed that I can't pass
Feeling lost~
It glows a beacon distant
In my~ shrouded throes
I'm not existant
Luna's ruse~
Oh Luna's ruse~