A feeling stirring deep down inside my soul
The rhythm's taking ho-old
And it's about to ro-oll
A million sparkles falling across the floor
So DJ give it mo-ore
It's what we're lo-oking for
Dance the night away
All our friends right by our side
It doesn't matter what style you bring
We're about to go on that ride
It's Dance Ma-agic
Once you ha-ave it
Let your body move
Step into the musi-i-ic
It's Dance Ma-agic
And it's ele-ectric
Let your body move to the mu-usic
Doesn't matter what style you got
Just keep dancin' on that spot
Friends like you for who you are
Dance queen, on the scene, superstar
Crystal Prep, you've got the moves
Rainboom bringin' all the grooves
Put 'em together and make 'em fit
Crystal Rainbooms, Dance Magic
Dance the night away
All our friends right by our side
It doesn't matter what style you bring
We're about to go on that ride
It's Dance Ma-agic
Once you ha-ave it
Let your body move
Step into the musi-i-ic
It's Dance ma-agic
And it's ele-ectric
Let your body move to the mu-usic
Crystal Rainbooms got a style that's all our own
Dancin' nonstop
Body movin' in the zone
Bring whatever style you've go-ot
'Cause the party is going o-on
It's Dance Ma-agic
And it's ele-ectric
Let your body move to the mu-usic