OH, COME ON!
I woke up but I wish I was dreaming
I rub my eyes just to check what I’m see~ing
You came in last night
And took everything that’s mi~ne
You came into my li~fe
And I would give you anythi~ng
But it loo~ks like that wasn’t enough
And now you’ve taken everythi~ng
Then why do I still want you?
I just wanna ha~te you
But I can’t help but lo~ve you
Maybe the rea~son
Is I can’t live without you
This is a nightmare
You're the devil that’s lau~ghing
My heart skips a bea~t and
Now I am gasping for air
I think of you each and every Saturday
But after that you hurt me each other day
I blast off, touch down
I keep coming back for more
With all the sh*t you do
You'd think by now I’d have walked awa~y
But a voice inside my head
Keeps begging me to sta~~y
Oh, why do I still want you?
I just wanna ha~te you
But I can’t help but lo~ve you
Maybe the rea~son
Is I can’t live without you
This is a nightmare
You're the devil that’s lau~ghing
My heart skips a bea~t and
Now I am gasping for air
You’re the drug a~nd I’m the addict
Why can’t I just quit you~?
Oh, might as well live with it...
Love and tolerate, you know?
I just wanna ha~te you
But I can’t help but lo~ve you
Maybe the rea~son
Is I can’t live without you
This is a nightmare
You're the devil that’s lau~ghing
My heart skips a bea~t and
Now I am gasping for air