Fluttershy, Fluttershy, Fluttershy can hardly fly!
Hey sky, I wanna rip you up
Maybe I'm not strong enough
Maybe I'm not fast enough
Sister Shy~
Oddest of all us pegasi
Maybe you're the one I want
Maybe you're my hospital
Sift me with your wings
I'll carry you home
Risk it this time
You're so much more than you think, little pony
Building a symptom won't cure you
Only facing what keeps you hiding
Wayward cloud
Chase this ground your whole life
You must go on
You must go, go on
I'll go on
Oh, don't you cry
Dear we're here~
Sister tampopo right by your side
Dear you hear~ this all the time
Fluttershy, Fluttershy, Fluttershy can hardly fly!
Sister Shy~, flower of all things sweet and kind
Maybe you're a little late
Maybe you're a hurricane
Please stay a while
Are these feathers I see spinning with me?
A piece of the puzzle finds herself