Yay yay
Yay
Yay yay yay
Who's always first to the scene
When there is a pony in need?
Who'll be there to save the day and
In the coolest way?
She'll be there ready to fly~
Call for help she~ won't pass you by
If you need a helping hand
She'll cometo make a stand
Rainbow Dash it's time to try your best now
Never ever break your vow
If there's trouble be there in a flash
Never give up Rainbow Dash
You can win if you don't hold back here
So in earnest do we cheer
If there's trouble be there in a flash
Never give up Rainbow Dash
You stand up even alone
Ready to protect our home
Ponyville depends on you
So youmust carry through
Rainbow Dash it's time to try your best now
Never ever break your vow
If there's trouble be there in a flash
Never give up Rainbow Dash
You can win if you don't hold back here
So in earnest do we cheer
If there's trouble be there in a flash
Never give up Rainbow Dash
Yay