Ah~~
Dun duh duh da~ da
Duh duh dun~ da dun da duh da da
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Until you all shared its magic with me
While ago if you would ask me~
What I watch~ in my spare time
No I prob'ly wouldn't tell you~
What was really on my mind~
But lately I've been thinking~
Of a rea~son I should hide
F-I-M as if to mention it where painful~
When it feels so good inside
Why can't I mention Fluttershy~
And her timid loving mind?
How she can be herself near animals~
But shies away from her own kind
Why can't I mention Pinkie Pie~
And the way she kind of
Acts a bit like me sometimes?
You see I use to hate that I liked
My Little Pony not any more
And I'm proud to be a brony
Many try to make me feel embarrassed~
Their attempts have been in vain
Though they tell me I'm the one with problems~
They're the ones who are insane
For those who watch but won't admit it~
Well you shouldn't be like that
Cause you could be twenty percent cooler
In ten seconds flat
Why don't you mention Rainbow Dash
And her acrobatic skill?
How she will try her hoof in~
Anything just to get a little thrill
Why don't you mention Applejack
Talk about her honest
Southern style~ pow~er of will?
See you don't~ have to fake~
That you hate~ My Little~ Pony~
Yeah yeah yeah~
Shout it out~
I'm~ proud to be a bro~ny yeah~~~
I'm proud to be a brony
My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Until you all shared this magic with me
Thread by thread stitching it together
Twilight's dress cutting up the pattern snip by snip
Cupcakes so sweet and tasty
Cupcakes don't be too hasty
Winter Wrap Up Winter Wrap Up
'Cause tomorrow spring is~ here
So I'm gonna mention Rarity
And how she's oh so lady like~
But even though she's prim~ and prop~~er
She could make it in a fight~
And I'm gonna mention Twilight
And she's kind~ of nerdy
Boasts a power tucked away
Could take an Ursa any day~
How~ 'bout you? Would you do
What I~ do or be phony?~ Hah
I'm asking you now
You proud to be a brony? Yeah~
You proud to be a bro~ny?~