'Been lurking in these shades for so long
But I'm working and quite soon they'll be gone
My changelings now's the time for revenge
And I'm saying: rush inside and change
Hive! Now you're free to~~ feed
I've satisfied your~~ need~
Been starving, seen no love for so long
But Queen's carving on her way and she's strong
She's leading - we are following her
Love's bleeding, ponies - give us more
Queen! We're at your command
We're fighting to the end
Hive! Now you're free to~~ feed
Queen! We're at your com~mand
I've sa~tisfied your~~ need~
We're fighting to the~end
Hive! Now you're free to~~ feed
Queen! We're at your com~mand
I've satisfied your~~ need~
We're fighting to the~