I still remember it like it was yesterday,
though it was countless moons ago
After he was defeated,
not much of our once beautiful home was left
And the two brave ones that stood up for us all
ruled Equestria from then on
One day, the younger one, saddened by our daily struggles,
proposed to form a new colony
where all of us would grow strong and happy
But the elder one forbade it,
for she felt that it would divide and shatter the weakened kingdom
forever
Nopony knows that we're still here,
smiling beneath the moonlight
while remembering our dear mother,
for we will forever be...
her children of the night
Come little children, I'll take thee away
Into a land of enchantment
Come little children, the time's come to play
Here in my garden of sha-a-adows
Follow sweet children, I'll show thee the way
Through all the pain and the sorrows
Weep not poor children, for life is this way
Murdering beauty and passions
Hush now dear children, it must be this way
Too weary o-of life and deceptio~ns
Come little children
I'll take thee away
Into a land of enchantment
Come little children
The time's come to play
Here in my garden of sha-ado-ows