Twilight is searching for
Stars to fill her sky
White light blinds her
The sun is far too~ bright
Dark night brings her
To somewhere deep inside
Twilight is searching
For something she can't find~
Something strange has happened to
The flowers and the trees
This is not, is not, the time
For them to change their leaves~
Something strange has happened to
The flowers and the trees
This is not, is not, the time
For them to change their leaves~
So Twilight wanders through
Letters she can't write
Time stands still when she
Looks into her eyes
Twilight's tears flow
And pools reflect her~ light
Try as she might
She cannot calm the tides~
Something strange has happened to
The rainbow in the sky
The light has cast a shadow and
The colors aren't quite right
Something strange has happened to
The rainbow in the~ sky
The light has cast a shadow and
The colors aren't quite right~~
As Twilight is burning up
A fire~ she can't~ fight
Crystal trees shine
With leaves as sharp as knives
Ink and graphite
Become the darkest light
Twilight takes flight
She cannot bear to cry~
Something strange has happened to
The sun, the moon and stars
The constellations vanished, but
Their light has left a scar
Something strange has happened to
The sun, the moon and stars
The constellations vanished, but
Their light has left a scar
But Twi~light is fading as
Darkness fills the sky
Moonlight is dripping in-
To her violet eyes
Starlight is singing
A lonely lullaby
Daylight is dancing
Away from paradise~
Something strange has happened to
The rivers and the sea
The water's standing still
And reflections can't be seen
Something strange has happened to
The rivers and the~ sea
The water's standing still
And reflections can't be seen
Ah ah ah
Ah ah ah ah
Now Twilight is sleeping as
Memories pass her~ by
Sun follows moonshine
The beauty of the~ night
Twilight is ending
And so she says goodbye