In the end, it was easy for my life to break
Every choice that I made was another mistake
But a second chance takes all the world for~ a turn
One more chance to entrance and to love and to learn
And woah-oh-oh-woah-oh, the world will be free
And woah-oh, you'll be~ with me
I used to wonder what friendship could be
Now you're here to share it with me-e-e
This feeling is taking me o~ver
This feeling that I can't deny
'Cause through all the pain~ and the crip~pling loss
It's so good to know I'm alive
And I won't give in to the sor~row~~
And I will~ not rest till~ I've won~
And I'll make a brighter tomor~~ro-o-ow
And give you the world when I'm done
And I'll leave you~ the world when I'm done
Broken hearts can restart, see the light in the skies
Looking into the truth in the depths of your eyes
No more sorrow arri~ving~ at some better place
Finding home in the heart and the smile on your face
And woah-oh-oh, the world will be free
And woah-oh-oh-woah-oh, you'll be~ with me
I used to wonder what my life could be
Now you're here to share it with me~~
This feeling is taking me o~ver~~
This feeling that I can't deny
'Cause through all the pain and the crip~pling loss
It's so good to know~ I'm~ alive~
And I won't give in to the sor~row~~
And I will~ not rest till~ I've~ won
And I'll make a brighter tomor~~ro-o-ow
And give you the world when I'm done
And I'll leave you the world when I'm done
Ah, ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah, ah, ah-ah
Ah, ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah, ah-ah-ah, ah
Ah-ah-ah, ah-ah, ah, ah-ah-ah-ah-ah, ah-ah
Ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah, ah, ah, ah
This feeling is taking me o~ver~
This feeling that I will be free
'Cause through all the pain and the weight of~ the world
It's so good to know~ you're~ with me~
This feeling is taking me o~ver~~
This feeling that I can't deny
'Cause through all the pain and~ the crip~pling loss
It's so good to know~ I'm~ alive~
And I won't give in to the sor~row~~
And I will~ not rest till~ I've won
And I'll make a brigh~ter tomor~~row
And give you~ the world when I'm done
And I'll leave you the world when I'm done