It's time for us to come together
It's the only way that things will ge-et better
It's time for us to take a stand
So come on and lend a helpi-i-ing hand
Fix it up
Yeah, it's alri-ight
We'll get it ready by toni-ight
Mix it up
Yeah, help a fri-end
We'll come together in the end
It's time to sho-ow that we've got school spirit
Raise your voice and le-et everyone hear it
It's time to sho-ow that we're strong
So come on everybody, sing a-along
Look ho-ow we've all
Come together
Things a-are only just
Starting to get better
Look ho-ow we've all
Come together
Things a-are only gonna get
Better, better, better, better!
Fix it up
Yeah, it's alri-ight
We'll get it ready by toni-ight
Mix it up
Yeah, help a fri-end
We'll come together in the end
Fix it up
Yeah, it's alri-ight
We'll get it ready by toni-ight
Mix it up
Yeah, help a fri-end
We'll come together, together now!