I never imagined my-yself o-ut o-on my o-own
Tryin' to find out what's ne-ext for me-e
The Cutie Mark Crusa-aders
Have always been my ho-o-o-o-o-o-o-ome
Maybe now, there's more that I could be-e
I guess as time go-o-oes by-y-y
Everypo-ony has to go-o out on the-ir o-own
And maybe someday I'll ha-ave to try-y-y
Somethin' new that's just for me
A little somethin' that co-uld be-e
Just my-y o-own and I won't feel so-o left behi-i-ind
We used to say-y that we'd be-e always side by si-ide
Maybe thi-ings are changin' and this could me-e-an goodbye
I always tho-ught our friendship was all I'd ever ne-ed
We've always be-en crusadin' - what else is there for me?
I guess as time go-o-oes by-y-y
Everypo-ony has to go-o out on the-ir o-own
And maybe someday I'll ha-ave to try-y-y
Somethin' ne-ew that's just for me
A little so-omethin' that co-uld be-e
Just my-y o-own and I won't feel so-o left behi-i-ind