Greet the early morning glow
Before the sun~ kisses the hills
Brother, Sister, Gran in~ tow
Times like these I remember them still
Sweat dripping off my back
We work the hours of the sun
Bundle up the dry hay stacks
We don't rest up until we're done~~
Grittin' teeth and burning sides
The trees tremble at my hoof
I take the pain in my~ stride
I feel them here~, don't need no proof
Lay me down~ on golden~ fields
Rest my head down on the barley
Feel the sun upon my face
Watch the clouds~ a~~bove me race~~
Watch the clouds~ a~bove me race~~
And feel you closer than ever
I whisper while the apples~ fall
Pretend that it's you who speaks
I know you won't answer when I~ call
But I think you're there~ within the leaves~~
Feel the sun upon my face
Watch the clouds~ a~bove me race~~
And feel you closer than ever
You don't talk so much with~ words
As you do with summer breeze
That rests 'neath the wings of the~ birds
You move with grace and you move with ease~~
Guess that's what happens when you die
And you're gone much too soon
You leave a feather while you fly
For your loved ones to remember you by~~
Lay me~ down~ on golden fields
Rest my head down on the barley
Feel the sun upon my face~~
Watch the clouds a~bove me race~~
And feel you closer than ever
I feel you closer