Hay there Ms Derpy how's it
Going in Equestria?
I'm another world away but filly
You just look so pretty yes you do
Rainbow ain't got nothin on you
My dear Ms Derpy don't you worry don't you fret
I'll be there if you get lonely even
If we've never met we'll start to fly
Listen to my voice it tells no lies
Hey girl I really love your eyes~
And some day~ I'll wish upon a star
And wake up somewhere~ very far
A land~ I only heard about before
And the first~ thing that I'm gonna do is
Search right across that~ land for you
Because you are the pony I adore
And I~ swear I'll love you forever more
Hay there Ms Derpy I've got
So much that I want to say
If only I could speak with you
I know I'd find a way to say it all
Together into love we'd fall
My sweet Ms Derpy I know
That this song is getting long
It was meant to be so simple
I just don't know what went wrong it's
All for you
You know that I'll always come through
My Derpy Hooves this song's for you
And some day~ I'll wish upon a star
And wake up somewhere~ very far
A land~ I only heard about before
And the first~ thing that I'm gonna do is
Search right across that~ land for you
Because you are the pony I adore
And I~ swear I'll love you forever more