Night falls over town
The witching hour~ crashes in and all the monsters walk about
The sky is inked with flutters
The town is filled with mutters
The kings and queens of moonlight all~ step out
And I know where we're heading toni-ight
A small clearing lit by~ firelight
We'll act like animals until the break of dawn
And all around we'll be singin'
And I know it'll all turn out alright
We look odd to the ones who make their reign~ in su~nlight
But we pass them by without a worry or care
'Cause we know there's a whole 'nother world~~ out there
And I know~ it'll all turn out alright
We look odd to the ones who make their reign~ in su~nlight
But we pass them by without a worry or care
'Cause we know there's a whole 'nother world
And I know where we're heading toni-ight
A small clearing lit by~ firelight
We'll act like animals until the break of dawn
And all around we'll be singin'
"Woah-oh-oh-oh-oh"
Go!
And I know where we're heading toni-ight
A small clearing lit by~ firelight
We'll act like animals until the break of dawn
And all around we'll be singin'
"Oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh"
And I know where we're heading toni-ight
A small clearing lit by~ firelight
We'll act like animals until the break of dawn
And all around we'll be singin'