I still can remember the tear in her eye
When she cast her spell and said nothing more than "goodby-y-ye"
The faces fade as the memories age
A lifetime lost and a chi-ildhood thrown awa-a-ay
Best of luck to the world out there and I hope yo-ou'll be o-okay
Meanwhi-ile, I'm feeling right at home
With what I got around me
Seems li-ike I would be all alone
If no one ever found me
If you come looking around for me, leave me be-e
'Cause the only friends I've got are all I-I need
The hunter finds his food for the night
With a quick-sharp aim and a hunger from deep insi-i-ide
The little bear goes where his mama will go
The mother bear goes where the little cub knows to fo-ollow
The rest of them in the world out there have a differe-ent way o-of life
Meanwhi-ile, I'm feeling right atHome
With what I got around me
Seems li-ike I would be all alone
If no one ever found me
If you come looking around for me, leave me be-e
'Cause the only friends I've got are all I-I need
Meanwhi-ile, I'm feeling right at home
With what I got around me
Seems li-ike I would be all alone
If no one ever found me
If you come looking around for me, leave me be-e
'Cause the only friends I've got are all I-I...
They're all I-I need