Tell me it's perso-o-nal, then say it twice
But I can hear eve-en more behind your eyes
There's no illusion~ whe-e-en you hi-ide your lies
Why don't we sit and talk a while?
I don't want to take too~ long, or long at all
Just tell me how yo-ou feel, and share your thoughts
When I was your age I~ neve-er fe-elt the same
But you can tell me-e anywa-ay
(Don't run away)
You can pack your ba-ags
Buy your ti-icket, take yo-our train
You don't have to wa-ait a da-ay
(Don't run away)
The rain will soon come do-own
One day wash a-away this town
You can leave, but don't ru-un a-wa-ay
Woah-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh
I hope you're liste-ening just li-ike you say
I need a shoulde-er I can lean on for the day
I have been feeli-ing like I must be o-on my-y way
'Cause no one has told me-e I should sta-ay
Is that oka-ay?
(Don't run away)
You can pack your ba-ags
Buy your ti-icket, take yo-our train
You don't have to wa-ait a da-ay
(Don't run away)
The rain will soon come do-own
One day wash a-away this town
You can leave, but don't ru-un a-wa-ay
Woah-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh