I guess I'm up in spa-ace
We-ell, what can you do?
You shouldn't challenge fate
When you're likely to lo-ose
It's been a while since I took a vaca-ation
I'll just relax and watch as they rai~se the~ sun
So
This is what it's like
Ste-epping in sister's hooves
And this is ho-ow it feels
When you got nothing to lose
And I can't he-elp but thi-ink
Of everything I've done wrong
But now that I kno-ow, it's a wonder
Why I sent her here for so-o long
La da la la
La da la la da da da da da
It's been a couple weeks and I'm starting to shake
I can't believe I thought I was taking a brea~k
No walls to hold me in but I ca~n't brea~k out
Of all the stars around me I'm lo-osi-ing count
So
This is what it's like
Ste-epping in sister's hooves
And this is ho-ow it feels
When you got nothing to lose
And I can't he-elp but thi-ink
Of everything I've done wrong
But now that I kno-ow, it's a wonder
Why I sent her here for so-o long
It's been a thousand years
Never felt so alo-one
I don't know what I learned
I just want to go ho-ome
I'm not the princess everyone kne-ew be-efore
My sunlight hides away-y my sha-ado-owed core
So
This is what it's like
Ste-epping in sister's hooves
And this is ho-ow it feels
When you got nothing to lose
And I can't he-elp but thi-ink
Of everything I've done wrong
But now that I kno-ow, it's a wonder
Why I sent her here for so-o long
La da la la
La da la la da da da da da
La da la la da da da da-a da