Beats down the sun getting hotter
Cause these nights won't stay any longer
And I'd rather you near
Than far from here
And these streets don't get any longer
When you're this far from the harbour
Making it quite hard to sail away
And leave my hopes at bay
But now I'm gliding through the atmosphere
Bright lights to make it so clear
And I'll travel the stars till I find you
But these foggy nebulas around me
Cloud my vision until I can't see
Still I'll travel alone till' I find home
The sunlight it breaks through my cold walls
Through open windows, dark frozen halls
Lighting up the sky, days pass me by~
So I've built a starship in my room
To take me to a place I can see you
Because I cannot cope with my lost hope
But now I'm gliding through the atmosphere
Bright lights to make it so clear
And I'll travel the stars till I find you
But these foggy nebulas around me
Cloud my vision until I can't see
Still I'll travel alone till I find home~
These old nights aren't too nice to~ me
Left alone oh why can't I see
Hope that I once had the hope in you~
But you've opened my eyes to see
Stars that glisten all around me
Hope that I once had has been renewed
And now I'm gliding through the atmosphere
Bright lights to make it so clear
And I'll travel the stars till I find you~
'Cause I've found by all those around me
These future suns are all here to guide me
Through each and every day throw fears away~
Through my lunar telescope
I've found my Fort~~ Hope~