Shoop bee doo shoop shoop bee doo
Call upon the Sea Po~nies when you're in distress
Helpful as can be po~nies simply signal S O S
If you find you're past the drift and haven't got an oar~
Count upon the Sea Po~nies they'll see you~ to shore
Shoop bee doo shoop shoop bee doo
Are you sinking fast?
Had some nasty shocks?
Feeling like all hope is gone
And washed up on the rocks?
Washed up on the rocks
Shoop bee doo shoop shoop bee doo
Call upon the Sea Po~nies when you're in distress
Helpful as can be po~nies simply signal S O S
If your rudder runs aground~ or seaweed holds~ a grip kelp
Count upon the Sea Po~nies they'll see you
Sea Ponies Sea~ Po~nies
Simply signal S O~ S
Oh yes