Good night, my fellow ponies
For I shall guard your dreams
Until the moonlight lowers
You're safe from troubles life can bring
Close your eyes, leave behind
Worries, griefs and fears
Listen to twinkling stars
Whispers of the summer wi-ind
Night may not be light and bright
Like my sister's day
But it can take you far away
To-o heart's desired pla-ace
Hush, my little ponies
Catch your sweetest dreams
Fly amid the planets
Drift in sta-a-arry streams
Fear you not, I'll be there
Shall the nightmares come
Lay to rest~, be well prepared
To meet the sun at dawn
Night may not be light and bright
Like my sister's da-ay
But it can take you far away
To-o heart's desired lands