Wings that can't fly
They aren't wings at all
But he told me he believed~~
And now I'm on fire~
And I'm flying higher
Than I ever dreamed before~~
You got~ me soa~rin'
There's just one chance, one moment
Hold it fast, don't blow it
You got to stay~ strong
I'll tell you what he told me
That "yes, you are worthy"
"In the sky~ you belong"
Now pick yourself up, do it
You're a Wonderbolt? Then prove it!
Your heart won't steer you wrong
I can see that you've got talent
You're tough, you're smart, you're gallant
Colt, ain't you gonna soar
I'm not a mare to lie
I just can't deny
I think I've seen you before
Could it be that I, I know you?
Can you see it too?
I want to know you more~~~
More~~~~~~~
All those years ago
It was you who told me
Told me you believed
You got me soarin'
You got me Soarin
You got me
There's just one chance, one moment
Hold it fast, don't blow it
You got to stay~ strong
I'll tell you what he told me
That "yes, you are worthy"
"In the sky~ you belong"
Now pick yourself up, do it
You're a Wonderbolt? Then prove it!
Your heart won't steer you wrong
I can see that you've got talent
You're tough, you're smart, you're gallant
Colt, ain't you gonna soar
I'm not a mare to lie
I just can't deny
I think I've seen you before
Could it be that I, I know you?
Can you see it too?
I want to know you more~~~
More~~~~~~~