In the club smiles on my face
In the club please don't stop that bass
In the club just can't stop my feet
In the club shaking to the beat
In the club smiles on my face
In the club please don't stop that bass
In the club just can't stop my feet
In the club shaking to the beat
In the club smiles on my face
In the club please don't stop that bass
In the club just can't stop my feet
In the club shaking to the beat
In the club smiles on my face
In the club please don't stop that bass
In the club just can't stop my feet
In the club shaking to the beat
We're the mane six and we're cute chicks
Made you shit bricks? Take a pro tip
In the club you can't handle us
So slick so fierce so sclandalous
We party hard to our heart's desire
So hot that we set everypony on fire
O ther ponies jelly 'cause we look delicious
Wishin' they could be so Twilightlicious
Elements of kindness magic loyalty
Wanna be like us but you know you could never be
Honesty laughter and generosity
Always keep a standard to your fabulosity
We're gonna get this party started
Hope that you'll come and be a part and
Raise the roof to the city of Cloudsdale
Stamp on the ground and wave your tail
In the club smiles on my face
In the club please don't stop that bass
In the club just can't stop my feet
In the club shaking to the beat