I work the hardest when the sun is setting
I play the numbers but I keep forgetting
My broken heart, my beating chest
My blackened scars, my bated breath
My callus lungs, my empathy
My tired eyes, my hopes and dreams
I don't want to work myself to death
I don't want to break your concentration
Can I ever learn to love myself
Will I ever cure my loneliness
I don't wanna heed my own advice
I don't wanna feed my desperation
Even when the dirges start to play
Maybe I'll enjoy the silence
A marble counter and a plastic ghetto
A candy corset and a pink stiletto
My tangled mane, my tattered seams
My tiny thoughts, my reveries
My weathered veins, my hollow frame
My horoscope, my twisted fate
I don't want to work myself to death
I don't want to break your concentration
Can I ever learn to love myself
Will I ever cure my loneliness
I don't wanna heed my own advice
I don't wanna feed my desperation
Even when the dirges start to play
Maybe I'll enjoy the silence
Hard Knocks felt worn as the 9 to 5 tea parties rolled on
dreamlike, everything tinted by the soft salmon horizon
guided by giant little invisible hands of fate
she prayed some far dreamer would take her away
And when the doctor writes his last prescription
He'll shake his head to stave my sad addiction
My swollen neck, my second skin
My bloodied socks, my crooked chin
My wooden teeth, my splintered spine
My gauze, my pain, my god, my name
I don't want to work myself to death
I don't want to break your concentration
Can I ever learn to love myself
Will I ever cure my loneliness
I don't wanna live my life alone
I don't wanna plead with my own shadow
Baby when the hard knock life is won
Do you think I'll stop forgetting