Come on Eileen~
Poor old Johnnie Ray~~
Sounded sad upon the radio
He moved a million hearts in mo~no
Our mothers used~~
To sing~ along who'd blame them?
You're grown
So grown~~
Now~ I must say more~ than ever
Come on Eileen~
Too-ra-loo-~ra too-~ra-loo-~rye-~~ay
And we can sing just like our fa~thers
Come on Eileen~, oh~ I~ swear well he means
At this moment~
You mean
Everything~~
You in that dress, oh
My thoughts I confess
Verge on dirty~~~
Ah, come on Eileen~~~
Come on Eileen~
These people 'round here~~
Wear beaten-down eyes sunk in smoke-dried
Faces resigned to what their fate~ is
But not us no not us~~
We~ are far too young~ and clever
Remember~
Too-ra-loo-~ra too-~ra-loo-~rye-~~ay
Ei~leen I'll hum this tune fore~ver
Too-ra-loo-~ra too-ra-loo-~rye-~~ay
Come on Eileen~, oh~ I~ swear well he means
Ah, come on let's~
Take off everything~~
That~ pretty red dress
Oh~, Ei~leen tell him let's
Ah, come on let's~
Ah, come on Eileen~~~
Come on
Eileen ta-loo-rye-ay
Too-ra
too-ra ta-loo-ra
Oh~~~~~, Eileen~~~~, I said
Come on Eileen
Oh~, come~ on Eileen~~
We~~ are far too young~~ and clever
And things won't~ ever change and I say
Too-ra-loo-ra
Too-ra-loo-~rye-~~ay~
Come on Eileen, oh I
Swear well he means at this moment~
You mean everything~~ to me~
Oh~~~, to me~~~~
Whoa~~, Eileen~~~
You mean
E~verything~~~~