You see me soaring through the sky
I see you below as you walk on by
I could clear the sky in ten seconds flat
How about that? Oh, how about tha-at?
I could be sitting here on a cloud
Watching the sun as it starts to go down
The only thing missing
Is you by~ my side
Give me a smidge of confide-ence
Give me a speck of something that makes~ sense
Give me an idea of dependency~
Give me a dash of loya-alty~~
Loy~al~ty~
I could save my lonely soul for you~~~
But the feeling in my heart can't follow through~
You can give your broken heart to me~~~
'Cause you know that I'll stay with you~
That's why they call~ me loyalty~~
Loyal~ty
The sun shines bri-ight, yet the rain pours on
Rainbows here one minute and then they are gone
They remind me of me and you
What did you do? What did I do-o?
Determination~ in those eyes
Where has it gone? Has it said goodbye?
A lot's happened
But I'll stay by~ your side
Give me a smidge of confidence~
Give me a speck of something that makes sense
Give me an idea of dependency~
Give me a dash of loyal~ty~~
Loyal~ty~~~~
I could save my lo~nely soul for you~~~
But the feeling in my heart can't follow through~
You can give your broken heart to me~~~
'Cause you know that I'll stay with you~
That's why they call me loyalty
Time stands still when you're with~ me
How can I make you se-e-e?
Your crazy antics make me want to scream~
Your name so loud till my throat starts to~ bleed
To bleed~
I~ could save my lonely soul for you
But the feeling in my heart can't follow through~
You can give your broken heart to me~
'Cause you know that I'll stay with you~
That's why they call me loyalty~
I could save my lo~nely soul for you~~~
But the feeling in my heart can't follow through~
You can give your broken heart to me~~~
'Cause you know that I'll stay with you~
That's why they call, that's why they call me~
I could save my lo~nely soul for you~~~
But the feeling in my heart can't follow through~
You can give your broken heart to me~
'Cause you know that I'll stay with you~
That's why they call me loyal~ty~