Be yourself, they say, but be assertive
Hold your ground but do not be unkind
I have sought to be both lamb and lion
Heartache is the thing I tend to find
Can I only have what I can capture
Will I be unheard~ unless I shout
Clamor overwhelms~~ me and I wonder
What is there to be so~ loud about?
Many are the mu~sings of my shy~~~~~ heart
Though precious few are spoken out aloud
How I wish to wrap them up in confidence and style
And send them out like magic through the crowd
Then everyone would listen and I wouldn't be afraid~
I wouldn't shrink away~~ and disappear~~~
I don't want them to worship me or care that much at all
I only want to know~ they know~~ I'm here
I can wear a mask of pluck and power
But it never says what I intend
Words become like scissors in my keeping
And friendships are so difficult to mend
I don't want to shout above the babble
I'm not even sure~ what I would say
Maybe just, "Excuse me, could we maybe
Be a little quieter today~?"
Many are the mu~sings of my shy~~~~~ heart
Though precious few are spoken out aloud
How I wish to wrap them up in confidence and style
And send them out like magic through the crowd
Then everyone would listen and I wouldn't be afraid~
I wouldn't shrink away~~ and disappear~~~
I don't want them to worship me or care that much at all
I only want to know~ they know~ I'm here
I only want to know~ they know~~ I'm here
Part of me has things she wants and wishes
Part of me is worried she is wrong
Part of me is busy masquerading
As a girl whose pieces get along
I don't mean to come across as distant
I don't think it adds to my~ mystique
I just find it difficult conversing
And think an awful lot be~fore I speak
Many are the mu~sings of my shy~~~~~ heart
Though precious few are spoken out aloud
How I wish to wrap them up in confidence and style
And send them out like magic through the crowd
Then everyone would listen and I wouldn't be afraid
I wouldn't shrink away~~ and disappear~~~
I don't want them to worship me or care that much at all
I only want to know~ they know~~ I'm here
I only want to know~ they know~ I'm here