How could I have done this?
Please sister, forgive me!
I'm sorry!
Fate has been cru-u-u-el a-and order unkind
How can I have sent you away?
Just rest easy now, the punishment's mine
The darkness and silence pre-evade
Bu-ut into the sti-illness I'll bring you a song
And I will your company ke-ep
Through your tire-ed eyes, your sweet lullabies
Will carry me softly-y to-o sleep
Once did a pony who-o shone like the sun
Look out on her ki-ingdom and sigh
She smi-led and said, "Surely, there is nopony
So lovely and so-o well beloved as I"
So great was he-er reign and so brilliant her glo-ory-y
So great was her reign and so brilliant her glo-ory-y
That long wa-as the shado-ow she cast
Which fell dark upon the young siste-er you loved
And grew only darke-er as days and nights passed
Lullay moon princess, goodnight siste-er mine
Rest now in moonlight's embrace
I'll bear thy lullaby, winds o-of the earth
Through cloud and through sky and through space
Carry the peace and the coolness of night
Carry the peace a-and the coolness of night
I-I'll carry thy sorro-ow in ki-i-i-ind
I-I'll carry thy sorro-ow in kind
Luna, yo-u're loved so much mo-ore than you know
Forgive me for being so blind
Soon did that pony take notice that others
Did not give her sister her due
And neither had you loved me as I deserved
You watched as my rage and unhappiness grew
But such is the wa-ay of the limelight, it swe-etly-y
But such is the way of the limelight, it sweetly
Took hold o-of the mi-i-ind o-of its host
Took hold of the mind o-of its host
And both foolish ponies did nothi-ing to stop
The destruction of one who had needed her most
Lullay sun princess, goodnight siste-er mine
Rest now in moonlight's embrace
Bear up my-y lullaby, winds o-of the earth
Through cloud and through sky and through space
Through cloud, and through sky, a-and through space
Carry the peace a-and the coolness of night
Carry the peace and the coolness of night
And carry my sorro-ow in kind
And carry my sorro-ow in ki-i-i-ind
Tia, you loved me much more than I knew
May trouble-es be fa-ar from your mi-i-ind
And forgive me for being so blind
And forgive me fo-or being so blind
Oh, dear Tia!
I know not what I did
Please! Forgive me!
The years now be-e-fo-ore us
The years no-ow be-efo-ore us
Empty and unknown
Empty-y a-and unknown
I ne-eve-er ima-agined
I ne-eve-er i-ima-agined
We'd face them a-all a-alone
We'd face them all a-alone
May the-ese tho-usand wi-inters
May these tho-usand wi-inters
Swiftly-y pass, I pr-ay
Swiftly pass, I pray
I love you, I miss you
A-all these miles away
All these miles a-away
May all your dreams be sweet tonight
Safe upon your be-ed of moonlight
And know not of he-a-artache, pain, o-or care
And know not of heartache, pain, o-or care
And whe-en I dream, I'll fly-y away and meet you there
And when I-I dream I'll fly away and meet you there
Sleep, sleep, sle-ep...