The weatherman said it would be a hot one
He never said he wasn't talking about the sun~
And he never said she'd be so cold woh oh~
Travelling, impressing all the townsfolk
She'll take their praise but she thinks they are a joke
Been like this since she was three years old ~ ~
Watch out for her~ lies
She is shifty and deceitful
Looking down on the common people~
Watch out for her tricks
They can come in any size
It's clear to see she's plain not nice
You've got it wrong if you think I am the b*tch
I entertain you and what am I asking~
Just a little credit where is due~~~
You call me boastful and you just might be right~
But you know that underneath the stage lights
It's called showmanship and it's nothing new~~~
Watch out for her~ lies
She is shifty and deceitful
Looking down on the common people~
Watch out for her tricks
They can come in any size
It's clear to see she's plain not nice
Watch out for her~ lies
Watch out for her tricks
She is shifty and deceitful
Looking down on the common people~
Watch out for her tricks
They can come in any size
It's clear to see she's plain not nice