Sometimes I wish I could stand on a clo-oud
Or maybe just move it aro-ound
Wish I could take all the raindrops awa-ay
And keep them to myself for a day
The princess gave me a heart of gold
But I told her that I wanted wings
Guess what I just got a new pair of wings
Guess M.A. Larson made me a king
I mean a princess or whatever you call it
The po-oint is there's a lot in my wallet
And I can fly
But I'm not very good at it... (he can fly)
Still I can fly
Still I'm not very good at it... (he's not very good at flying)
I'll break down your house
I'll break down your streets
I'll break down the trees and the birds and the bees
I'll fly through the castle with my brand new wings
I'm less than a penny 'cause I'm free
The princess gave me a pair of wings
What was she thinking to give me-e these?
So, now I guess I can stand on a cloud