When the last ceremony starts
With the last crowd to attend
And the last guest come out
For the fandom we defend
(They) come from far away land
Though we have done this before
We will be all the Bronies
At the last Bronycon
When the first panel opens
To start the week-end one last time
And you look at the schedule
And realize how time is flying
And it seems the world is ending
Leaving just your friends to mourn
We join together in friendship
Of the last Bronycon
I'm alive
I'm ali~~ve
When the last ice cold water
Sends us off on the last morning
And the days in Bal timare pass
With out a last desperate warning
Then look to the memories
And where all friend ships were born
Remember how~ it started
Enjoy the last Bronycon
I'm alive
I'm ali~~ve