Now a rainbow's tale isn't quite as nice
As the story we knew of sugar and spice
But a rainbow's easy once you get to know it
With the help of the magic of a pegasus device
Let's delve deeper into rainbow philosophy
Far beyond that of Cloudsdale's mythology
It's easy to misjudge that floating city
With its alluring decor and social psychology
But with all great things comes a great responsibility
That of Cloudsdale's being weather stability
How, you ask, are they up to the task
To which the answer is in a simple facility
In the Rainbow Factory
Where your fears and horrors come true
Where not a single soul gets through
In the Rainbow Factory
Where your fears and horrors come true
Where not a single soul gets through
In the Rainbow Factory
Where your fears and horrors come true