Aah oh ah ee aw ee aw~ aa ooo~ oh
Aah oh ah ee aw ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Aah oh ah ee aw ee ooiyah~~
Ohaah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~~
Eep eep eep eep eep
Eep eep eep ahh oh~~~~
Eepeep ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Eep eep eep eep eep
Eep eep ahh oh~~~
C'MON!
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ee ooiyah~~
Ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ee ooiyah~~
Ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oh aah oh ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~~
Ee oh aah oh ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oo oh aah oh ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~~
Oh oh aah oh ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~~
Ooh oh aah oh ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Ooh oh aah oh ee yea~ ah~
Oh ee yea~ ah~
C'MON!
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ee ooiyah~~
Ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ee ooiyah~~
Ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~
Oh aah ee yea~ ah~ eaeah~~~ ohh~~~
Oh aah ee yea ah ah a a ee ee ooiyah~~ ooiyah~~