I'm back
And it feels good too
Oh this is gonna be so much fun my friends
Just stick around for a while
Trust me
You're gonna love it
Ooh
Hmm-hmm heh-hehOh ho~
Hmm-hmmm Mmm hmmmm
Hm-hmmm Huh hoo
Locked away for years 'cause I caused some tears
Someone took a joke wrong so I became feared
Thousand years of stone, sitting on my own
Stuck without a chance to prove myself along
Thousand years have passed, my shell starts to crack
I've had enough time to plan out my attack
Y'all got numbered days, Kaos will be raised
Time for me to - because now
I'm back and on the prowl, dont give me any lip
I'll put you in your place won't deal with such -
So get down on your knees, be sure to open wide
I'm making you my-
I'm back baby, I am alive
I am ali~~~~ve
Frantic for the factor I re place
Such dry weather needs a change of pace
Try to contest me, then it's time you're gone
Learn to respect me, 'cause I'm number one
Think you'll outsmart me, you'll soon find you're wrong
It's a crime that I'm free so come on follow on
I'm back and on the prowl, don't give me any lip
I'll put you in your place, won't deal with your -
So get down on your knees, be sure to open wide
I'm making you my-
Come back baby, I am alive
Insanity is pleasing to the eyes
Relish in destruction and demi~~se
Give you a wink then I'll leave you to cry
Use and abuse till your streams have run dry
Don't dare to fight it, you know you can't fly
Don't lie to yourself 'cause I'm like no one else
I'm back and on the prowl, don't give me any lip
I'll put you in your place, won't deal with such -
So get down on your knees, be sure to open wide
I'm making you -
I'm starting up your tide
I'm back and on the scene, so cower if you will
Just know when I got you I'll give such a thrill
Chaos is the thing you yearn for deep inside
Tonight you'll be -, I'm back baby I am alive
Mmm humm Hm hmm
Hm hmmmm Hm huh
Hm hmmm huh hooh
Huu-hooh hu-oooh