The kids in my town are getting weird
Ever since the new head librarian appeared
They're getting extra lessons when school ends
About the magic that comes from being friends
Oh, oh
Oh~, oh
The new librarian is a horse
And she's checking you out, of course
She's giving lessons to-o the kids
They're gonna learn how to be much better friends
The kids in my town are getting strange
But to be honest it's a welcome change
They're smiling more, they're less deadpan
Ever since the new head librarian began
Oh, oh
The new librarian is a horse
And she's checking you out, of course
She's giving lessons to-o the kids
They're gonna learn how to be much better friends
Oh, oh
The new librarian is a horse
And she's checking you out, of course
She's giving lessons to-o the kids
They're gonna learn how to be much better friends