Hey!
Rarity, oh can't you see
Why I need you?
I'm waiting in the dark for a spark
Just to see you
If light is what you want
Then I'll brighten your world
In a blaze
Rarity, oh count the hours
'Cause a storm is coming
Maybe we could hold it off
'stead of only running
We could make the world stand still
For hours or days
Darkness
You've been holding out for something you know
It's not the best
But I promise it's the brightest
Darkness
Just you wait; you'll have
No place to go
And we'll show you, we'll show you we'll glow~~
Maybe if that's what you want
We can start a fire
And ignite the dark
And maybe if we just try
We can find it all
In between the lines
Hey!
Rarity, oh can't we wait
Just a moment longer
How can I just say goodbye
And not start to wonder
What my life would come to be
Without your~ voice?
Rarity, imagine how
We could live forever
Drifting through this crazy world
Holding on together
We could make the perfect match
But it's your~ choice
Darkness
You've been holding out for something you know
It's not the best
But I promise it's the brightest
Darkness
Just you wait; you'll have no place to go
And we'll show you, we'll show you we'll glow~~
Maybe if that's what you~ want
We can start a fire
And ignite the dark
And maybe if we just try
We can find it all
In between the lines
Hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, ... hey