You may call it a crash
I call it a fly in
Here to perform on this deserted island
Jealous, cause I leave a pony smilin'?
You need to chill
Cause you knowin' who I am
Out here no cell phone service
With a blank stare
It don't serve its purpose
Not worthless
Look under the surface
Clear blue sea
And these ponies are shirtless
Spectacular
You don't speak tree
The vernacular
You know it beats me
Never mastered words, it isn't easy
Leave a wreck afterwards
So Tavi please please
I need a beat
We need an atlas,
I need a drink
But we're rather mapless
At an impasse
Pass me the track list
Trackless in fact
Though I lack this, I blast this
Not known to be patient
So far from home, from our Equestrian nation
Miss the standing ovation
Miss the lights and the stage
What a grand innovation
Pain is bass
Heavy, I drop it
Smile in place
Don't know you got it
Don't always get what you're hopin' for
More worry than a bat with a Jokermort
But we're still breathing
And the sunset is setting so sweetly this evening
Know you're thinking of leaving
But though it seems hopeless
I hope you believe me
It's an issue not insurmountable
Never was a test
No one holds you accountable
Can't advance in life without stressin'
But worry defeats
Let me teach you a lesson
Life is full of problems
Life is full of hurtin
But it's hardest to solve when your mind isn't certain
That you're on the right path, right track- what's that?
Don't know where we are, but I know where we're at
Gallopagos Islands
I'm here with you
Don't pick sides when it's only we two
Don't brood
What did I do?
You're my best friend
There's no need to argue!
To have a good time
I don't need your permission,
But time'll crawl by when's work's inefficient
Know that you're raring to go and get fishin'
But, Tavi, Tavi
Stop and just listen!
We'll carry on, somebody gets you,
So sing your song
The melody will let you
Get your worries gone
Celest'll bless you
New day will dawn
We'll focus on our rescue
1 2 3, Tavi dance with me
Though we're lost at sea
Depressed is just no way to be
Come on let's take things slow
Help is on its way I know
So we've nowhere to go
Call it a crash or
Call it a fly in
Here to perform on this deserted island
Jealous, cause I leave a pony smilin'?
You need to chill
Cause you know just who I am
Out here no cell phone service
With a blank stare
It don't serve its purpose
Not worthless look under the surface
Clear blue sea
And these ponies are shirtless