I don't know where to go
I can't find my way
The world turns slow
There is no end to my-y day
My vision is black
I am running blind
There is no turning back
On the pa-ath I can't find
On the pa-ath I can't find-
My bad~!
I'm sick of people thinking
I have no mind
Just 'cause my eyes are out of focus
Trust me I'm fine
Don't underestimate
Anypony can be great
My advice is to change your opinion
Before it's too late
To all of you defending me
I appreciate your kind words
But don't be absurd
I've got experience with the herd
If you wanna hold on my hooves,
It'll be gold for the fools
Who want to box me in
Keep me out of the tubes
I don't know where to go
I can't find my way
The world turns slow
There is no end to my-y day
My vision is black
I am running blind
There is no turning back
On the pa-ath I can't find