It's time to show 'em what you've got
It's time to go and get things done
But you don't have to do it on your own
'Cause you've got friends right here to make it fun
We got this
You got this
We got this together
Sometimes the pressure gets you down
And the clouds are dark and grey
Just kick them off and let the sun shine through
And scary as it seems
More help is on the way
'Cause friends have friends that want to help out too
We got this
You got this
We got this together
It's the festival of friendship
And we can get it done
A festival that they won't forget
A party to be proud of
A day of games and fun
Just you wait and see~
A magic day in perfect harmony
You got this
*tweet* ~ ~
We got this together!
With friends and family you are never alone
If you need help we've got your~ back
You can be honest let your problems be known
'Cause you got us
To pick up the slack
We got this
Eyup!
We got this together
Pay attention to the details
Every gem even spaced
Make the colors perfect
Taking one or two to taste
Inside and out~
Beautiful throughout~
Generosity is what we're all about~
We got this
You got this
We got this together
Today needs to be perfect
It all comes down to me
I don't know if I'm ready
For all the things they need me to be
I am the princess of friendship
But that is more than just a crown~
It's a promise to bring ponies together
And never let any pony down
We've got an awful lot to bake
Each pony needs a piece of cake
Oh, wait! There's something better
We can do
We're gonna need some more supplies
To make a really big surprise
She'll be so shocked
She's sure to love it too
You got this
We got this together
It's the festival of friendship
Together we are one
A day we will never forget
And now everything is ready
So when the day is done
The weather
The banquet
The style~
And music
All will be in perfect harmony!