A wow of silence?
That's err, that's why they asked me to leave
I hope it's not a sore subject but,
You mind explaining why you all went quiet in the first place?
It's a long story
*sigh*
You'd rather not talk about it?
No, I'd rather sing
La, la-la-la, la la
La-la-la, la-la-la
The Kirin used to speak and sing
We weren't always quiet
We told stories and funny jokes
My stand-up was a riot
But then one day a fight broke out
And hurtful words were said
Flaring tempers were inflamed
Destruction quickly spread
And flaming bred from head to head
Even burnt our bread
Sorry, I forgot how much I love rhyming
Where was I? Oh, right!
My happy village lay in ruins
Relationships got worse
Spoiler alert: we quickly learned
That words could be a curse
"No more talking," yelled our leader
The last thing said aloud
Into the Stream of Silence
We stepped as a crowd
The water cooled emotions
And peace was soon restored
But with no way to speak my thoughts
I got super bored
Seriously, there's only so long that
Sudoku can keep you entertained!
'Cause rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you let it rain
And shiny apples sometimes come with worms
No, you can't give up yo-ur laughter
'Cause you're scared of a little pain
It's a lesson that the-e Kirin never learned
I was stuck in silent pri-ison
With the voices in my-y head
'Til I tripped over my-y salvation
In a helpful flowerbed
I found a cure to cle-ar my pipes
And I became quite chatty
With years and years of sto-ored-up words
I drove my village batty
They didn't like my jokes 'n' songs
And daily dose of news
The plays I wrote, the speeches spoke
Variety revues
Or the story about the Kirin
Who hid below an opera stage
And fell in love with this opera singer
And he wore a freaky half-mask thing
And he played the organ a lot
And got all broody
Because the singer was in love with another dude
So he took her away on this underground gondola
I mean, who doesn't love musical theater?!
The village leader made it clear
I had to make my choice
I could stay and live with them
Or I could keep my voice
So I came here, but left the couch alo-one
They're hard to move
With just the view for company
Until ya heard me gro-ove
Take it away, boys!
...
'Cause rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you let it rain
Candles just won't glow until they're burned
No, you can't give up yo-ur laughter
'Cause you're scared of a little pain
It's a lesson that my-y village never learned
No matter how hard I schooled them
Fear of hu-urt is still what ruled them
Sometimes you gotta le-et it rain
Yeah, sometimes you've gotta let it ra-in
'Cause rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you let it rain
And candles just won't glow until they're burned
No, you can't give up yo-ur laughter
'Cause you're scared of a little pain
It's a lesson that my-y village never learned
Oh, yes, 'cause rainbows won't light up the sky
Unless you letit
Rain