Til death do us 'part~
But we're already past that phase
This is a brand new~ start~
And I think I deserve some praise
For the way that I am~~~~
Despite having overdosed
And ending up comatose
I don't give a damn~~~~
I've let my emotions go
Fuck being a sober hoe
This is the mantra
This is my life~
You're playing with now
Til the end of the night~
Surrounded by fire~
The passion ignites~
A hit of that heaven and hell, a helluva high~
I'm addict~ed
To the mad~ness
This hotel is
My Atlan~tis
We're forever gonna have a fucking reason to sin
Let me leave my soul to burn and I'll be breathing it in
I'm addict~ed
To the feel~ing
Getting higher
Than the cei~ling
And we're never gonna want this fucking feeling to end
Just concede and give in to your inner demons again
Yeah you fell in love~
But you fell deeper in this pit~
While death rains from above~
So count your blessings 'cause this is it
You’re not letting it go~~~~
So what if I misbehave
It's what everybody craves
You already know~~~~
So come if you're feeling brave
And fancy yourself a mate
You want it, I got it
See what you like~?
We could have it all
By the end of the night~
Your money and power
My sinful delight~
A hit of that heaven and hell, a helluva high~
I'm addict~ed
To the mad~ness
This hotel is
My Atlan~tis
We're forever gonna have a fucking reason to sin
Let me leave my soul to burn and I'll be breathing it in
I'm addict~ed
To the feel~ing
Getting high~er
Than the ceil~ing
And we're never gonna want this fucking feeling to end
Just concede and give in to your inner demons again
I'm addict~ed
To the feel~ing
Getting high~er
Than the ceil~ing
And we're never gonna want this fucking feeling to end
Just concede and give in to your inner demons again