Be strong
The song of life is long
Performance isn't wrong
But when you play out of key
The discordance serves to only
Break
So have another take
See now what's all at stake~
Bringing yourself into tune
Helps to orchestrate
Relate
Every step you take~
To this aim
Although
We have different names
We're the same
We
All have our parts to play
If we just meet halfway
You'll see dissonance fall away
We
Are perfectly wrote~
So now take up this oath~
To lift up every single note~~~~
Like
A grand symphony~
Perfect polyphony~
Is in diversity~~~~
Notes
Of different colors - We
Make up all we see~
And hear together we are one
For now
Forever and a day
Our crowning harmony
Will spill into the air
Timpanys hit
Trumpets blare
The stage
Is set for you to unleash
Who you are
Uniquely sounding rhythmic bars~~
Never far
Are those
Who raise their voices~ high~
From every walk of life~
Can be heard in the choir~~~~
We
Are perfectly wrote~~
So now take up this oath~
To lift up every single note~~~~~~
Like
A grand symphony~
Perfect polyphony~
Is in diversity~~~
Oh Oh~ oh oh
We are perfectly wrote~~~
We are
Yes we are~~~~~
We a- a- are~
We're perfectly wrote~~~~
Oh oooh~
Oh oh oh oooh
Oh oh oh oh oh
Oh oh oh oh ooh oh
C'mon c'mon
Lift up your note~~~~
High~
High in the sky~
Lift up your note~~~~~~~~~~~~
We are
We are~~~~~~~~
We are~~~
Perfectly wrote~~~~
We are
We are~~~~~~~
We are perfectly wrote
So lift up your note
Come on