Hello weary traveler
You strike me, an admirer, of ancient lore
With a penchant I see
For old history
As you’ve never heard it before
It’s a familiar tale
Of a once mighty king
But the story you know
Goes much deeper, so
Sit back as I tell you and sing
There once was a colt with a coat dark as coal
Who had eyes of a bright burning red
Courageous and strong, it was not very long
‘til the crown was bestowed on his head
For the king in the North had to be a great force
To survive all the harsh elements
But the power he held from the keep where he dwelled
Would lead to his people’s lament~
But there was a time
When his rule was kind
When the kingdom was wealthy and thrived
Someone caught his eye
And he soon realized
That he wanted a wife by his side
He thought all was right
They saw eye to eye
A princess from a Southern ally
His heart had grown fond
As they fostered a bond
That the world could not ever defy
Grand Regent
Unequaled
Transcendent
Eternal
Both hearts longing for simple love to soar
But nothing’s simple for kingdoms and kings
What stands certainly?
For eternity?
Fear what a veiled future brings
One thing’s for sure
As the ages move on
The harshest of debts
Is to live with regret
So chase what you love
Or you’ll find it’s departed and gone…