The North is beautiful, the land at rest so peacefully
Why did we wait so long to travel up to~ see?
Oh yes, it’s overdue, but now we’re making history
To draw much closer ties
And join our people as they’re meant to (be)
My warmest welcome to you dears
I hope safe travels brought you here
Come feast your eyes, there’s much to show
Of our oasis in the snow
(Shining) crystal peaks, down to the frozen ground below
We’ve worked the arctic earth and reaped the bounty that we’ve sown
My lord, you’re much too kind…
You needn’t go through such fanfare
You’ve clearly marked your reign with acumen and care
No wait, we’ve just arrived
I’m sure we still have much to see
Lead on, oh gracious king
Acquaint us with your kingdom’s majes(ty)
Why not, it’s time to celebrate
Our nations joined to commemorate
A future gilt in brightest gold
Forged here amongst the winter cold
(Gleaming) in the sun our colors shine in every hue
We’ve fought off every foe and seen our troubles through
Standing side-by-side, two nations fortunate and free
A righteous pony empire spanning sea to sea!
Oh, ah ah
Gleaming in the sun our colors shine in every hue
We’ve fought off every foe and seen our troublesthrough
Standing side-by-side, two nations fortunate and free
A righteous pony empire spanning sea to sea!
Oh, ah ah!