Finally we end a long and busy day
Let the moon rise, slumber all~ the world away
Watch the colors dance from the vast and great unknown
Now for once it feels~ like I~ am not alone
Through all the pain and strife
On these crossroads of life
We’ve finally met to~ make the journey side by~ side
After all this time, the~ long and distant years
Fate has finally brought~ us both~ together here
No more royal talks, or~ visiting through charms
Soon I’ll always hold~ you tight~ly in my arms
Through all the pain and strife
On these crossroads of life
We’ve finally met to make the journey side by side
As all the world is right
Our future’s shining bright
The heavens waltz with the auroras in the night
So much to do, a wedding to~ muse!
I’ll talk to you soon, once I break the news
Go, and take your time, my~ lovely future bride
Soon we’ll make that journey walking side by side