Luna, come sit here
It’s become quite clear
You’ve let your heart grow far too fond
How can you say this?
Don’t we deserve bliss?
Is it a crime~ to share a bond?
You know that is not the way
Can we never love, never just disobey?
Duty takes priority
But he is a king, the same royalty
Bound by his mortality
That doesn’t matter, at least not to me
But it will
Even still
You must know that
Heavy is the crown we wear
It is the price, the burden we bear
Why must it be, the burden I bear?
Stop this or else it will break your heart~~
How can I live with a broken heart~~~?
Well hello my dear, I thought you had gone~~~
Yes I did but now we~ need to~ talk~~
I have been thinking
My heart’s been sinking
And I don’t think we can go on
What are you saying?
You must be playing…
What could have changed, what did I do wrong?
Please, you do not share the blame
Tell me that you’re wrong, that we are still the same
It’s already killing me
Or was it the “queen”, your dear sister’s decree?
I’ll watch you grow old and gray
I don’t have to die, there still might be a way
But you will
Even still
You must know that
Heavy is the crown we wear
Missing the short-lived life that we share
Why just discard the life we could share?
Left to grieve for all eternity~~~
Must we flee~ before e~ternity~~?
Heavy is the crown we wear
That is the cost, the burden I bear
At any cost, I’ll take it and bear
Sombra, please, you have to~ let me go~~~~
Luna, I~ will never~ let you go~~~