Oh, my king, what miracle is this?
Here I thought we’d share our final kiss
Now~ to see~ you draped in onyx wings
You cannot know~ the joy it brings
How could I just let you slip away?
When, no matter what, I’d find a way
Nothing known could disagree, and
Keep you away from me
Why spend these ages trapped in loneliness?
Why should it be?
When we could rule as regents of~ the dark~ness
Think of how the world~ could really be
Why should light command the ra~ven sea?
Why should shadows hide away~, when they give light its stay
When it’s the sun that should bow down to us!
What do you mean?
And fall~ before the regents of~ the dark
Sombra, please answer me
Every blessing has its cost
Though I bear its every~ weight
I will face this “queen’s” accost
We’ll be forced to separate
And face her wishes handed down as~ fate
It can be just you and me
Once we’re finally left alone
We’ll command eternity!
We can shape it as our own
As we both share the seat of darkness’ throne
Do you understand the words you say?
Must this spell have lead your mind astray?
Wait there safe beloved king, I’ll find~ the cure~ and bring
Then once I have you back we can pro~fess
Soon you will see
Eternal love~ as regents of the dark~ness!
Eternal love as regents of the dar~kness!