Grand Regent
Unequaled
Transcendent
Eternal
Oh, what a sight to see
That you would offer up your armies and
Renounce your sovereignty
At least hold on to your dignity
And just surrender yourself
And your power willingly
We revoke your infernal doctrine
Renounce the mantle you have laid
Your laws, your rule, will be forgotten
As your light is left to fade!
Heaven's fury raining down
Kneel before the aurora’s crown
Sun and shadow both will bow
Living as my queen and I allow
How~ could you fall~ to this
That you would desecrate your kingdom
Bring them into this abyss
Reverse this curse that afflicts them all
Or in this battle you will face
I promise, you will fall!
Your emotions have left you blinded
Would you just throw this peace away?
Tonight, it ends, so loose their bindings
Don’t prolong this sad display!
Heaven's fury~ raining~ down
Cast aside this corrupted crown
You forsake your~ royal~ vows
For a crime I simply can’t allow!
Know that in the end, you can’t make us relent
We won’t let you take away our love again!
For above all else, it’s the only covenant
I would ever keep and follow to my grave~~
Once I simply thought, that we could rise above
All the trials that we~ might face together
But this dark descent, con~sumed the one I love
Return to me, before this brings the end
Heaven's fury~ raining~ down
We can’t ignore our hea~vy~ crowns
We can make it work somehow
If your pride would~ on~ly~ just allow
You sacrifice your fate, abandon our future
You choose to desecrate, and let our love fade away~~~
But you won’t win this day
Despite your treachery~~
No matter what you say
The empire belongs to me~~~~~~
Come to the darkness, all who have offered up
Their souls to me
Into the starless tundra
You’ll follow your true and rightful king
Come to the darkness, all who have offered up
Of their souls to me
Into the starless tundra, you’ll follow
Your true and rightful king
Come to the darkness, all who have offered up
Of their souls to me
Into the starless tundra
You’ll follow your true and rightful—