This is Garnet
Back together
And I'm never going down at the hands of the likes of you
Because I'm so much better
And ev'ry part of me is saying go get 'er
The two of us ain't gonna follow your rules
Come at me without any of your fancy tools
Let's go, just me and you
Let's go, just one on two
Go ahead and try and hit me if you're able
Can't you see that my relationship is stable
I can see you hate the way we intermingle
But I think you're just mad cause you're single
And you're not gonna stop what we've made together
We are gonna stay like this forever
If you break~ us apart we'll just come back newer
And we'll always be twice the gem that you are
I am made~ oh-oh-oh-oh-of
Lo-oh-oh-oh-ove
Oh-oh-oh-oh-ove
Hm hm hm hm hm
This is who we are
This is who I am
And if you think you can stop me
Then you need to think again
'Cause I am a feeling
And I will never end
And I won't let you hurt my planet
And I won't let you hurt my friends
Go ahead and try and hit me if you're able
Can't you see that my relationship is stable
I know you think I'm not something you're afraid of
'Cause you think that you've seen what I'm made of
Well I am even more than the two of them
Ev'rything they care about is what I am
I am their fury, I am their patience
I am a conversation
I~ am made oh-oh-oh-oh-of
Lo-oh-oh-oh-ove
Oh-oh-oh-oh-ove
And it's stronger than you
Lo-oh-oh-oh-ove
Oh-oh-oh-oh-ove
And it's stronger than you
Lo-oh-oh-oh-ove
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh