When I was just sixteen
I had a car that was lean and mean~
Put Dashie in my window
Was the coolest thing I'd seen
But these kids from down the road~
They were rather cold~
I found my Dashie lay in pieces
Broken and alone
But I had my group of friends~
Who would defend me to the end~~
And we picked up every piece and tried
To make her whole again
'Cause toge~ther we can do it
Overcome our fears and doubts
Though everypony loves~ to shun us
Together we stand proud
Hoof in hoof we all will weather
The storm~ and the~ hate
'Cause as long as we're together
We're better off this way
We've got brony pride~ forever
Well it wasn't long thereafter
I went to my first con
Had a lot of new~ adventures
And I had a lot of fun
I spent a weekend in~ a world
Much different from my own
And I learned a million things about
The ponies from the show
But when I had to say~ goodbye~
The tears fell from my eyes~
But I forced a smile and turned away
And said I think I'll be alright
'Cause toge~ther we can do it
Overcome our fears and doubts
Though everypony loves~ to shun us
Together we stand~ proud
Hoof in hoof we all will weather
The storm~ and the~ hate
'Cause as long as we're together
We're better off this way
We've got brony pride~ forever
These years have sure flown by
Still got Dashie by my side~~
I still have my pride~
And I'm still a bro~ny
And many years~ from now
Gonna sit my children down~~
And tell them all about~
These amazing~~ times
I joined the herd and learned that I
Will ne~ver be alone~~
I'm surrounded by~ my friends who always
Help me feel at home
'Cause together we can do it
Overcome our fears and doubts
Though everypony loves~ to shun us
Together we stand proud
Hoof in hoof we all will weather
The storm~ and the hate
'Cause as long as we're together
We're better off this way
Yes, together we can do it
Overcome our fears and doubts
Though everypony loves~ to shun us
Together we stand proud
Hoof in hoof we all will weather
The storm~ and the hate
'Cause as long as we're together
We're better off this way
We've got brony pride~ forever