So this~ is my ascent
A corona~tion on~ly I'll at~tend
The night~ of which I dreamed~
With no one to~ admire it but me~
In the dark~ness I've embraced
I still see your twisted~ face
"To~ the moon" - my sister's iro~ny~
If this~ is how it ends
Nightmare in~side me my only~ friend
How different will it be~
From reigning o~ver quietude and~ sleep~
Safe in dreams~ so bright and~ clear
My subjects can~ ignore their~ fears
But also all~ of my night's majesty~
My story does not~ end in this fall
(My story never ends)
Despite~ this exo~dus
I'll~ return~ to rule you~ all
So spend this night in sweet pursuit
And hope the queen~ of nightmares smiles~
Upon~ your tribute
So dream~ of me tonight
Show me your~ devotion in your fright
Know a world~ forever without sun
Drowning in this terror I've become
My sister hides~ a tyrant's lies
In brightest day~ and sunlit skies
But in the world~ I rule, there is no light
My story does not~ end in this fall
(My story never ends)
Despite~ this exo~dus
I'll~ return~ to rule you~ all
So spend this night in sweet pursuit
And hope the queen~ of nightmares smiles~
Upon~ your tri~bute