I'm waking up, the sun shines~ in
I want to learn to fight, to~ win
The day again, a longing heart
For now is when I must depart
An open land awaits to try
Another cause to quench de~sire
I'm ready and I say goodbye
I'm a story, a legend, I'll never be gone
I'll change the world
'Cause all it ever takes is one
You will revere me
The fighter for Celesti~a
I am a Legend
A Legend of Equestria
I'm a warrior
A myth, and I'm finally set
I'm the memory the world will not soon for~get
I will defend you
The ponies of Celestia
I am a Legend
A Legend of Equestria
Ahhhhh~~~
Ohhhhh~~~~~
I'm a story, a legend, I'll never be gone
I'll change the world
'Cause all it ever takes is one
You will revere me
The fighter for Celesti~a
I am a Legend
A Legend of Equestria
I'm a warrior
A myth, and I'm finally set
I'm the memory the world will not soon forget
I will defend you
The ponies of Celestia-a-a-a
A Legend of Equestria
Ahhhhh~~~
Ohhhhh~~~~~