As the summe-er ends
The leaves will cha-ange from green to re-ed
And life begins to shy away
Leaving deca-ay in its stead
Will you stay by me
Admire all that's there to see?
And when the season's turned
Will you sti-ill be there for me?
Running throu- ough the leaves, before the hold of night
Watch the fi-irey autumn skyline burning bright
Singing A-ah, a-ah
Take me a-away
A -ah, a-ah
Fly me away
'til it's all okay
Gaze into my-y eyes
And hold my spi-irit in your gra-asp
Give me a-all the strength I need, and love I know wi-ill last
Help me with my pain
I'll do the same for you if you-u please
We'll float on toge-ether
Through life's never ending seas
As we harvest all the fru-uits of all our seeds
Hear the flowing wind, as it whistles through the trees
Singing A-ah, a-ah
Take me a-away
A -ah, a-ah
Fly me away
'til it's all okay
'til it's all o-okay
A -ah a-ah, o-oh
A -ah, a-ah, o-o-o-oh
A -ah, a-ah
A -a-ah, a-a-ah
As the nights get cold
I still ho-old you close to me-e
Silent in the shadows of what we kno-ow we co-ould be
Sum mer's now behind us
Dead is all that grew
What now la-ays ahead?
I wish that I still knew
No thing's certain
In the fire of the fall
Now you're gone
I cry to find point in i-it all
Singing, A-ah, a-ah
Take me a-away
A -ah, a-ah
Fly me away
'till it's all okay