You've~ got no alibi~
'Cause ev~erything~ you say~ is a lie
You're gun~ning~ for half past~ twelve~
It's dee~per into your mind~~ we delve
The ol~der sister of~ one makes two~
But~ you say she's coming after you
A lit~tle lie~ lets the story un~fold~
That lit~tle lie~ keeps the stor~y told~~
A tall~ tale of ambition and power~
Lun~a's ruse is the one~ of the hour
Your sis~ter's mind~ has been bought and~ sold~
Now ev~erypony thinks you're made~ of gold~
But what~ they don't know surely can't do harm~
It's bet~ter sounding Nightmare Moon's alarm
A lit~tle lie~ sends her to the moon~~~
A little lie~ gets disco~vered soon~
A little story and you've~ got~ all the power
Gone a thousand years~~ with the tale of the hour
You're tel~ling vicious lies
Your power knows no com~promise
To be the savior in~ their eyes
Nightmare Night descends upon the world~
Your web~ of lies~ and deceit unfurl
With ev~erypony looking to the sky~
Ne~ver knowing that it's all a lie
Send~ the elements to beat her down~
Ne~vermind you're nowhere to be found
Ano~ther lie~ only seals their~ fate~
For~ all time it's Nightmare Moon~ they hate~
A little story and you've~ got~ all the power
Gone a thousand years~~
with the tale of the hour~~~~~~~~
You're tel~ling vicious lies
Your power knows no com~promise
To be the savior in~ their eyes
You're tel~ling vicious lies
Your power knows no com~promise
You're tel~ling vicious lies~~
To be the savior in~ their eyes