I used to bite my tongue and hold my breath
Scared to rock the boat and make a mess
So I sat quietly
Agreed politely
I guess that I forgot I had a choice
I let you push me past the breaking point
I stood for no~thing,
So I fell for everything
You held me down
But I got up
Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice~
You hear that sound~
Like thunder gonna shake the ground
You held me down
But I got up
Get ready cause I've had enough
I see it all~
I see it now~
I got the eye of the tiger
A fighter
Dancing through the fire~
Cause I am
A champion
And you're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Louder
Louder than a lion
Cause I am
A champion
And you're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~~~~~~~~
Oh~ oh oh oh oh oh~~
You're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Now I'm floating like a butterfly
Stinging like a bee I earned my stripes
I went from ze~ro
To my own he~ro
You held me down
But I got up
Already brushing off the dust
You hear my voice~
You hear that sound~
Like thunder gonna shake the ground
You held me down
But I got up
Get ready 'cause I've had enough
I see it all~
I see it now~
I got the eye of the tiger
A fighter
Dancing through the fire~
Cause I am
A champion
And you're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Louder
Louder than a lion
Cause I am
A champion
And you're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Oh~ oh oh oh oh oh~~
You're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
You'll hear me roar~~
You're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Roar~
I got the eye of the tiger, a fighter
Dancing through the fire-~
A champion
And you're gonna hear~ me~
Roar~~
Louder
Louder than a lion
Cause I am
A champion
And you're gonna
Hear~ me~ roar~
Oh~
You're gonna hear me~
Roar~~
You'll hear me roar
You're gonna
Hear~ me~ roar~