I'm turning nine tonight…
Happy Birthday, Dusk!
Time to explore a-all the secrets
Today I am a kid no more
This destiny ca-alls out to-o me-e
After those years I'll smile and so-oar
I'll follow the path a-and the hoofsteps
Left behind by my great-grand-father
I'll discover
What my grand-father did to gain such a
Huge po-ower
Today I start my jo-ourney
Never to stop until I find
What has happened to my father
Who I am, and my peace of mi-i-ind
Illusions? Dark powers? What a shame.
I expected something... different.
Well, I can work with that.
Of course you do, my-y little one!
Don't be afraid, for you are me
Pleased to meet you!
And this will be so fun...
And we are just two fri-ends to be-e-e-e, ah
But I am the price for those po-wers
Invincible!
That is a fact!
I'll borrow that body of ours
And don't go thinking you can fi-ight back.
"I won't let you, you mean monster!"
I doubt that friend, just look at me
You're the student and I-I'm the master
So sit down, freeze, and let me be, ah
Who do you think I am, you weakling?
You are just a toy in my hoo-o-of
A-all the magic, I am the king
And your demise will be the pro-of
HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA! HA!
I must admit I'm having quite a good time!
Today's forecast: black clouds!
Witness the return of the curse
Celestia's blind and won't notice
The threat that will make all things worse
Hahaha!
Turn off the lights, run away
Hide yourself far, gallop and flee
I will catch you, you are my prey
Powerless to stop, ah, what you see-e
Hear my words and be afraid
There will soon be no place to hi-ide
From the shadows a-and the te-error
They will all fall with darkness on my-y-y si-i-i-ide
My si-ide
I've got a-all the darkness on my si-i-i-i-ide...
?????????????
HAHAHAHAHAHAHA!
AH,HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!