Hey there big sister
I've got a question
Why do they love you
Why do they scorn my beauty
Moon's in the sky now
Not long 'till sunrise
You say to drop it
I don't see why I have to
And I feel~ so alive~
As I take~ to the skies~
And I shout~ my decry~
Look up now~ say goodbye~
You won't see it rise tomorrow
Hey there big sister
Why the long face?~
Are you just jealous
Jealous that they adore me?
No point in fighting
I'm in control now
Celestia darling
This is my new republic
And I feel~ so alive~
As I take~ to the skies~
And I shout~ my decry~
Look up now~ say goodbye~
You won't see it rise tomorrow
The price of freedom
Tonight we end the tyranny of our solar queen
Lower the moon they cry as they fall from the skies
Fear on their treacherous sunloving faces
A small price to pay for they all now bow to me
Come at me if you dare strike down the ones you love
But you won't ever douse the fire that burns inside of me
Torture me all you want lock me up in a cell
You bully me with your friends but never will I lower the moon
And I feel so alive
As I take to the skies
The moon~ takes me in her cold~ embrace
No regrets for what I've done
The night shall last forever