I know you, you're a spe~cial one
Some see~ crazy, where I see love~
You fall so low but shoot~~ so high~
Big dreamers shoot for o~~pen sky
So~ much life~ in those open eyes~
So~ much~ depth~, you look for~ the light~
When your wounds open~, you~~ will cry~
You’ll cry out now~ and you’ll question why~
I can see a rainbow~
In your tears as they fall on down
I can see your soul~ grow~
Through the pain as they hit the ground
I can see a rainbow~
In your tears as the sun comes out
As the sun comes out~~~~
I am here and I see~ your~ pain
Through the storms, through the clouds~, the~ rain
I’m telling you, you can now~~ escape~
You can do~ it, just feel~ ba~by~~
I can see a rainbow~
In your tears as they fall on down
I can see your soul~ grow~
Through the pain as they hit the ground
I can see a rain~bow~
In your tears as the sun comes~ out
As the sun~ comes out~~~~~
Here comes the sun~~
Smiling down~
Here comes the sun~
Smiling down
Smiling down~
I can see a rain~bow~
In your tears~ as they fall on down
I can see your soul grow~~
Through the pain as they hit the ground~~
I can see a rain~bow~~
In your tears as the sun comes~ out
As the sun~ comes~ out~~~~~
I can see a rain~bow~
In your tears~ as they fall on down
I can see your soul~ grow~~
Through the pain as they hit the ground
I can see a rain~bow~
In your tears as the sun comes out
As the sun comes out~~~~~