Many a waltz spun awkwardly out of the rain
She was an anxious refrain
Takin' your time with the imperceptible
Beautiful myths of becoming animal~
Wasp to orchid, orchid to the winter
To regress is to move towards lesser difference
Memories of a sorceress girl
Endless fascination with the secrets of the world
Dreams of the youth: those cute, little movements
Darlin'
Flowing across in the pure past
We change it every day with each little thing we say
This one's a chemist
This one's a friend of mine
This one's an actress
This one's named Pinkie Pie~
This one's for kindness
This one can really fly~
This one's my fa~vorite
Closing upon our mutual love
It's harmony
You are so silly~, ah~
A kind voice, a gentle face
A friend who vanished without a trace
A new body
Without organs just erased
This is the place for us
The place for us
Make this the place we love, or learn to love
To join our separate lives
To seize and multiply
Unless disassembly line extracting from you!
Calm your hair smooth your dress
Tidy up
Smile for us
Clear your throat take a breath
Giddy up!
Smile for us
Memories of a sorceress girl
Endless fascination with the secret of the world
This one's a chemist
This one's a friend of mine
This one's an actress
This one's named Pinkie Pie~
This one's for kindness
This one can really fly~
This one's my fa~vorite
Closing upon our mutual love, it's-