Many a waltz spun awkwardly out of the rain
She was an anxious refrain
Takin' your time with the imperceptible
Beautiful myths of becoming animal
Wasp to orchid, orchid to the winter
To regress is to move towards lesser difference
Memories of a sorceress girl
Endless fascination with the secrets of the world
Dreams of the youth: those cute, little movements
Darlin'
Emit and combine particles-signs that transform
A body into flame
So tell me that this love is all we are~
This simple story, this carousel we're on
A little magic, a different kind of spark
Our glassy essence just float~ing in the dark
It's how you taught us to conjure up~
A little kindness to take inside our hearts
Our will to power
Together, not apart
Trace of the Other
(a tru~ly modern art)
All that you are and all that you'll be
Is harmony~
Darlin' walk with me~, ah~
A kind voice, a gentle face
A friend who vanished without a trace
A blue body
An illusionist on stage~
Twitcha-twitcha, can you stop a moment?
What does Hegel mean by "Absolute Spirit"?
So much love you are
Memories of a sorceress girl
Endless fascination with the secrets of the world
Here we are starin' up
Lookin' up at the same rainbow