The trees ablaze with reds and oranges whisper to the wind
They rustle secrets to each other
The clouds respond with vacant tears as they leave the trees behind
But their responses grow ever colder~
The days grow glum~ it's time to wrap up everypony
The days grow glum~ with warm smiles~ in every window~
Though we all lay all snug at home with our backs turned to the breeze
We hear the words they speak through our windows
The day has come to lend a hoof to help us say goodbye
The days wave thanks~ as they grow ever colder~
The days grow glum~ it's time to wrap up everypony
The days grow numb~ with warm smiles~ in every window~
As we run on through the leaves we leave our tears behind
The trees try to follow if they're able
Our task complete we head back home snuggle up warm in our graves
And we look forward to next November~
The days grow glum~ it's time to wrap up everypony
The days grow numb~ with warm smiles~ in every window~