Don't come back Luna
I don't want you around here
I'm just a filly but I'm taking a stand
Oh~ no, don't come back Luna
You ain't such a big shot
You think it's your land but I tell you it's not
A new stained glass window pane
A prophecy that's been rewritten again
A new story to tell all your foals
They'll turn to legend and then forgotten scrolls
You never know
Just how it feels to be alone
'Til you're cryin' for your thro-o-o-one
Don't come back Luna
I don't want you around here
I'm just a filly but I'm taking a stand
Oh no, don't come back Luna, you ain't such a big shot
You think it's your land but I tell you it's not
I'm not the type for jealousy
But sister I won't let you usurp me
I'm not afraid to use my horn
The sun will rule the moon 'til twilight is born
You won't get free
It's perfectly meant to be
Just like elements of harmony
Don't come back Luna
I don't want you around here
I'm just a filly but I'm taking a stand
Oh no, don't come back Luna
You ain't such a big shot
You think it's your land but I tell you it's not
One little pony left without a home
Two little fillies with a new world to roam~
One thousand years or maybe more it'll be
Six little ponies it'll take to set you free, ah!
Don't come back Luna
I don't want you around here
I'm just a filly but I'm taking a stand
Oh~ no, don't come back Luna
You ain't such a big shot
You think it's your land
You really think it's your land, baby
Don't come back Luna
I don't want you around here
Oh, I'm just a filly, but this is my stand
Oh~ no, don't come back Luna
You ain't such a big shot
You think it's your land but I tell you it's not
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no~
Don't come back Luna