Ya, da da da, da da da, da da da da da da
Da, da da da, da da da, da da da da da da
Here's where my story begins
I've lost my job for a bunch of trouble I fell in
But I can't sit at home and cry
I need some work
So for my Dinky I can provide
"Equestria Speedy Shipping Services
We'll meet all your shipping needs"
Sounds like a job for a pony like me
But little did I know just what shipping could mean
But now I think I finally see
That I've found the job for me
I've got everything I need
For my filly 'neath my wing
And though push may come to shove
I'll help you find the one you love
Though it might cost extra
For shipping and handling
Ya, da da da, da da da, da da da da da da
Da, da da da, da da da, da da da da da da
If there's a pony you love
Give me a call
And I'll come swooping in from above
I'll help you show them that you care
'Cause love that's true
Now that's a thing that's really rare
Equestria Speedy Shipping Services
I think I know just what it means
It's bringing ponies together with a little push
'Cause sometimes love needs a helping hoof
Yeah now I think I finally see
That I've found the job for me
I've got everything I need
For my filly 'neath my wing
And though push may come to shove
I'll help you find the one you love
Though it might cost extra
For shipping and handling
Ah, da da, da da da
Da da da da da da da
Da da da, da da da
Da da da da da da
Da da da da da da da da
Now I think I finally see
Love is waiting here for me
I've got everything I need
For my filly 'neath my wing
And though push may come to shove
I'll help you find the one you love
Though it might cost extra
For shipping and handling
Now I think I finally see
That I've found the job for me
I've got everything I need
For my filly 'neath my wing
And though push may come to shove
I'll help you find the one you love
Though it might cost extra
For shipping and handling