They say there was a jealous mare
With dark blue skin and starry hair
And everypony say~s her na~me was Luna
But then one night of pain and tears
She started one of a thousand years
And from the Moon, she could hear the Halleluujah
Halleluujah
Hallelujah
Halleluuuuujah
Some will tell you otherwise
But there's another one who crie~s the wo~rds
"Sister mi~ne, I thou~ght I knew ya
"Now look at you, you've grown so tall
"But no one kno~ws your face at a~ll
"When you return we'll all sing Halleluujah"
Halleluujah
Hallelujah
Halleluuuuujah
Ponies gathered from around
To celebrate as the sun went do~wn
But no one had foresee~n the gra~nd illusion
A flash of light the thunder rolls
The absence of~ their only ho~pe
The stranger screams in vengeance Halleluujah
Halleluujah
Hallelujah
Hallelu~jah
Halleluuuuujah
Oblivious and out of sight
The real he~ro o~f the night
Was lost inside her ve~ry own conclusion
But then behind the nightmare's call
She heard the voices down the ha~ll
And when she did it felt like Halleluujaah
Halleluujah
Hallelujah
Halleluuuuuujah
We've heard the tale a million times
But many folks don't realize
The weight behind a powerful bo~nding union
It's not a myth engraved in stone
It can't be fe~lt when all alone
It makes me tell the whole world~ Halleluujah
Halleluujah
Hallelujah
Halleluuujah
Halleluujah
Hallelujaah
Halleluuuujah
Hallelujah
Halleluujah
Halleluuuuujah