Plucking strings and broken wings
Are the things that defined my Ponyville Summer
When Nice Nurse Mare from urgent care
Put my wings in slings oh gosh what a bummer
You wouldn't care when you're in the care of
When you're in the care of Lyra and Bon-Bon
I looked all day for a place to stay
But no vacancy signs went on for miles~
They saw my cast they didn't even ask
They took me right in to stay for a~ while~
You wouldn't ask when you're as desp'rate as I~
You don't ask why~ when it's Lyra and Bon-Bon
I watched them together while under the weather and
Couldn't believe my eyes
Two ponies like this who will share every kiss like
They'll share the rest of their lives
It made me blue and a little bit green
That they were flushed red with love
I'm too yellow to tell them I'm leaving today
Under the orange sunset above~
Ooh~~
Ooh~~~
Plucking strings and broken wings
Are the things that defined my Ponyville Summer