She's been shrink~ing
And no one knows~ why
We've been think~ing
Is she gonna die?
I have an ink~ling
Of when she's gonna stop
When she becomes the rock~
She's been turning grey
Or is it just our eyes
If she gets stuck this way
Can we adjust our lives?
Will she be okay
Will we still hear her talk?
When she becomes the rock
Everything about her is~ big
Except for her size
Don't waste your time feeling sad for her
You'll be sorry kid
The time of Maud is on the rise
Right before your eyes
She's been getting hard
Especially in her stare
It's no lie this part~
We're getting kinda scared
So lock your doors at night
'Cause you might hear a knock~~
When she becomes the rock
She's been getting smooth
Does she still have~ fur
There are no~ grooves
Anywhere on~ her
If you thought she was hard to move
Well you're in for a shock~~
When she becomes the rock~
Everything about her is~ big
Except for her size
Don't waste your time feeling sad for her
You'll be sorry that you did
The time of Maud is on the rise
Right before your eyes