A million stars, shine like spotlights
But not as much as you
In the most bashful walk, under the branch
I ask "Is there room for two?"
Talking like I'm robust, when more than anything
I wish someone would take me under their wing
Tired and freezing, but still he-ere, in spite
For one who is only awake at night
The sight of you sure brightens up every ni-ight
More than the sun ever could
So how abo-out it?
A colo-ony of just me~ and you
You're the moonlight that shines my way back home
When I don't know what to do
They say "Early to bed and early to rise
Makes a stallion healthy, and wealthy and wise"
But do you mind if I stay with you?
A colony
Of just me~ and you
A million thoughts run through my~ head
Of what I should say
My heart audible when I see you in my dreams
And when I think of you every day
I have come quite a way, in this night cold as stone
Hoping that when I see~ you, that you'd be alone
The closer I am, the slower I'll walk
Though my heart is stri-iking, I'm still in shock
The sight of you, just shatters away my fatigue
More than daylight eve-er has
How abo-out it?
A colo-ony of just me~ and you
You're the moonlight that shines my way back home
When I don't know what to do
They say "Early to bed and early to rise
Makes a stallion healthy, and wealthy and wise"
But I'd stay up all night with you
A colony of just me~ and you
Woah-oh-oh-woah-oh-oh
Just me~ and you
Just me and you
The perfect night sky, can only revolve around you
No one else but you
No one else bu-ut you
The stars live to spo-otlight you
If you'd le-et me
A colo-ony of just me and you
Leave our worries behind, take the whole world by storm
Immersing in every view
They say "Early to bed and early to rise
Makes a stallion healthy, and wealthy and wise"
But I'll stay up all night with you
A colony of just me~ and you
Woah-oh-oh-woah-oh-oh
Just me~ and you
Just me and you
Oh-oh, just me and~ you
Just me~ and you