Had a pegasister back in school
Only flier for a mile or two
We was like two hairs in a tail
Even got myself up to Cloudsdayle
Flock of friends flew me up held tight~
Bass and the liquor were poundin' till the daylight
Drunk hit my brain like a medium crescendo
Then they started chuckin' ponies out the window
One by one~ were thrown off
And flew back~ up do~ ing tricks~
It happened fast but some~ how
I~ got thrown~ off~ in~ the mix~~
The ground came at me lightning quick
Got me cryin' screamin' and kinda sick
You were too drunk to notice and too~ loud to listen but I
Guess my broken limb ain't worth the fallin'~ distance
Guess I'll heal myself on the ground cuz my
Lack of fringes just seems to slow you~ down
You called out
"Hey glad you didn't bite it!"
Ooh~ well glue your wings and jump and buckin' see how you~ like it
If there's a race in life you'd win I'll be
Here below the stratosphere while you stay~ in it
Can't flutter for nothin' but you still got a rise~
I'd love to be flapping instead~ of just tapping but that's
Just not hap'ning
I'll never be fly~ like~ you
Fly~ like you~~~~~~
Hey sorry to blink in but I heard you on the street
And I had to give my side of it
What the hell are you talk...
I played that show and sorry Dash was so shitty
But don't worry I put her in her place
Whatd'ya do? And who are you?
PON~ 3!
Spinnin' in the sky just hoofin' mah set
Then I saw you dive bomb no feathers no net I said
Hey dudes you got some wings you can spare
The muthabuckas shrugged it off like
She can grow a pair
So I cussed her out I don't give a shit
Got enough shows got enough bits
What was I gonna do? Sit and bite my lip?
Maybe you can clear your own clouds skip
I took mah horn to the window like a weapon
And I bust the sky up in about two seconds
Did it all without droppin' the beat
So how's it feel to be obsolete?
Watch that jaw drop put that attitude on
Full stop don't need wings to be on top
Pon- 3 on the bass
And I beat your time by eight
So how's that technicolor hat taste?
I've been told to turn~ the other cheek
And~ rise above it
But the weather is perfect
So all expect~ worship but
I~ think they can shove it~
Bite my tongue, choke, swallow and
Smile when I'm~ around~ her
But it's tough to be manic
'bout the aerody~ namic when there's
All these wiseguy pegasi flyin' by screamin'
(Suck it grounder!)
I~ give up~ whatever I tried
And I'll never crack your clique 'cuz I don't~ go~ Mach Five
Countin' down the days 'til you crash~ and~ witness
How gravity makes the rest of us its dirty little mistress
If there was a race in~ life you'd win
I'll be here~ below the stratosphere while you stay~ in it
Go and get your camera it's the last time I'll be by~
Flexing your wing's all you do~ it's depressing~~~~
Oh and watch out for lightning and turbulence
when you splat it's really nasty
To hell with your flapping all your wings will need wrapping
While we all die~ happy never bein' fly
Can't keep up whate~ver I do
Can't keep up whate~ver I do~~
Can't keep up whatever I do
But I'll die before I'm ever
Fly like you~
Fly like~ you
Fly like you
You~~~~
I'll never be fly~ like~ you