Three months of winter coolness
And awesome holi-idays
We've ke-ept our hoovsies warm at home
Time off from work to-o play
But the food we've stored i-is running out
And we ca-an't grow in thi-is cold
And even though I love my boots
This fashion's getti-ing old
A true, true friend
Helps a friend i-in need
A friend will be there to help you see
A true, true fri-end
Helps a friend in need
To see the light
That shines from a true, true friend
The time has come to welcome spring
And all things warm and green
But it's also time to sa-ay goodbye
It's winter we must clean
We move the clo-uds
And we melt the white snow
When the sun comes up
Its warmth and beauty will glo-o-ow
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend wi-ill be there to help them see
A true, true fri-end
Helps a friend i-in need to see the light
That shines from a true, true friend
Little critters hibe-ernate
Under the snow and ice
We must wake up all their sleepy heads
So quietly and nice
We help them gather up the-ir food
Fix their homes belo-ow
We welcome back the southe-ern birds
So their families ca-an grow!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend wi-ill be there to help them see
A true, true fri-end
Helps a friend i-in need to see the light
That shines from a true, true friend
Now that I know what they a-all do
I have to find my-y place
And help with a-all of my-y heart
Tough task ahead I face
How will I do without my magic?
Help the earth pony way
I wanna belong so I-I must
Do my best to-oday
Do my best toda-a-y!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend wi-ill be there to help them see
A true, true fri-end
Helps a friend in need to see the light
That shines
From a true, true friend