How could you run off frigh~tened
When they all needed you?
To leave them 'neath the spell, abandon all you once knew
And after all that's hap~pened
Just you alone are free
But what more can I do, then turn my tail and flee
I've lived a simple life
I'm no one great or migh~ty
What more could I have done
Who would the hero rightly be?
The hero I seek
Protect the humble and weak
If only I could find~ one
A warrior or mage
Or even search for him, the greatest wizard of this age
But who would wish to come
To save our lowly town
When monsters hide in every shadow that is found
But how would they all hide
If light could shine for all to see?
Why find a single knight
When we could have an army be
The heroes I seek
To fight what evil may wreak
If they'd only hear my plea
Far be~yond the Sirens
Just imagine what could be
We would stand the vanguard against anything
Every battle could be won
When they'd need~ us we would be
United, as guardians to save everyone
History is full of evils left astray
Like a plague upon the world
Darkness we could finally seal away
We could forge something great
Protect all those who are in need
Each foe would know their fate
As righteous Pillars they could be
The heroes I seek
To stand when all else looks bleak
To save the vanquished and meek
The heroes I seek
She came, demanding tribute
Our harvest hers to consume
As our hunger continued
It seemed she'd be our doom
There was no one to stop her
This Sphinx a beast so daunting
Yet still our Prince would be stirred
To resist her taunting
The beast was displeased
Snatched him away to her temple lair
For him to be freed
Her riddle must be solved if we dare
All we know
All we owe
All that shines as the Glowpaz glows
All from faith
All from Hope~
I knew it was my doing
From such an innocent alm
Quickly I galloped after
I knew I must save Hi~san
She asked me the phrase
One simple riddle with all at stake
Then, I would elate
I knew the answer without mistake
The sphinx scrunched up her wicked face
To hear the answer found
She roared and said "you'll know your place"
Then stomped against the ground
"But the riddles' solved!"
"You're not absolved"
She said with leering eyes
"Your bounty still belongs to me"
Her word, a hollow lie
I could not leave the Prince in chains
And let her steal from everyone
"But what about another game?
A challenge all or none"
"But if I win you'll go away
And leave our village be"
The Sphinx intrigued said: "We shall see"
Then laughed aloud in glee
Blind and without wings
She had me cross that most dangerous pool
But I made the leap
I held to Hope like a precious jewel
All we know
All we owe
All that shines as the Glowpaz glows
All from faith
All from Hope
I was blessed
I still owe
There's no way I could tell you "no"
I will come
Bring them Hope~!
As but a colt
I would work in the fields
Of our peaceful seaside realm
Wishing one day
I could be strong enough
To join the~ Mighty Helm
But I was small
Not muscled or tall
'Twas a thing I might never be
Shovel in hoof
I set out to prove
That they would have a place for me
With what strength I could find
I worked hard as I might
'Twas a dream I would never let go
With all body and mind
Through the day and the night
I refused to relent
'Til I made that dream so
Our village laid place
At a volcano base
Never once had we seen it blow
Then on that day
We found we would face
The~ wrath of its fiery glow
We had no way to fight
All the lava we saw
And the Helm said we had to go
But despite all our fright
We just couldn't withdraw
We could not leave our homes
And the land that we know
The river of lava got closer and closer
Soon to consume everything that we were
I could do little but had to do something
So shovel in hoof I dug into the dirt
Digging the trench all my efforts seemed foolish
Weak as I was I would run out of time
I needed a strength that would meet my ambition
When there in a flash happened something divine
With what I'd been blessed
I carved out the trench
And was able to save the town
The lesson I learned
Was still to endure
When it seems all is com~ing down
With Great Strength you can find
That no matter the fight
You can beat almost every foe
With your brethren combined
You'll be able to smite
Every villain that you couldn't face (just alone)
With the Helm at my side
We protected our land
And with them that will still be so
For these Sirens may try
But they're standing in sand
We'll knock them aside
Yes indeed I will go~~!
Deep here in the Hayseed Swamp
We've lived a long 'ol time
Doin' our best to get along
With all the critter life
Our masks and stews all simple but
It's peaceful and sublime
Never had too much hardship or
Even a little strife
'Til the folks fell sick
With all these horrid spots
Coughing up with bubbles
Sneezing lightning snot
Cough, pop, zap and boom
The plague was spreading way too soon
I feared it'd be our doom
If I could not mix a healin' brew
The fever'd claim me too
With no one left to do
We'd say adieu
Every old elixir and
Each potion I could find
Didn't change that accursed plant
Or poison that's inside
When soon it claimed my mother too
In bed she slept maligned
I stared down in the bayou to
See if that'd provide
Me the answer to
Save everyone I loved
When some flash bees flew out
Hovered just above
​Cough, pop, zap and boom
The flowers opened up their plumes
Cough, pop, zap and boom
And spread their toxic fumes
But the flash bees were left unamused
And took the pollen too
And that is when I knew
What I must do
After many tries
And far too many stings
I did realize
Just what would be the thing
For my healin' mask
Looked like the flash bee queen
Let me take their honey
Without gettin' mean
Cough, pop, zap and boom
One by one and room to room
The honey once consumed
Healed them all up quick, shooed away the gloom
We drank the healin' brew
And all escaped the tomb
But now… not much I can do
Unless you need a potion brewed
But I've done my due
To see our problems through
If you really think you need me too
I'll pack some different brews
And help you to undo
The Sirens' gloom
Being just a Legion grunt
I traveled wherever they needed me
And although the pegasi do rule the skies
The job ain't that easy
But it's not the griffons or the hippogriffs
That give us much to fear
When one of those giant stinking dragons
Gets a little bit too near~~~
Every tempest you may see~
None shall stay thee
Knowing you are called to be
Brave enough!
No matter what the problem
Forged so tough!
If it tries to kill you
Show your stuff!
'Cause it's them who won't be
Brave enough!
Then on such a mission
We did have to get
Across the dragon lands
When we saw two of them large enough
To wrap us in a single hand
Many of our comrades were ensnared
And taken back into their cave
I could not just leave them like that
There must be a way that we can save~!
Like feathers in a wing
We'd be nothing
And as one be ascending~
Brave enough!
Out from the cave I led them
Forged so tough!
As they tried to roast me
Show your stuff!
With the shield I could be
Brave enough!
As the storm was gathering
Full of lightning
You'll not be cowering
Brave enough!
Somehow we really made it
Forged so tough!
Like the shield we all could
Show your stuff!
Play the role we all should
Brave enough!
You've got guts
To pull this all together
You know what?
Yes I'm gonna join you
They'd be~ nuts
If they think they could beat
All of us!
All my life I saw the goodness in the world
In the great and little~ things
I had strived to bring more everywhere I could
Like a flower in the~ spring
Yet I was so unconscious of
Where ugliness could cling
Where such a pain might have fes~tered
Where I was need~ed to bring~~
True beauty inside
Not seeking glory
Trying to justify
I had let decay~
So~ long
After years I found my village left in ruin
How I felt like such a~ fool
That I'd let her steal all beauty that she could
To create an empty~ jewel
And what I found there upon the throne
In her abhorrent rule
Was an old friend I cared about
And I had let her turn so cruel~~
All beauty outside
Filling the palace
All an attempt to hide
A curse born from an en~vious pride~~
How our village cried
I should have seen
The cause of this great divide
Now I had to face~ her
For beauty isn't ours a~lone
A thing to steal or hoard or own
It is a light for all to~ see
A well of life to let flow~ free
And in the end, when I held her there
I knew I had to prove
Give up my beau~ty for everyone
And e~ven her too~~
True beauty inside
Shines on its own
All vanity aside
Frees those who let u~gliness hide~~~
All I could provide
All I can do
To help out your vil~lage too
I'll do it to help~
You~~
So now you've heard each story we~ could tell
And what has brought me to you as~ well
My village left bewitched beneath~ their song
With every passing day, it prolongs~~
Everyone I know and love
Cursed to be their slaves
We could bring the Si~rens down
We could save
I sympathise what you've en~dured
But you know not what you're saying
And know not its al~lure
All of my students come to~ learn
That all sorcery is power
Which demands that you dis~cern
You collect them like torches to burn a fire~ bright
But think not what to do when you too ignite
When forged by life, what we can create
Is all but a candle compared to the fates
But you wish to take their power for your own
When forged divine, a magic runs deep
An ocean whose edges that we'll never see
You know not the costs such sorcery
Could rise from the unknown
Respectfully, you must believe me
That these gifts that they~ were granted
Are branches of~ a tree
I think of them more like the~ sun
Not a group of little torches~
But a light for every~one
Or as beams in a rainbow of every colored light
Who could end e~very storm and be glowing bright
They're forged as one, whatever you say
All elements of something come from the fates
You can see it for yourself or turn away
For all you've done, the spells you have penned
The things that will shape ponykind to its end
Yet you disavow this chance we have
'Cause of what we might pay?
I know I should have died that day
By dragon fire or lightning yet
We found that we could do much more
When greater challenges are set
I thought I'd failed my home and kin
But from the state that things were in
We turned the darkness back and
Found the answer hiding deep within
While fear once al~most held me back
I couldn't sit around and mope
I had to take the leap and
Put my trust in hope
Alright, I've heard you make your~ case
It is clear to me these wonders
Must have a higher~ place
And since you'll do it either~ way
With a sorcerer~ to guide you
You might not go as~tray
There indeed is much darkness
That we could cast away
To a place they'd be left
To decay~~~~
So forged as one, with firmament laid
We'll rise up as Pillars protecting the gates
For all who may need us on that day
And forged as one, we'll keep building high
These gifts for all creatures to come for all time
And bring Harmony to all
Who have been left in dismay~~