How could you run off frigh~tened
When they all needed you?
To leave them 'neath the spell, abandon all you once knew
And after all that's hap~pened
Just you alone are free
But what more can I do, then turn my tail and flee
I've lived a simple life
I'm no one great or migh~ty
What more could I have done
Who would the hero rightly be?
The hero I seek
Protect the humble and weak
If only I could find~ one
A warrior or mage
Or even search for him, the greatest wizard of this age
But who would wish to come
To save our lowly town
When monsters hide in every shadow that is found
But how would they all hide
If light could shine for all to see?
Why find a single knight
When we could have an army be
The heroes I seek
To fight what evil may wreak
If they'd only hear my plea
Far be~yond the Sirens
Just imagine what could be
We would stand the vanguard against anything
Every battle could be won
When they'd need~ us we would be
United, as guardians to save everyone
History is full of evils left astray
Like a plague upon the world
Darkness we could finally seal away
We could forge something great
Protect all those who are in need
Each foe would know their fate
As righteous Pillars they could be
The heroes I seek
To stand when all else looks bleak
To save the vanquished and meek
The heroes I seek