Deep here in the Hayseed Swamp
We've lived a long 'ol time
Doin' our best to get along
With all the critter life
Our masks and stews all simple but
It's peaceful and sublime
Never had too much hardship or
Even a little strife
'Til the folks fell sick
With all these horrid spots
Coughing up with bubbles
Sneezing lightning snot
Cough, pop, zap and boom
The plague was spreading way too soon
I feared it'd be our doom
If I could not mix a healin' brew
The fever'd claim me too
With no one left to do
We'd say adieu
Every old elixir and
Each potion I could find
Didn't change that accursed plant
Or poison that's inside
When soon it claimed my mother too
In bed she slept maligned
I stared down in the bayou to
See if that'd provide
Me the answer to
Save everyone I loved
When some flash bees flew out
Hovered just above
​Cough, pop, zap and boom
The flowers opened up their plumes
Cough, pop, zap and boom
And spread their toxic fumes
But the flash bees were left unamused
And took the pollen too
And that is when I knew
What I must do
After many tries
And far too many stings
I did realize
Just what would be the thing
For my healin' mask
Looked like the flash bee queen
Let me take their honey
Without gettin' mean
Cough, pop, zap and boom
One by one and room to room
The honey once consumed
Healed them all up quick, shooed away the gloom
We drank the healin' brew
And all escaped the tomb
But now… not much I can do
Unless you need a potion brewed
But I've done my due
To see our problems through
If you really think you need me too
I'll pack some different brews
And help you to undo
The Sirens' gloom