All my life I saw the goodness in the world
In the great and little~ things
I had strived to bring more everywhere I could
Like a flower in the~ spring
Yet I was so unconscious of
Where ugliness could cling
Where such a pain might have fes~tered
Where I was need~ed to bring~~
True beauty inside
Not seeking glory
Trying to justify
I had let decay~
So~ long
After years I found my village left in ruin
How I felt like such a~ fool
That I'd let her steal all beauty that she could
To create an empty~ jewel
And what I found there upon the throne
In her abhorrent rule
Was an old friend I cared about
And I had let her turn so cruel~~
All beauty outside
Filling the palace
All an attempt to hide
A curse born from an en~vious pride~~
How our village cried
I should have seen
The cause of this great divide
Now I had to face~ her
For beauty isn't ours a~lone
A thing to steal or hoard or own
It is a light for all to~ see
A well of life to let flow~ free
And in the end, when I held her there
I knew I had to prove
Give up my beau~ty for everyone
And e~ven her too~~
True beauty inside
Shines on its own
All vanity aside
Frees those who let u~gliness hide~~~
All I could provide
All I can do
To help out your vil~lage too
I'll do it to help~
You~~