Come up, come up with a magical mystery cure
To save the day!
Come up!
Come up with a mystery cure!
A perfect preparation
For a coronation
The magical mystery cure
Is friendship that's saving the day
Magic that's saving the day
Come up!
Come up with a mystery cure!
You know friendship's all you need
It will restore harmony
The magical mystery cure
Is friendship that's saving the day
Magic that's saving the day
Mystery spell
Aaaaah!
The magical mystery cure
Come up!
Come up with a mystery cure
A perfect preparation
For a coronation
The magical mystery cure
Is friendship that's saving the day
Magic that's saving the day
The magical mystery cure
Is fixing what's happened today
Fixing what's happened today
Oh what a day