She can't be contained, she can't be controlled
Won't do what you say, and won't do as she's told
Heart of gold, and wings of steel,
An angelic face that's hell on wheels
She'll stay with you when things get dire
Your saving grace is a flaming tire
She's everything you want and everything you admire
That's why you call her Wild Fire!
She can't be contained, she can't be controlled
Won't do what you say, and won't do as she's told
Heart of gold, and wings of steel,
An angelic face that's hell on wheels
She'll stay with you when things get dire
Your saving grace is a flaming tire,
She's everything you want and everything you admire
That's why you call her Wild Fire!