Hey now, don't be sad
I know we cannot stay
But we've got a couple minutes
And a little time to play
I know you have important things
So it's oka-ay, just go
But we can still pick one small, little thing
To do with you, you know
One small thing
Doesn't seem like a lot
Work with the time you've got
Soon one small thing becomes two
After two, perhaps another few
Then one small thing is not so small
One small thing can be the biggest thing of all
All right now, since you're here
Let's see what we can do
Swim with the flow until you go
Together, me and you
I've got necklaces for everyfish
So what else do ya got?
Well, we could play the bubblefish
You'll like this one a lot
One small thing
It's a good place to start
And we don't seem so far apart
Soon, one small thing leads to more
It's so much more than there was before
Just one small thing, and you will see
The start of something big for you and me
One small thing
Or a tall thing
Or a sing thing
Or a bling thi-i-ing
A conga thing
Or a longer thing
A blue thing, true thing, you thing
A whee thing, sea thing, me thing
So many things and everything
Until our time is done
There's one small thing for each and everyone
One small thing, so much we can create
You and me, we sta-arted something great
It's so amazing, look around
At all the happy sights and so-o-unds
One small thing is big, it's true
You did this a-all for u-us
I just wish there was one small thing
An extra special kind of thing
That we could do for you
...We could do for you
One small thing