I do not worry, I'm never in a hurry
The past so far is just fine, I'll take it, risk it
The time that you've spent locked up with decisions
Has hindered more than aided, I'll free you, free you
Don't need a plan, the fun is unknown
I'm never alone, I've got you, got you
Don't need a map, the fun's adventure
And all I've risked yet - Dive in, dive in!
Dive in, dive in
I do not worry, I'm never in a hurry
The past so far is just fine, I'll take it, risk it
The time that you've spent locked up with decisions
Has hindered more than aided, I'll free you, free you
Don't need a plan, the fun is unknown
I'm never alone, I've got you, got you
Don't need a map, the fun's adventure
And all I've risked yet - Dive in, dive in!
Dive in, dive in
I hear the wind rushing past my ears
As I start to think, are they listening?
As I fly so fast, farther than they'd dare
'Cause my heart is full, theirs is filled with fear
'Cause they can't let go, they keep holding on
To the past, scared to be out of control
They will never know of this thrill, just think
That I'm cra~zy, when I dive in
Dive in, dive in