So I see you're still stuck on the ground~
Caught down there all warm and safe and~ sound
I know what it's like to be down there~
Dreaming of the sky and open~ air
One day soon I know you'll~ see
Raise your head and smile~ for me
Laugh about~ our histo~ry
Know just what you're meant to be
You sigh and always try to play it cool~
But deep inside you still feel like a fool
The world's so big and you, you feel so~ small
Wondering if you should try~ at all
But tomorrow's not til today is~ gone
Live the mo~ment, don't take~ long
Forget the trou~bles you think~ on
Smile~ for impending~ dawn
Is it time to break the mold?
Are you doing what you're told?
Go ahead, you can be~ bold
Live for living, don't be cold
When the final days have come
Smile at the mile's~ you have run
Come on have a little fun
Spread your wings your time has~ come~~~~~!
Sitting, hoping for the wings you've earned~
Silent as the fire in you~ burned
Brush away the dust and~ ash
On your shoulders from the past~
Smile~ at the things that last
Feel the beat~, your dice are~ cast
Stroke of luck, or fate, re~joice
Now you finally have a choice~
So prove them wrong in what they~ say~
Or wait another day