It was a bright and sunny day~ in August
Whe~n she came to town~
She had a carriage full of props and tricks
And a confidence that knew no bounds~
And my heart skipped a beat as love I found
The sun rose high as she got up on stage
And started to perform her~ show~
And as she shared her tricks I could feel~ the love
Inside of me begin to grow~
And my heart said don't you dare let her go
Tri~xie you're the mare I love
Girl you know it's true~
There ain't no other po~ny like you
Tri~xie you're the one I want
No one can stop me~ now~
I'm gonna make you mine somehow
Some ponies say she has an ego
Big enough for two but that's not~ true
She's a showmare and an artist
Her dedication will show through~
And I know nopony ever could outdo
Tri~xie you're the mare I love
Girl you know it's true~
There ain't no other po~ny like you
Tri~xie you're the one I want
No one can stop me~ now~
I'm gonna make you mine somehow
Tri~xie~~~
Tri~xie you're the mare I love
Girl you know it's true~
There ain't no other po~ny like you
Tri~xie you're the one I want
No one can stop me~ now~
I'm gonna make you mine somehow
Tri~xie~~~