Don't you know who you are?
I'm waiting for a new start
Dreaming of a new heart
Just praying for real love~
The days are ringing hollow
Like there is no tomorrow
No path for me to follow
Just waiting for real love~
I don't want to miss you
But I could never kiss you
Not after all I've lived through
And all~ you do
What's the worth of a word
Or all the words in the world?
Or all the worlds in the universe
When it can't get worse, no
What's the worth of my love
'Cause I was never enough
You know it's true~
I was never enough for you
Don't you know who I am?
I don't know if you can
I'm the shadow of a dead man
Just praying for real love~
But I am more than you know
And I know I can let you go~
No more taking things slow~
Just waiting for real love~
I could never miss you
And I could never kiss you
Not after all I've lived through
And all~ you do
What's the worth of a word
Or all the words in the world?
Or all the worlds in the universe
When it can't get worse~, no
What's the worth of my love
'Cause I was never enough
You know it's true~
I was never enough for~ you