So I see you're still stuck on the ground~
Caught down there all warm and safe and~ sound
I know what it's like to be down there~
Dreaming of the sky and o~pen air
One day soon I know you'll~ see
Raise your head and smile for me
Laugh about~ our histo~ry
Learn just what you're meant to be
You sigh and always try to play it cool~
But deep inside you still feel like a fool
The world's so big and you, you feel so~ small
Wondering if you should try at all
Well, tomorrow's not til today is~ gone
Live the moment, don't take~ long
Smile~ for impending~ dawn
Forget the troubles you think~ on
Is it time to break the mold?
Are you doing what you're told?
Go ahead you can be~ bold
Live for living, don't be cold!
When your final days have come
Smile at the mile's you have run
Come on, have a little fun
Spread your wings, your time has come!
Sitting, hoping for the wings you've~ earned
Silent as the fires in you~ burn
Brush away the dust and~ ash
On your shoulders from the past
Smile at the things that~ last
Feel the beat, your dice are cast
Stroke of luck, or fate, re~joice
Now you finally have a choice
So prove them wrong, this much is true
Just wait another day