What is this thing we call emotion?
Can it be brought into the light?
Where is it now? Is it on vacation?
Can someone help me out of my mind?
So many memories are jumbled and twisted
Crossed out the faces, and let go of friends
The line is slender between death and sadness
I've~ seen it over and over again
No more to this one, and no more to that one
Some thoughts are smeared~ with a canvas of black
I'm~ not ashamed~ of the pieces I'm missing
They're not much to~ la-a-a-a-ack
The shadow clouds our sight
But we know that, to light,
The dark will surren~der
So let us not forget
Of all the good we met
We~ will~ remember
Wonderful times or painful reflections
Confusing thoughts are plain as can be
It's all a maze of endless directions
But who said happiness would be free?
Sometimes I feel afraid, of all the memories ma-ade
And how~ they'll~ remind~ me
But I guess that's okay, 'cause I know that one day~
You'll come~ ba-ack to fi-ind me~
And once aga-a-ain
Oooh, I lose~ a frie-e-e-end
The faces come and go
They take a toll on~ knowing how~
They'll all be gone one day
Yet nothin' seems~ to slow me down~
The shadow clouds our sight
But we know that, to light,
The dark will surren~der
So let us not forget
Of all the good we met
We will~ remember