Who are you the next day
Well, I can only guess
You're hiding deep inside from real life and stress
And I want to understand what makes you who you are
We'll never let you fall apart
Let me see your true face
Behind veil and mask
Mystery
That's what you are
I will hide my true face
Behind veil and mist
Mystery
That's not true me
I cannot read your face
I cannot read your thoughts
You act like total stranger when you don't wanna talk
And I can barely see
What you need the most
I would have done anything
To have you here, so close
Let me see your true face
Behind veil and mask
Mystery
That's what you are
I will hide my true face
Behind veil and mist
Mystery
That's not
That's what you are
How could you look into my~ mind
My face is mask and there's nothing be~hind
My loneliness you cannot break
My feelings that you cannot fake
I'll hide again
I'll run away
Tomorrow I won't be the~ same
Let me see your true face
I will hide my true face
Behind veil and mask
Behind veil and mist
Mystery
That's not true me
That's what you are
I will hide my true face
Let me see your true face
Behind veil and mist
Behind veil and mask
Mystery not
Mystery