I thought he was someone to believe on his purposes
The only reason that I don't feel this right
than her eyes and her smile don't convince me
I can't express myself how this feels
It's like everything I did was for nothing
But he told you what if the world comes out in
Lose your calm with this half beast
He's crazy but hold on, this world will never be the same~
After all those changes he did to me
My dreams and my thoughts, my future has gone
The past now it's done than he can't leave me now~
Now! Because he's the only one who can change me now
Ah!
Shining goals what I thought complete
They turned to grey with this bad dream
Fighting is the only way to survive
Chaos will never win this now~
Lose your calm with this half beast
He's crazy but hold on, this world will never be the same
After all those changes he did to me
My dreams and my thoughts, my future has gone
The past now it's done that he can't leave me now~
Now! Because he's the only one who can change me now
Lose your calm with this half beast
He's crazy but hold on, this world will never be the same~
After all those changes he did to me
My dreams and my thoughts, my future has gone
The past now it's done than he can't leave me now~
Now! Because he's the only one who can change me now
Ah!