Oh~~ oh oh~~ oh oh~ yeah~~
If you could only see~ what it's like to be
Be yourself~ as you are you could be a shining star
If I could only be~ a little less like me
Be like you~ start a new learning everything you do
Just dress in your own style~ you don't need to impress
Just threw out all my clothes tell me where you got that dress
You can think for yourself~ just say what's on~ your mind
What you said is perfect I've got to memorize that line~
Be your~self
Be like you I wanna be just~ like you
Be like you from your shoes to your hair to your new shampoo
Try out a brand new hobby like painting or ballet
I~ just changed all my classes we can hang out every day~
Maybe take a trip~ it's a big world out there
I'll just stay close to you I'm not goin' anywhere~
Be yourself
Be like you I wanna be just~ like you
Be your~self
Be like you act like you we'll be best friends and sisters too