There is no feeling inside I can call my-y own
I-I cannot reap the seeds that I've never spoke
Even if it fee-els like this body is real
I've got to face the truth and fulfill my destiny-y-y-y-y
I am just a memory of a life I've ne-ever lived
I am just a memory of the gifts I cannot give
And even if I wa-anted to
I could never be like yo-ou
There is nothing to-o be
I am just a memory
I-I-I will continu-ue o-on...
There is no feeling inside I can call my-y own
I-I-I will...
I-I wi-ill continu-ue on...
I-I wi-i-i-ill...
This light inside of me just doesn't belong
E-emotions sho-ouldn't exist at all
A simple spe-ell i-is all that I a-am, you see
Should not procrastinate and you are master to me
I am just a memory of your imagina-ation
I am just a memory of something that should make yo-ou run
And you can try to defy it
But I'm an evil spi-irit
You can't save me-e-e-e
I am just a memory
I-I-I will continu-ue o-o-on...
I-I-I will...
I-I wi-ill continu-ue on...
I-I wi-i-i-ill...