I've waited far too long for my one~ moment to shine~
To show them all that I'm not like the other~ pegasi~
But you are told that you are not what they expected
"If you cannot push your limits, how do you~ expect to lead them?"
In the end, you will finally realize
I can see it in your~ eyes~
Count your stars and all your dreams~
And take off to the skies~
Shut out all~ of your doubts
And forget what you've been told~
This is what~ it'll take~
To be a Wonderbolt
So you all think you've got what it takes to be elite fliers, huh?
Yeah! Well uh...
Well I've got news for you
You don't!
If you had what it took you already would've been a Wonderbolt!
YES MA'AM!
So many times I've tried to show that I'm a leader
Pulled my head out from the clouds to show them all I'm not a dreamer
Speeding out~ just to be ahead~
We've been pushing everyone back in the dust
We showed them all
They've been outdone!
In the end you will finally realize
I can see it in your~ eyes~
Count your stars and all your dreams~
And take off to the skies~
Shut out all~ of your doubts
And forget what you've been told~
This is what~ it'll take~
To be a Wonderbolt
You took too long to see it
How could you be so blind~?
If you're going to~ be reckless
You can leave your dreams behind
Follow your ambitions
And do it your~ own way~~
You'll never see the light~~
(If you can't) clear it for today!
In the end you will finally realize
I can see it in your~ eyes~
Count your stars and all your dreams~
And take off to the skies~
Shut out all~ of your doubts
And forget what you've been told~
This is what~ it'll take~
To be a Wonderbolt
…You will finally realize
I can see it in your eyes~
Count your stars~ and all your dreams~
And take off to the skies~
Shut out all~ of your doubts~
And forget what you've been told
This is what~ it'll take~
To be a Wonderbolt!
Wonderbolt~, as you soar~ right to the sky~~!