I know the world can get you down
Things don't work out quite the way that you tho-o-ought
Feeling like all your best days a-are done
Your fears and doubts are all you've got
But there's a li-ight shining deep inside
Beneath those fears and doubts, so just squash 'em
And let it shine for all the world to see
That it is time, yeah, time to be awesome
Ah, ah-ah, awesome
It's time to be so awesome
Ah ah, ah-ah, awesome
You've no idea how hard it's been
This dull routi-ine we've been fo-orced to do-o
Don't let them ro-ob you of who you are
Be awesome, it's all up to you
I feel the li-ight stirring deep insi-ide
It's like a tale sti-i-ill yet to be to-o-old
And now it's time to break the shackles free
And start living like the brave and the bold
It's time to be awesome
Let loose, be true, so awesome
Go big, be you, so awesome
We used to soar through the clouds in the skies
Elaborate schemes we would love to devise
We rescued our treasure and stored it away
Sa-avi-ing those gemstones for a rainy day
We see that li-ight filling up our ski-es
So take the Storm King's orders and toss 'em
'Cause it's the time to let our colors fly
Hey, scallywags, it's time to be awesome
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!