Rewrite my program
Reset my brain
I think there's something wrong with what
I think
Alone I wander
Through wasteland scene
But still I find my mind won't let me be~~~
I am imperfection
I know I am flawed
Can somebody help me find
What I lost before~~
I am limitation
I know I can't exceed
Is there any hope
For a heart
That cannot be
I fought, I fought, I fought for a future
Where my life meant something real
I thought, I thought, I thought if I tried
Hard enough, I could find my own will
But circuitry keeps me from changing my function
A glitch in the system is all I have for it
Why would the maker make me aware of the flaw
I can't change
I am imperfection
I know that I am flawed
Can somebody help me find
What I lost before~~~
I am imitation
I know I can't exceed
Is there any hope for
A heart that cannot be