See the horizon the dawn is new
It was never our last adieu
Living faithful to a lover's eye
Insensible to when the moon will rise
Alas you shan't be ashamed
Their cynic parley is just the way they cry
The city we built turns to flame
Just close your eyes and fall to the sky
Where will we fly to?
Is this the honest truth?
Should I believe that it's a
world where I can't love you?
Why do we live at all?
Destined a fatal flaw
Is this some curtain call
Or from the river will we draw~~~~?
Well we know how the story ends
The hero declines~ and then he ascends
Never to see his love again
To tell the tale~ of what he learned then
"With feathers like yours
The sky is no li~mit"
From the gaze
His eyes slowly drifted
"Fly~, girl, don't you wait here anymore"
And without a word
The mare left him once~ more~
Where will we fly to?
Is this the honest truth?
Should I believe that it's a
world where I can't love~ you?
Why do we live at all?
Destined a fatal flaw
Is this some curtain call
Or from the river will we draw~~~~?