One! Two! One, two, three, four!
Dashing through the snow
In a one-horse open sleigh
Over the fields we go
Laughing all the way
Bells on bob tail ring
Making spirits bright
What fun it is to fly and sing
A sleighing song tonight
Oh, jingle bells
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to fly
In a one-horse open sleigh
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride
In a one-horse open sleigh
Thought I'd grab some friends
And take them for a ride
Not so sure what's up
As ponies run and hide
Put Rarity in the back
Right next to Pinkie Pie
Better buckle up, my friends
'Cause we're about to fly
Oh, jingle bells
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to fly
In a one-horse open sleigh
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride
In a one-horse open sleigh
Go grab Applejack
Who's hiding in the barn
Put her in the back
And leave behind the farm
Sky is clear and blue
And the wind is at our tails
Ponies, hold on tight because
We're 'bout to tip the scales
Tomorrow is Christmas morning
Tomorrow is Christmas day
And Santa's coming 'round the corner
And he's bringin' presents
'Cause he's been fillin' up that
Fillin' up that Santa sleigh
We start speeding up
As colors start to show
Streaming through our manes
The higher up we go
Even faster still
Faces fearing doom
What fun it is to fly and sing
As we SONIC RAINBOOM!
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to fly
In a one-horse open sleigh
Jingle bells
Jingle all the way
Oh, what fun it is to ride
In a one-horse open sleigh