My darling dears your mother's here
My love protects you there's no need to fear
I'm so sorry it all went wrong
Let me sing you a little song
We took the bride I took her form
And all of you prepared a mighty swarm
But our efforts were brought do-own low.
Tears of joy turned to tears of woe.
But worry-y not your mother has a plan
We will return and will take back the-e land
Strength in numbers we have o-on staff
So we will have the fi-ina-al laugh
Now listen close to what I have to say
Prepare to fly and we will win the-e-e day
If you're patient we'll carry-y on
And our foes will all soon be gone.
We must be smart we must be wise
We must be quick if we're to cla-aim the prize
Their dear princess controls the sun
And she's worshipped by ev'ryone
Her protege and all her friends
Must be dealt with before the story ends
Careful planning is what we need
This is what mother has decreed
We the hivemind, we the swarm have faith in our mother
She inspires us and teaches us and calms us during storms
If only others knew her love they wouldn't see a bad girl
For it's her love that keeps us safe out there in a cruel world
I can hear your song
It makes me proud to know you all are strong
Stretch your wings and prepare for flight
Bare your teeth and prepare to-o bite
Now rise and sing and call my name
Equestria will never be the same
We must act now the ti-ime is soon
To take down both the sun a-and moon
And then we'll feast at any time of day
And we will rule in ev'ry single-e way
No more hiding, we will be free
When the ponies look u-up to see
A mighty swarm consuming the whole world
A changeling army with its fa-angs unfurled
Food aplenty for all our kin
Over others we a-all sha-all win.
We the swarm will take whatever lands upon our plates
We don't care what price we must pa-a-ay!
And in any kind of weather we all have to stick together,
And we don't want it any other way!
Let's feed!
Yes I do so-o love my-y brood
It's my~ heart that feeds them food
I won't let harm come to what is mine!
Hurry now we must take care
We must be ready and we can't fight fair
With the buzzing of countless wings
Gather all your most precious things
And follow me as we take flight
We can't stop now because the ti-ime is right
Raise your voices and fill the-e air
Hidden monsters; we're ev'rywhere
The ponies' time is coming to an end
An age of changelings will begin again
We will conquer and we will rule
And the ponies will be our fools
They all will fall for our grand masquerade
And they won't doubt the faces o-on parade
Let's make haste so we can proceed
This is what mother has decreed!
La la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la laaaaaaaa