Take a seat youngin'; Stay around for a spell
I got a little story that I wanted to tell
Would ya
Please stick around, take a listen and see
Cause back in my day, things were always grand as can be
Now all the
Streets were paved with gold and gems; Glimmerin'
Lightin' up the skies at noon; This town is shimmerin'
Waitin' on nobody cause we got stuff to do
Cause we're through with the new
We're talking old school, just
Back in the da-ay it was the prime of the ti-ime
Imagine all the greats singing together in rhy-ymes
and listening together o-on old gramophones
and on old radios it was a hell of a ti-ime
Let me tell ya youngin', man the old days were grand
You could walk down to the beach and plant your hooves in the sa-and
have no worries
All was grand as can be
So everybody take a listen
Open your eyes and see
Trot with me through the autumn leaves
And keep close to stay warm
Soon you'll see how much you mean to me
Feelings I've never felt before
Skippi-do-bop was the name of the game
Swinging like crazy everyone goes insa-ane
It's a ga-ame except everyone wins
Why isn't music like that, anymore?
My god everything is such a bore now
Everything's the same over again
With all that hippin' and the hoppin'
and the bippen' and the boppen'
They dunno what the jazz is all about, you see
You'll look back at your days
I'm sure you will experience it sometime
'cause when you grow old
everything seems cold
a new generation will arri-i-i-ive
Trot with me through the autumn leaves
And keep close to stay warm
Soon you'll see how much you mean to me
Feelings I've never felt before
Trot with me through the autumn leaves
And keep close to stay warm
Soon you'll see how much you mean to me
Feelings I've never felt before