CQ CQ CQ DX
Every morning when day~ breaks
Lonely days, radio waves
Sending just one way
Waiting, waiting all day long
Maybe my modulation's wrong
Lighthouse on the shore
I can't hold no more
Call me, call me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I am lonely here
Call~ me, call~ me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I'm so lonely here
CQ CQ CQ DX
Without you my heart breaks
Lonely nights, I'm alone
With my ear~phones
Waiting, waiting all the night
My call sign is always~ right
Echo Queen 1 L H Y
I am standing by
Call me, call me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I am lonely here
Call~ me, call~ me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I'm so lonely here
Call me, call me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I am lonely here
Call~ me, call~ me
My Cutie-H: Equestria
Please hear me loud and clear
I'm so lonely here