Wading through a ruthless wasteland
Stealing glimpses at the light
Whoever thought we’d be walking without you
You were the glue that kept us all so tight
Darkness wants to last forever
All that's good just seems to pass
The insight you had that you gave to us freely
You made our view grow brighter and clearer
By passing through your glass
And now that we are on our own
The rain~ has gotten wetter
All the clouds are more dark
But we will~ make these things better
Your keen eyes for observation
Peering out for duty's need
I had been blessed when they set~tled upon me
Flawed and foolish it was all agreed
As time went on we grew closer
Little secrets get revealed
And All together~ we could work magic
You helped me to understand the need
Your~ strength, our shield
And now that we are on our own
The rain~ has gotten wetter
All the clouds are more dark
But we will~ make these things better
One less soul who knows our secrets
Another spirit roaming free
For sure I know we’ll take heed of the whispers
Left in our ears like shadows that could be
We have dreams and inner demons
We push on through our regret
We’re thinking about all the joy at our victories
Even while sadness snares us in its net
So I know that we’ll remember
Even if we need you now
It’s easy to start, but it’s so hard to finish
Living without you there’s less to hold on to
It’s so much harder now
And now that we are on our own
The rain~ has gotten wetter
All the clouds are more da~ark
But we will~ make these things better
And now that we are on our~ own
The road has gotten longer
With every step we~ take
We are grow~ing ever stronger