Back on the road of adventure
Saving the world yet again
Faking the smile for the goodbye
Why do I have to pretend?
Don't get me wro-ong, I belong here
Facing the fire with my friends
But I always look forward to afte-er it a-all ends
I'd rather be in the o-orchard
Kickin' the trees while the su-un sets
Oh, I'd rather be with my family
But I know that he-ere i-is whe-ere they ne-eed me
Brother can handle the harvest
Sister can grow on her own
Granny will keep things in o-order
Good thing they're not all alone
Don't get me wro-ong, it's a pleasure
To wander aro-ound every land
But I often wish I had my own roof ove-erhead
I'd rather be in the o-orchard
Kickin' the trees while the su-un sets
Oh, I'd rather be with my family
But I know that here i-is whe-ere they need me-e-e
I'd rather be in the o-orchard
Kickin' the trees while the su-un sets
Oh, I'd rather be with my family
But I know that he-ere i-is where they need me