In un mondo splendi-ido
Colorato e magi-ico
Little ponies vivo-ono
Pace e sempre in armoni-ia
In a colorful magical land
Filled with beauty, isn't it grand?
Little ponies live peacefully, and
Harmony won't ever e-end
They make the sun shine splendi-idly
And keep the land safe from foes of harmony
The joy they spread will make yo-ur day
When you pass the-em by-y
Go take flight, my little pony
No need to be lonely
You'll make it, I promise
Listen close, while we're together
We'll build up our friendships
Thro-ugh all kinds of weather
Go take flight, my little pony
No need to be lonely
You'll make it, I promise
Listen close, while we're together
We'll build up our friendships
Thro-ugh all kinds of weather
Don't you stop!
My little pony, if you wanna make friends then
Come here where it's sunny
Come here where it's su-u-unny!
Go take flight, my little pony
No need to be lonely
You'll make it, I promise
Listen close, while we're together
We'll build up our friendships
Thro-ugh all kinds of weather