The sound of every beating heart
Is music to my ears
The melody is torn apart
When listening through tears
Is it too soon~, or am I too late?
How have I done?
The words still echo
But I'm not repeating one
This is who I'm meant to be
Raise that sun so I can see
Again
One by~ one
Days seem longer
Let me~ run
Let me~ wander
I wish to leave it all ~behind
And never to return
It seems avoiding what is mine
Is not the way to learn
Ring around the rosie
No one really knows me
Ashes to ashes
The walls fall down
This is who I'm meant to be
I am lost so mental~ly
Again
One by~one
Days seem longer
Let me~ run
Let me~ wander
One by~ one
Days seem longer
Let me~ run
Let me~ wander