Look, here, are three little ponies
Ready to sing for this crowd
Listen up, 'cause here's our story
I'm gonna sing it
Very loud
When you're a younger pony
And your flank is very bare
Feels like the sun will never come
When your cutie mark's not there
So the three of us will fight the fight
There is nothing that we fear
We'll have to figure out what we'll do next
Till our cutie marks are here
We are the Cutie Mark Crusaders
On a quest to find out who we are
And we will never stop the journey
Not until we have our cutie marks
They all say that you'll get your mark
When the time is really right
And you know just what you're supposed to do
And your talent comes to light
But it's not as easy as it sounds
And that waiting's hard to do
So we test our talents ev'rywhere
Until our face is blue
We are the Cutie Mark Crusaders
On a quest to find out who we are
And we will never stop the journey
Not until we have our cutie marks
We are the Cutie Mark Crusaders
On a quest to find out who we are
And we will never stop the journey
Not until we have our cutie marks