Look, here, are three little ponies
Ready to sing for this crowd
Listen up, 'cause here's our story
I'm gonna sing it
Very loud
When you're a younger pony
And your flank is very bare
Feels like the sun will never come
When your cutie mark's not there
So the three of us will fight the fight
There is nothing that we-e fear
We'll have to figure out what we'll do next
Till our cutie marks are here
We are the Cutie Mark Crusa-aders
On a quest to find out who we a-are
And we will never sto-op the journey
Not until we have our cutie ma-arks
They all say that you'll get your mark
When the time is really right
And you know just what you're suppo-osed to do
And your talent comes to-o li-ight
But it's not as easy as it sounds
And that waiting's hard to do
So we test our talents e-ev'rywhere
Until our fa-ace is blue
We are the Cu-utie Mark Crusa-aders
On a quest to find out who we are~
And we will never stop the jo-urney
Not until we have our cutie mark
We are the Cutie Mark Crusa-aders
On a quest to find out who we a-a-are
And we will never stop the jo-urney
Not until we have our cutie marks