Another night I spend alone
Another silent ma-are forced out in the cold
My mind is left to wonder
When do my dreams come true
This starry ni-ight we're under
Are the stars dreaming too
And I kno-ow now
The truth we-e seek
In this lonely-y night
Isn't quite so bleak
It's Ok
I'm right here
Don't you ever feel alone
If you ever need a shoulder
To cry on
Come find me
You're not different
We're a-all the-e sa-a-ame
I seem to ble-end in perfectly
It's as though they can't even see
I'm standing ri-ight in front of them
I'm standing right before them
And it seems crystal clear
Nobody wants me here
Why do we e-even go on
When everybody's screaming
I kno-ow now
The truth we-e seek
These lonely-y nights
Isn't quite so ble-e-a-ak
It's Ok
I'm right here
Don't you ever feel alone
If you ever need a shoulder
To cry on
Come find me
You're not different
We're a-all the-e sa-a-ame
It's O-Ok
I'm ri-ight here
Don't you ever feel alo-one
If you ever need a shoulder
To cry on
Come find me
You're not different
We're a-all the-e sa-a-ame
And if you try
I know you'll win
Just spread your wings
And fly