Oh Uh-Whoa
There's a chance that I could fall
And no-ot co-ome back
And never regret a thi-ing
I'd never get back on tra-ack
Darkness all around me
I can't find the light
I let it all surround me-e
Giving up without a fight
The bitterness and pain inside
Countless tears I had to cry
I was facing all my fears
Just to let you in
To dry my tears, bu-ut
Your kindness won't betray me
I feel your heart and soul
Your kindness still can save me
I choose to-o not let go
Stretching out you somehow reach me
I know this can't be wro-ong
I'm re-eady won't you teach me
Your song of ki-indness
Quiet grace surrou-unds you
And helps me find my-y own
I can't tell you how you've helped me
And how much I have grown
Even though you're far away
Inspiration comes from you
To shine a little brighter every day
If you only knew
I will never get upset
And I will never, ever forget
The happiness you made me feel
Almost as if you're actually real, but
Your kindness won't betray me
I fe-el your heart and soul
Your ki-indness sti-ill can save me,
I choose to-o not let go
Stretching out you somehow reach me
I kno-ow this can't be wro-ong
I'm re-ady, won't you teach me
Your song of ki-i-indne-ess
Your kindness won't betray me
I fe-el your heart and soul
Your ki-indness still can save me
In a way you'll neve-er know
Your kindness won't betray me
I feel your he-eart and soul
Your ki-indness still can save me
I choose to-o not let go
Stretching out you somehow reach me
I kno-ow this can't be wro-ong
I'm re-ady, won't you teach me
The way to get along
Even when the cold wind's blo-owing
And I want to just give i-in
It warms my heart just kno-owing
I'll hear your voice a-again
So wo-on't you sing it loud
And won't you sing it long
I pro-omise to remember
Your song of ki-indne-ess
I-I promise to-o remembe-e-er
I promise to-o remember