I am now what I~ wannabe
Stand by my side
We all shall be~ e~quality
Oh~~~
And I will make my~ dream~~
Become rea~li~ty~~
And I will leave~ no apology
Because I have~ now authority
You are too far gone to come around
Your world is coming down~~~
All things falling, and you're calling out
Wishing you had listened to me now
Equality, identical
We all are the same, and best of all
You're still below~~ me
So welcome to a brave new world
Two lines on a flag, and now
You're turning toward me
Come and get it, I will make you regret it
This is the moment to step in
And give in your everything
Fully convinced, I will go for the win
So bring all that you worship
It won't stop a thing
Been through disasters
What I thought after
Was the abandoned but still I was casted
Spellbooks were blasted, still I was faster
Now the student outperforms the master
Magic I hijacked, rage I made unpacked
Played time itself, harder than backtrack
Still counting stacks, cutie marks on racks
Left out every track, done with looking back
Saw through every scam
Outran the program
Took in every wham
Still took the marks back
My Starlight refuses to scram
I'll rimram all of you wannabe glim glams