We'll take a walk down by the river
Watch the sunset from the fi-eld
We'll plant the seeds of lo-ove together
And water 'em right for a really good yield
Sugar Belle, sweet as pie
You're the apple of my e-eye
A cherry blossom in a field of rye-e-e
And when the heifer's milked and fed
And the pigs are in the sty
Won't you be the-ere by my si-ide?
Sugar Belle, when I look in your eyes
*cough* I see the color... blue
And it reminds me of the sky above
Uh, which is also blue
I've been writin' this song for yo-u
Searchin' for the perfe-ect rhyme
For the words I wanna sa-a-ay
Somethin', summ summ summ..., Be mine
Sugar Belle!
Roses are red and violets are blue!
Sugar Be-elle!
Sugar Belle!
...Be-e-ell...