Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
Manehattan, back to Ponyville
The path is laid out for~ me
Got my buckets of water filled
My delivery
The road ahead is long
And it's dangerous and sca~ry
But I'll just keep singin' this song
Free of all wary
I know to keep moving on
Don't need no train or fee
I know from the break of dawn
Celestia watches me
That's why I'm
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
I made my way through a small town
Where I was greeted evenly
Smiles were all around
I was welcomed equally
In the mountains I met a buffalo
He looked so sad and all alone
I said "don't hang your head so low
I'm also far from home"
I told him "No need to grunt
Just get back on track"
I told him "A hoof in front
Eventually leads you back"
I'll keep on…
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
I'll keep on singin' this tune~
With a smile on my face~
I'll be home very soon~
Just gotta keep up the Snails pace
Na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
Canterlot was great
I could see my house from up on high
And there across the way
The winged city in the sky
Home sweet home at last
Ponyville needs a refreshing drink
My journey was a blast
It was over in a blink
It's great to finally be done
And see my home again
It's great to think about it none
And finally call it in
I'm now done
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
Carryin' my water
My water, my wa~ter
On my shoulder pole
On my shoulder pole~~