Before the sun comes up
You gotta start your rocket boosters
Rise and shi-ine, I'm feelin' fine
Wake up, Mister Rooster
The early bird gets the wo-orm
The su-unrise makes me squirm
O-oh, keepin' busy is keepin' good
Keep on goin' just like you should
Call me crazy, misunderstood
But you won't hear me complain
'Cause I got time to spare
Fun to share
My friends along
A job well done by the break of da-a-a-a-awn
So many things need gettin' done
'Round the neighborhood
So get to work and get it done
Before the gettin' goin' gets go-od
Most people dread the grit and grime
But elbow grease works every time
Keepin' busy is keepin' good
Keep on goin' just like you should
Call me crazy, misunderstood
But you won't hear me complain
'Cause I got time to spare
Fun to share
My friends along
A job well done by the break of dawn
Count my chickens, milk the cows
Hang those lights, I'll show ya how
Invite my friends, clean the barn
This is so excitin'!
Strum a guitar and sing this yarn
Keepin' busy is keepin' good
Keep on goin' just like you should
Call me crazy, misunderstood
But you won't hear me complain
'Cause I got time to spare
I got fu-un to share
My friends along
A job well done by the break of dawn
Keepin' busy is keepin' good
Keep on goin' just like you should
Call me crazy, misunderstood
But you won't hear me complain
'Cause I got time to spare
I got fun to share
My friends along
A job well done by the break of da-a-a-a-awn
Zzzz!