As the sunlight leaves and darkness
Brings along a-a starry sky
You will dive into your dreams
Laying down you close your eyes
But there are so many wonders
Missing out? That can't be right!
Jump off bed, co-ome on and join us
Party on until sunrise
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
I won't let you sleep
Come to party all night
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
Let's go dance together
The moon's shining bright
Hah!
We are the night shift, we are silent
Watching out as you all shun
But these rules can be so boring
So let's break them and have fun
Giggles ring as it's exciting
Doing things you're not allowed
Would you dare to break out havoc
Beat the drums and sing out loud?
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
I won't let you sleep
Come to party all night
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
Let's go dance together
Under the moonlight
Tend the burdens your heart carries
Come along and join the fun!
Loosen up, forget your worries
Dance with me, the night is young
This is awesome, this is crazy
There is magic in the air
Give in to the Midnight Frenzy
Party on without a care!
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
I won't let you sleep
Come to party all night
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
Let's go dance together
Under the moonlight
You are too young to be up late!
Loosen up and celebrate!
Hooves are banging on the floor!
That's a nice beat, do some more!
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
I won't let you sleep
Come to party all night
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
Let's go dance together
The moon's shining bright
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
I won't let you sleep
Come to party all night
Ey Oh Ey Oh Ha!
Let's go dance together
The moon's shining bright