This brand new school of friendship
Is home to everyone
We're learning how to trust
We're here to all have fun
With friendship ties that bind us
Tighter than~ the strongest bonds
We're hoof-in-hoof~~
In hand in hoof in wing or even claw
There's a griffon in the garden
Hippogriffs hang in the hall
And the door will be open to
All creatures great and small
And a yak or two or three
Sing in perfect harmony
That might have been a changeling
But it kind of looks like me~
This school of friendship is for all of us~
A place where we belong~
Where we all learn to share and trust
The only rule here is to find your way~
And friendship always wins at the end~ of the day
Some things you just can't teach with books
Some things you only know~
So trust your heart and let us lead~
And your friendship's~ sure to grow
And once we master kindness
We will spread it 'cross this land
And give the gift that's ours to share
So others understand
This school of friendship is for all of us~
A place where we belong~
Where we all learn to share and trust
The only rule here is to find your way~
And friendship always wins at the end~ of the day