When you're rife with devastation
There's a simple explanation
You're a toymaker's creation
Trapped inside a crystal ball
Now whichever way he tilts it
Know that we must be resilient
We won't let them break our spirits
As we sing our silly song
When I was a little filly
A galloping blaze overtook my city
They shipped me off to the orphanage
Said, "ditch those roots if you wanna fit in"
So I dug one thousand holes
And cut a rug with orphan foals
Now, memories are blurred, and the faces are obscured
But I still know the words of this song
When you've bungled all your bangles
And your loved ones have been mangled
Listen to the jingle jangle
Of my gypsy tambourine
'Cause these chords are hypnotizing
And the whole world's harmonizing
So please children stop your crying
And just sing along with me
When I was a little filly
A galloping blaze overtook my city
They shipped me off to the orphanage.
Said, "ditch those roots if you wanna fit in"
So I dug one thousand holes
And cut a rug with orphan foals
Now, memories are blurred, and their faces are obscured
But I still know the words of this song
When you've bungled all your bangles
And your loved ones have been mangled
Listen to the jingle jangle
Of my gypsy tambourine
'Cause these chords are hypnotizing
And the whole world's harmonizing
So please children stop your crying
And just sing along with me
When you've bungled all your bangles
And your loved ones have been mangled
Listen to the jingle jangle
Of my gypsy tambourine
'Cause these chords are hypnotizing
And the whole world's harmonizing
So please children stop your crying
And just sing along with me