I used to think that stories were just that
Set in stone, concrete as a-a fact
It didn't dawn on me
That I could change history
Now I kno-ow I'm writi-ing my-y own song
Fight my way to the ending that I want
I'll turn a tragedy
Into an epic fantasy-y
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You can be a hero, too
Oh-oh-oh
Take my hand, I'm here for you
Come away with me
Be the legend you are meant to be
You'll always be ever free
Oh, oo-wah, ah-oh, oo-wah, ah-oh, oo-wah
To be the legend you are meant to be
There was a ti-ime when fear would hold me down
'Cause I let it chain me to the ground
Look at me no-ow, I'm soaring high
It's never bo-oring in the sky-y
When I kno-ow I've got friends o-on my side
Whatever tri-als, I'll take them all in stride
Together we will shine so bright
A radiant brilliance in the night
Hey! Hey! Hey!
You can be a hero, too
Oh-oh-oh
Take my hand, I'm here for you
Come away with me
Be the legend you are meant to be
You'll always be ever free
Oh, oo-wah, ah-oh, oo-wah, ah-oh, oo-wah
To be the legend you are meant to be