There's a long and winding road ahead
A few black clouds lay overhead
And the shining sun is nowhere to be seen
But with every step and fall you take
All your thoughts and leaps of faith
There's a silver lining somewhere in between
Close your eyes
Breathe in slow
Then let it go~~~~
Stop and smell the roses when your journey's getting long
When you feel your life's against you and your energy is gone
'Cause not everybody knows when it's just time to catch a break
When you're draining and you just don't wanna sho-ow it
Stop and smell the ro-oses
Today has found another way
To turn right into yesterday
'Cause time has taken all the light again
But if I fiddle with reality
To try and change who I should be
I'm tucking my own destiny in bed
Close your eyes
Breathe in slow
Then let it go~~~~
Stop and smell the roses when your journey's getting long
When you feel your life's against you and your energy is gone
'Cause not everybody knows when it's just time to catch a break
When you're draining and you just don't wanna sho-ow it
Stop and smell the roses when your journey's getting long
When you feel your life's against you and your energy is gone
'Cause not everybody knows when it's just time to catch a break
When you're draining and you just don't wanna sho-ow it
Stop and smell the ro-oses