Now, Rainbow my dear,
I cannot express my delight
It's abundantly clear
That somewhere out here
Is the pet that will suit you just right
I can't wait to get started,
But first let me set a few rules
It's of utmost importance
The pet that I get
Is something that's awesome and cool
Awesome, cool, got it
I have so many wonderful choices,
Just wait, you will see
I need something real fast
Like a bullet to keep up with me
Sure! How 'bout a bunny?
They're cutsey and wutsey
And quick as can be
Cutsey? Wutsey? Have you even met me?
Rainbow have faith
You see, I will bet you
Somewhere in here is the petthat will get you
C'mon, the sky's the limit!
Sky is good. I'd like it to fly!
Really? Because I think this widdle puddy tat
Has your name written all over him
Yes he does
Aww, look, he likes you!
Pass.
I have so many wonderful choices
For you to decide
There are otters and seals
With massive appeal
Otters and seals do not fly
Maybe not, but I've seen this particular seal catch
Ten feet of air when he breaches the water
That's it. I'm outta here.
Wait! There must be a pet here
That will fit the ticket
How 'bout a ladybug or a cute cricket?
Bigger! And cooler!
Bigger. Cooler. Right.
I've got just the thing in that tree, Dash
Meet your new fabulous pet
Squirrely!
It's just a squirrel
Not just any squirrel
A flying squirrel!
Yeah... So, like I was saying...
Fluttershy, pal, this won't cutit
I need a pet to keep up with me
Something awesome, something flying
With coolness that defies gravity
I'm sensing you want an animal that can fly
Ya think?
I have plenty of wonderful creatures
Who soar in the sky
Like a sweet hummingbird
Or a giant monarch butterfly
Better, but cooler!
I see, how 'bout an owl,
Or a wasp, or a toucan?
There's so many wonderfulcreatures the likes of that
There are falcons and eagles
They are both quite regal
Perhaps what you need
Is a dark and mysterious bat
Now you're talking!
But instead of just one stand out,
Now that's too many
So many choices,
And such riches aplenty
Not a bad problem to have if you ask me
The bat would be awesome,
But the wasp I'm digging too
D'you have something in a yellow striped bat?
No, I've got a hot pink flamingo,
Just dying to meet you
What to do? What to do? *GASP*
A prize! That's it!
There's really just one way
To find out which animal's best
Hold a contest, of speed,
Agility and guts
That will put each pet to the test!
Don't forget style,
That should be considered
Then we'll know for sure
Who's best of the litter
One who is ultimate cool
Just like me
Can't settle for less, 'cause I'm the best
So a contest we will see
Who's the number one, greatest, perfectest pet
In the world for me!
May the games begin
And may the best pet win!