When you hear the word "Magic"
Do you think of spells and incantations?
Think of flying brooms and cauldrons
Think of things that sci~ence can't explain
And the word "Friendship"
Do you think of those who are together
From now until fore~ver
To me they're the sa-ame thi-ing
And I've always had the Sun to guide my way
Didn't always have the Moon, but now she's here~ to stay
And I've always had~ Love deep inside~ my heart
And I know we'll never pa-art
It's ma~gic
Woah, ma~gic
Fore~ver
And e~ver
It's ma~gic
Wo-oah, ma~gic
When we're hеre
Toge~ther
And thе stars that shine in the Night
Retain the me~mory of every sin~gle Twilight
I spend with you
And that feels like magic
I can feel our hearts beat in time
I can feel our souls begin~ to shine
I can see a sparkle in your~ eyes
And when I do, I know all will be fine
So Loy~al, so Generous
So Kind, so Ho~nest
And all the while, Laughing all the way
Let me hear you shout one last time
Say he-e-ey!
It feels as if we've gotten to~ the end
But despite~ all that you'll always be my friend
There might come a time where we have to say goodbye
Just smile
If you cry I'll dry your~ eyes
It's ma~gic
Woah, ma~gic
Fore~ver
And e~ver
It's ma~gic
Wo-oah, ma~gic
When we're hеre
Toge~ther
And thе stars that shine in the Night
Retain the me~mory of every sin~gle Twilight
I spend with you
I know some days it feels like the darkness could win
I know it won't if we rise up and don't give in
Now let's stand, hand in hand
Together si-ide by side
We're at our strongest when we unite
Whoa-oh
Woah-oh
Wo-oah, oh
Whoa-oh
(Sing it!)
And I've always had the Sun to guide my way
Didn't always have the Moon, but now she's here~ to stay
And I've always had~ Love deep inside~ my heart
And I know we'll never pa-art
It's ma~gic
Woah, ma~gic
Fore~ver
And e~ver
It's ma~gic
Wo-oah, ma~gic
When we're hеre
Toge~ther
And thе stars that shine in the Night
Retain the me~mory of every sin~gle Twilight
I spend with you
And that feels like magi-ic