One-two-three, one-two-three…
I don't wanna change~~ you
I don't want to make~~ you different
I'm happy with the way~ it is~
And the way it isn't
We fit like puzzle pieces
In a per~~~fect way
Don't go seein' rain~drops
On a sun~~ny day
Oh I don't believe that my world isn't real
I wouldn't take you from yours
I just wanna find me~ some ma~gic somehow
Oh, don't be~ a neighsayer now
I wish you saw yourself
The way I've al~~ways seen you
You're so much stron~ger now~
For all you've been through
I don't believe that my world isn't real
And I wouldn't take you from yours
I just wanna find me some ma~gic somehow
Oh, don't be a neighsayer now
Together is better
You're my best friend forever
Together, whatever
May come my way~, I say
That I don't believe that my world isn't real
And I wouldn't take~ you from yours
I just wanna find me~ some magic somehow
Oh~, don't be a neighsayer now
Ahh, hmm~~mm… hmm hmm-hmmm