I watched them change before my eyes
Destinies rearranged to my surpri~se
I tried so hard to make amends
But my mistake has separated my fri~ends
White turned to blu~ue, and blue to white
Harmony rewritten ou~t of si~ght
What can I do to bring you back?
My technicolor world has faded to bla~ck
Wake up now and see the truth
I'm here to show the world to you
The way it was meant to be
So follow your destiny
This twisted future isn't right
Let's bring the real you to the light
I'm going to make you realize
So open your eyes
I've made mistakes and failed before
But somehow this time it's something mo~re
Broken your life and who you are
I'm afraid I've left a terrible scar~
But apologi~es won't save me now
It's up to me to restore you someho~w
I'll bring you back your memories
Piece by piece restoring harmony~
Wake up now and see the truth
I'm here to show the world to you
The way it was meant to be
So follow your destiny
This twisted future isn't right
Let's bring the real you to the light
I'm going to make you realize
So open your eyes
I've got to find a way
To make this all oka~~y
To fix my own mista~~ke
Oh, but I promise to succeed
I know you're still in need
I know you've been misused
And you're probably confused
But there's not much I can do
The cure is within you
So hold on tight
And open your e~~yes
Wake up now and see the truth
I'm here to show the world to you
The way it was meant to be
So follow your destiny
This twisted future isn't right
Let's bring the real you to the light
I'm going to make you realize
So open your e~yes
Wake up now and see the truth
I'm here to show the world to you
The way it was meant to be
So follow your destiny
This twisted future isn't right
Let's bring the real you to the light
I'm going to make you realize
So open your e~yes