The wind ruffling my mane
The speed, the sky, the rain
I still feel them constantly
When we're together
Sometimes, yes, it's tough
(but I) Can't rush fast enough
To stand by your side forever...
Oh Rainbow...
Fears and threats
Don't worry, defeat them
Lies, regrets
Forget those, outwit them
Can't you see all that
Really matters is you and me?
Rainbow streams
And apples are turning
Honesty
Loyalty returning
If friendship is magic,
Imagine what love can be.
Family an' sky above
The land Ah know and love
(Ah) always see them in your eyes
When we're together
Diamond in the rough
Ah can't rush fast enough
To stand by you, forever.
Fears and threats
Don't worry, defeat them
Lies, regrets
Forget those, outwit them
Can't you see all that
Really matters is you and me?
Rainbow streams
And apples are turning
Honesty
Loyalty returning
If friendship is magic,
Imagine what love can be.
Fears and threats
Don't worry, defeat them
Lies, regrets
Forget those, outwit them
Can't you see all that
Really matters is you and me?
Rainbow streams
And apples are turning
Honesty
Loyalty returning
If friendship is magic,
Imagine what love can be.
Diamond in the rough
Ah can't rush fast enough
To stand by you, forever.
Forever.
Foreve~r.