Princess Cadence needs our help
Her magic will not last fo-orever
I think we can do it
But we need to work together
We have to get this right
Yes, we have to make the-em see
We can save the crystal ponies
With their history-y
It says that they liked jousting
They flew a flag of many hues
Made sweets with crystal berries
They had a petting zoo with tiny ewes
Oh we have to get this right
Yes, we have to make the-em see
We can save the crystal ponies
With their history-y
There was a crystal flugelhorn
That everypony liked to-o play
And the crystal kingdom anthem
Can you learn it in a da-a-ay?
Oh we have to get this right
Yes,we have to make them see
We can save the crystal ponies
With their histo-o-ry