I've walked through all these halls before
I've been in and out of every door, oh-woah-oh
There's nothing in this scho-ol that I-I don't kno-o-o-ow
In every class my grade's the best
The highest score on every test
I think that means it's
Time for me to go
I know there's more that's out there
And I just haven't found it ye-et
Another "me" I haven't met
Everyone he-ere likes who I am
And it's not from a magic spell's command, oh-woah-oh
My friends look pa-ast the thi-ing I've do-one befo-ore
Still I miss those quests
The mythic creatures, magic tests
Highschool's great, sure
But who am I anymore?
It's not that I'm ungra-ateful
Or trying to succe-e-e-e-ed
But there's something le-eft sti-ill mi-issing
Something that I ne-ed
I know there's more tha-at's out there
Maybe folks that need my he-elp
I know there's more that's out there
Because I've seen it for myse-elf
There's only so much this town can offer
And I'm not saying that's so ba-ad
But I know there's more that's out the-ere
'Cause it's a life tha-at I once had
Beyond these rooms, beyond these wa-alls
So much to learn, I can't se-e-e it a-a-all
This town is home, this school is sa-a-a-a-a-afe
But how can I be home
And still feel out of pla-a-ace?
And I know there's more that's out there
Another world to explore
Am I wrong for wanti-ing mo-ore?
And I can't wait for it to-o happen
Though what it is I cannot sa-ay
I just know there's more that's out the-ere
And it's calling out my na-ame
And I'm searching for the answer
'Cause I feel I lost my wa-ay
I mean I know it's re-ally out there
But I'll find out someday
I'll find out someday