So we wanna stay
But can't find peace while sittin' still~
I guess we never will
We're on the way
We won't hurry back again~
The journey is the end
I love this very moment
We're speedin' up, not slowin'
We might know we can't win~
But we're dumb enough to try
We're going, there's no maybe
That's why they call us crazy
And we'll say if anybody asks us
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
We never need to know
Seekin' boundaries to break~
Let's forget the ones we've made
So we carry on~~
Don't let good things pass us by
The time we're gone will be the
Best time of our life
I love this very moment
We're speedin' up, not slowin'
We might know we can't win~
But we're dumb enough to try
We're going, there's no maybe
That's why they call us crazy
And we'll say if anybody asks us
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
So go tell 'em we won't stop
We know they can't change us
We're gonna go way off the map
To get ourselves back on the track
Go tell 'em we won't stop
We know they can't change us
No need to worry so much
We do whatever we want
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
Hey, where you gonna go?
We're off to see the world
We don't need to know
Ohh~~~ oh oh-~~oh-oh oh
Ohh oh-oh oh oh oh