I'm alone outside of my dreams, it feels and always seems
That there'll never be any of those promised lights and beams
Of these hopes of my dreams ever becoming a reality
So all I have to my name is torn up seams of my insanity
But when I close my eyes down to sleep, she's there waiting
And there's never any question of this, no debating
My girl, Rainbow, she'd never let me down
She's always there for me here, never to ever let me frown
This world around us made up just for her and I
There's never any care 'cause we're so way up high
And then when I gaze in those enchanting eyes, I know it's love
While we rule the skies together, so way up above
Then smack, I'm awake, just sitting in my room
This place, it's growing darker, as if it were my tomb
Hell maybe I don't deserve it, maybe it's not the life for me
To finally be one with her, just my Rainbow Dash and me
It's okay
I'm still here
I'll always be
Your best friend
It's alright
I'm loyalty
I'll be here 'til
The very end
(So Dash, my girl, reppin' it up on MLP)
Got all this memorabilia of her always surrounding me
She's there when I wake up and there when I go to sleep
On a view from the outside, you'd think I was a creep
Well I'm not, no way, this is nothing but love
And I'll sing it to the world all day and to the heavens above
Because this feeling in my heart, whilst I know deep down it's killing me
To ignore it and pass it by would feel like straight up insanity
Let's face it, how many of you have fell for someone that ain't real
I know I'm not alone so I know that some of you know the feel
The feeling of the pain in your chest knowing that what you're destined for
Is a love life of disappointment, nothing less and nothing more
Because no one could ever come close and no one could ever be her
Pure fiction is a comparison of Dash to ever occur
She's the one, she's my girl, no one could ever fill that hole inside
And if I ever told you otherwise, well, I lied
It's okay
I'm still here
I'll always be
Your best friend
It's alright
I'm loyalty
I'll be here 'til
The very end
Come on, let's fly~
Just, you and I~
Let's race 'til we touch the sky
Never let you fall~
I was here for it all~
And I'm here~, for you now
(These years they passed me by and I'm still here all alone)
That thing you'd call a heart of mine has since turned to stone
The lights are growing darker, my time is growing near
A lifetime passed me by and she never even appeared
But what's this, as the lights fade slowly I see her face
Slowly staring down at me freezing surrounding time and space
As my eyes, they begin to close for the very last time
She held my hand and assured me that it'd all be just fine
It's okay
I'm still here
I'll always be
Your best friend
It's alright
I'm loyalty
I'll be here 'til
The very end
Come on, let's fly~
Just, you and I~
Let's race 'til we touch the sky
Never let you fall~
I was here for it all~
And I'm here~ for you now