Yeaah hey, yeah!
Why don't you come on down
To Sweet Apple Acres
Got a whole family full
Of tasty treat makers
And to top it all off
We're apple pie bakers
Don't be fooled by
The Flim Flam fakers
We'll wet your whistle
With sweet Apple Cider
We wanna be your number one
Apple provider
We got everything
You could ever ask for
And then we even got
A little bit more than
All the apples you could ever want
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more
We got
All the apples you could ever want
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more~
It's a beautiful day
It's a beautiful day~
To keep the doctor away~
It's a beautiful day
It's a beautiful day~
To keep the doctor away
So I'm guessing by now
You know our name
And you know we ain't green
To this apple bucking game~
We're well deserving
Of all this apple fame
Everypony who visited
Smiled after they came
So whatcha waiting for?
Ain't you feelin' hungry yet?
There's no reason for you
Not to get the very best apples
At our happy little farm
So why don't you visit
And sample our charms with
All the apples you could ever want
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more more more more more
And I say
All the apples you could ever want
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more
Na na na na na na na
It's a beautiful day
It's a beautiful day~
Such a~ beautiful day
It's a beautiful day
To keep the doctor away~
To keep the doctor away
All the apples you could ever want
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And mo- mo-mo-more mo-mo-more more more more
At Sweet Apple -
Come on why don't you sing with us come on
All the apples you could ever want
And more~~
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more more more more more more more
At Sweet Apple Acres
Sweet Apple Acres singin'
All the apples you could ever want
And more
More more more more more
More, oh so much more
We got all the apples