Look here are three little ponies
Ready to sing for this crowd
Listen up 'cause here's our story
I'm gonna sing it very loud~~
When you're a younger po~ny
And your flank is very bare~
Feels like the sun will never come~
When your cutie mark's not there~
So the three of us will fight the fight
There is nothing that we fear~
We'll have to figure out what we'll do next
'Til our cutie marks are here~
We are the Cut~ie Mark Crusad~ers
On a quest to find out who we are~
And we'll never stop the jour~ney
Not until we have our cutie marks~~~~
They all say that you'll get your mark~
When the time is really right~
And you know just what you're supposed~ to do
And your talent comes to light~
But it's not as easy as it sounds~
And that waiting's hard to~ do~
So we test our talents eve~rywhere
Until our face~ turns blue~
We are the Cutie Mark Crusad~ers
On a quest to find out who we are~
And we will never stop the jour~ney
Not until we have our cutie marks~
We are the Cutie Mark Crusad~ers
On a quest to find out who we are~
And we will never stop the jour~ney
Not until we have our cutie marks~