It hasn't been nearly long enough
But I seem to be doing alright
I was today; I made my meals~~
Some days I can't be sure
That I'm out of my curse
That I can't go back again~
I secretly hope I won't~ if I~ try~
I see friendly faces from time to time~
Some days it's hard to even stand upright~
Some days are better
I even go outside
Maybe it's true that time heals all wounds
Maybe it works both ways
One fate for me and for the rest of us
Where consequence is a novel idea~
And it still feels like~
Another encore's a blink away~
There's something better ahead
And it's waiting for me
Wait for me
Along the streets that saw me die~
The rain is dancing under the sun~
It washed away~ all the blood and the death
And all that's left is all the time that is mine
I can wait~ for peace to catch up with my head
For the surprises up ahead~
For the decisions left to make
For all the love left to give~
And I know it's been~ rough
And I can't say enough
And neither can I pretend
That I understand
But if you put your trust in me
I'll show you how special your time can be
And even if I can't know what it's like
Because your life's not mine
I can show you that I care
For you I'm always there
You have someone to help you see things through
If you believe in me I'll be good to you too
I don't want to be lonely
I'll stay, I'll stay, with you
When I feel like I'm falling
When the nightmares get to me
I'll stay, I'll stay, with you
When I feel too tired to breathe~~~~
I'll stay, I'll stay, with you~~
'Cause in this time~line~
We've got a shot at a happy ending
The rest can wait until tomorrow
And it still feels~ like~
Another encore's a blink away~
But it can wait until tomorrow
I don't want to be lonely
I'll stay, I'll stay, with you~~
I'll stay, I'll stay
Oh I'll stay, I'll stay, with you~~
I'll stay, I'll stay, with you~~