I say good mor~ning to only~ me
Around books as far as the eye can~ see
Close the blinds, this is~ all I~ need
Just my mind and the ability to~ read
This was a~ life that I once~ led
Their words covered by the pages I read
"This is it, no way can I be more content"
Was what I thought right before I was sent
far away, wanting to be alone
To a place, I'd never thought I'd call home
Now, under warm blue~ ski-ies, or cold winter stars
I know that home is where my friends are
(Go!)
I say good mor~ning to my~ friends
My smile~ meets worried faces again
Don't you fret, I'm here to~ help all the way
Later on, you'll learn something new to~day
So much I would miss when I would re~flect
Life is full of things you'll never expect
Like when I thought friendship would not help me through
Now I know, that the opposite is true
Honesty, kindness, loyalty
Laughter~ and genero~sity
Met to make ma~gic, kindled by the spark
That's when I knew who~ my friends are
Now I know that when it feels like the end
When ni-ightmares feel like they aren't pretend
You're never alo-one and home isn't too far
Because home is where our~ friends~ are
There were times when I'd been pushed to the edge
And never wan~ted to go back again
Now I know that when it feels like the end
When ni-ightmares feel like they aren't pretend
You're never alo-one and home isn't too far
Because home is where our friends are
Home is where my~ friends are
Whoa-oh-oh
Home is where my~ frie-ends are
Home is where my frie-ends are
Home is where my friends are