I know that something isn't right
The moon is down, so where's the light?
Nine a.m., it should be bri-i-ight
Of all the things that could occur
I still don't know what there is to learn
Maybe my clock just overtu-u-urned
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
Seems we've got too much time to spend
Feels like this night will never end
I guess it just depends
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
My sister won't get out of bed
What's in her mind? What's in her head?
Seems she has other plans inste-e-ead
She's always liked to play pretend
But she should be up, it's almost ten
And if not, what the-e-en?
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
Seems we've got too much time to spend
Feels like this night will never end
I guess it just depends
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
The world should sleep~ today
Think I dese-erve a~ break
You'll see, this way it's better
We'll all just nap together
The night will last forever
THAT'S NOT FUNNY!
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
Seems we've got too much time to spend
Feels like this night will never end
I guess it just depends
Who knows when the sun will rise again?
Sun will rise again
Seems we've got too much time to spend
Too much time to spend
Feels like this night will never end
I guess it just depends
Who knows when the sun will rise again~~~~?
Who cares if the sun will rise again?
Wha--!? What meanest thou!?
Everypony cares, do they not?
*sigh* Oh, so be it...
They can't let a princess sleep in just once, it seems
Sleep in!? T'is ten thirty!
We are quite certain that thou hast already done a fine job of sleeping in!
Yes, I suppose...
Well, up with the sun then...
Really, sister...?
What?
It is thy calling
I should get a break, shouldn't I?
I mean, I can have you raise the sun for a while to make up for lost time, right?
What!? How canst thou say such a thing!?!?
*sigh* Fine, fine...
Perhaps I am acting a bit childish this morning...
Hah... At least it's still morning, you know
...Thou art too old for this.