Skies are dark
A lifeless sanguine abyss~
Keep hoping for a day
When you think you'll be missed~
So start your journey
A thousand times you've done this before
'Cause the life worth living
Isn't there anymore~
Memories~ that go through the eons' past
So many friends that you've just lost track
When all your friends have gone
The chapter ahead looks black
You can try your best but you can't turn back
Forever you trot down this lonely road
Companionless, upset and alone
The magic of friendship is a feeling unknown
Time and space don't mean a thing
And why should they
When you've lost the meaning they bring
These tales of~ old
Everlasting Life's the very curse you loathe~
When will you learn, Colgate
When things don't look up
That's not the time to stop
Or contemplate giving up~
So keep your head up high~
Don't~ ever look back
'Cause girl it's worth a try~
Keep your sights straight for~ward
So keep your head up high~
And soon you will see
There's more to life
Than this game~ of immortality
Than this game~
So keep your head up high~
Don't ever look back
'Cause girl it's worth a try~
Keep your sights straight for~ward
So keep your head up high~
And soon you will see
There's more to life
Than this game~ of immortality
Days turn to months to years
As the centuries pass
Every day feels longer than the rest you had
'Cause everywhere you go
You find pieces of your past
Bringing back the memories
You forgot you had
And every time you fall in love you know
Remind yourself that you gotta let go
Remember the moment you first felt alone
Time and space don't mean a thing
And why should they
When you've lost the meaning they bring
These tales of~ old
Everlasting Life's the very curse you loathe~
When will you learn, Colgate
When things don't look up
That's not the time to stop
Or contemplate giving up~
So keep your head up high~
Don't~ ever look back
'Cause girl it's worth a try~
Keep your sights straight for~ward
So keep your head up high~
And soon you will see
There's more to life
Than this game~ of immortality
Than this game~
So keep your head up high~
Don't ever look back
'Cause girl it's worth a try~
Keep your sights straight for~ward
So keep your head up high~
And soon you will see
There's more to life
Than this game~ of immortality
It's just not e~very day
You see a unicorn who forges her own way
Reminding you Colgate to tie up loose ends
What good is this love
If you'll just get hurt again?
What good is the morning
If the night never comes?