The world is a place
Where the villains wear a smile on their face
While they take what you can never replace
Stolen moments gone forever
Well, tables can turn
As my enemies will soon enough learn
I will strike a match and then watch them burn
On the pyre of obsession
You run ’till you drop
Chasing on advantage
You’ll pay any price
If you think it’s free
I will carry hell to your doorstep
I will make you pay
You will reap the hate you’ve sown
On my judgment da-a-ay
Sleepless nights and days of damnation
Soon and evermore
I will bring the Château D’If
Knocking upon your door
And love is a lie
Swearing that no matter what it won’t die
Disappearing like a star in the sky
In the hot light of morning
But what do I care?
There are women to be had everywhere
First there’s retribution I must prepare
Mighty vengeance is mine
I have a nice show
That will tempt you o-onward
And just when you’re sure
That the prize is yours
I’ll deliver hell to your doorstep
Dressed in rich facade
Then, I’ll burn you to the ground
Like an angry go-o-od
Once you’re in my shining cathedral
Heed the tolling be-ell
It’s the final sound you hear
As you descend to hell
Fall down on your knees
Fall down and let me hear you pray
’till I can hear you bargaining, scheming
Begging and screaming to me
I will carry hell to your doorstep
You will ru-ue the day
You will reap the hate you’ve sown
No matter how hard you pray
It’s a place without any mercy
Fashioned in cold blood
Stones of fear and stones of doubt
No forgiveness, no way out
Only justice
Then, ame-en