Hey Fluttershy listen to me
When I say you do not need any of this
There's no way that changing who you are
Could prove to us that you're assertive
They can't tell you how to act
When they don't know what you've been through
The only one who can decide to try and change this is you
You gotta keep it together
Little filly tell me now~
Why this angel never leaves the ground
She's not the type to follow through
This story's pages start and end with you
She's left out in the rain~
She's too shy to complain~
Just suck it up and let it go
How she feels inside we'll never…
One two three four
Her eyes glued to the floor
Five six seven eight~
Left feeling second rate
While her dreams pass her by~~
She'll wish she weren't so shy~~
Why can't I just make myself be less scared to try~
The things I wish I could do like soar into the sky~
The more I try to hide my doubts the~ more that I find~
Perhaps I should give up and just pretend I don't mind~
Little filly tell me now~
Why this angel never leaves the ground
She's not the type to follow through
This story's pages start and end with you
She's left out in the rain~
She's too shy to complain~
Just suck it up and let it go
How she feels inside we'll never know~~~~
Fluttershy don't let this end
No one's a perfect friend
This burden's not just yours to bear
You've gotta know your friends are always there
So come out of the rain~
We didn't mean to cause this pain~
Just grab your dreams and don't let go
They're yours to keep so hold them close