And when you're blue, she will send an "I love you"
And if you're not, X-O-X-O marks the spot
Like hidden treasure there's a letter unfettered
But how did she break into my house?
(oh no... did she climb in through my chimney??)
Drop a note right in her ask box
She can't speak but she's got sweet talk
Spreading her love letters through the town
Coat is pink and mane is stripey
Neck so long it's kinda frightening!
Spreading her love letters through the town
That Dissy Dee, she can be rather angry
She said, "Enough!" then she left in a big huff
Our poor Love Letters knit a sweater to get her
But Dissy uses it as a mop
(she pretends she doesn't like it, but she does)
She writes letters, decked in glitter
Hearts and stars and smiling stickers
Spreading her love letters through the town
She wears perfume like a sunscreen
Don't get trapped inside her love beams!
Spreading her love letters through the town
Valentine's gets her excited
Once a year she's in the limelight
Spreading her love letters through the town
Friendly gift or imposition?
Pupil hearts or eye condition?
Never can be too sure in this town
She sells gift cards as a business
Cheers you up with hugs and kisses
Barely turns a profit in this town
X- O- X- O, love is ipso facto
Love unconditionally
la la la la lalalala la la
la lalalalala la
la la la la lalalala la love
love unconditionally