Na na na
Na na ah ah ah
Two years since the start of this perfect story
I don't want it to e-end
The bonds we've made here, extraordinary
I could never surrend'
But my royal duties are dragging me away
I can't say I'll be~ home someday
Standing on the platform
See you one la-ast ti-ime
It's never been so hard for me to say goodbye~
I could never tell you in person
I'm not comi-ing home
No, I'm not comi-ing home
A darkness in the distance, a letter in fi-re
Bound with Celestia's seal
Signs of a struggle and I'm requi-ered
There's no time fo-or tears
I'm sorry, but I need to do this a-alone
You~ all have been the~ best I've~ kno-own
Standing on the platform
See you one la-ast ti-ime
It's never been so hard for me to say goodbye~
I could never tell you in~ person
I'm not comi-ing home
No I'm not coming home~~~
I'll never lie a-and I'll never gi-ive up
Laugh at the fear~ whe-en it rises up~
Kindness to all, I-'ll give all I can
You~ a-all have made me~ the be-est I~ ca-an
The best I~~ ca~~~~n
Ooh ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh
Standing on the platform
See you one la-ast ti-ime
It's never been so hard for me to say goodbye~
I could never tell you i-in person
I'm not comi-ing home
This Twilight is ending
The ni-ight has co-ome
The stars in the sky~ will carry me~ o-on
I could never tell you in person
I'm not comi-ing home
No, I'm not comi-ing home