Sometimes I think my head is filled with clouds
Kicking up a storm when I feel~ down
I can't put it in words~ like you can
Though it don't matter 'cause you understand
Sometimes I think that I am overwhelmed
By the vastness of my realm
Reaching up the sun splits in five
And somehow I know I'm alive
I'm alive
Woah I know~ I'm alive
Alive
Ripping up the sky, I leave my mark
And though I'm not quite there, I feel a part
Of something more than just~ me
And I know I'm meant to be
Leaving co~lours in my wake
Leaving co~lours in my wake~~~~~~
Sometimes I think the weight will make me fall
And yet I don't seem to care at all
Maybe 'cause I don't believe
That I obey the laws of gravity
I can fly
I~ can~ fly~~~~~~
And nothing can stop me~
Ripping up the sky, I leave my mark
And though I'm not quite there, I feel a part
Of something more than just~ me
And I know I'm meant to be
Ripping up the sky, I leave my mark
And though I'm not quite there, I feel a part
Of something more than just~ me
And I know I'm meant to be
Leaving co~lours in my wake
Leaving colours in my wake~~~