Someone tell me
Someone show me
Someone let me~ know
Who I'm supposed to be
If you know me
You can take~ me
To the~ deep blue sky
Over the big~ blue sea
I know
If you've seen
Where I'll be
In the future
Oh please
Tell me
I can dream
What you see there
I'm lost
Within
And behind
All the madness
But I found
I can shine
My light
In the darkness
Into the hour of night
Where my pain gets left~ behind
I won't give up the fight
I'll just say that I don't mind
What would you do to me
If I set the universe free
Come~ sit~ next to me
Behold your galaxy
I know
If you've seen
Where I'll be
In the future
Oh please
Tell me
I can dream
What you see there
I'm lost
Within
And behind
All the madness
But I found
I can shine
My light
In the darkness
I know
If you've seen
Where I'll be
In the future
Oh please
Tell me
I can dream
What you see there
I'm lost
Within
And behind
All the madness
But I found
I can shine
My light
In the darkness
Oooh~ ooh ooh ooh
Oooh
Oooh ooh ooh ooh
Ooh ooh~ ooh
Ooh ooh ooh ooh
Oooh~
Oooh