My breath stolen from such a night
Staying awake only for this sight
How would these stars look reflected in your eyes?
I could dream of soaring just as high
Then wake up with a-a hopeless sigh
A nightmare is where you're not by my-y side
Is it time to move on ye-et?
That's one more thing I could regre-et
They say few things are worth waiting forever more
You taught me that it's never true
Few things are worth waiting an eternity for
But I'll wait forever for you
…be by your side
…I could a-ide
Is it about time?
This hardship stays afloat
I won't promise no-o tears
Wake up in a ne-ew world,
I won't promise no-o fears
This hardship sta-ays aflo-at
I won't promise no-o tears
Wake up in a ne-ew world,
I won't promise no-o fears
Goodby-y-ye
They say few things are worth mo-urning forever more
But if there's someone worth waiting an eternity for
I’ll wait forever for you