Fate has been cruel and order unkind
How can I have sent you away?
The blame was my~ own
The punishment yours
The harmony's silent today
But~ into the stillness
I'll bring you a song
And I will your company keep
Till your tired eyes and my lullabies
Have carried you softly to sleep
Once did a pony who shone like the sun
Look out on her kingdom and sigh
She smiled and said
"Su-urely there is no pony
So lovely and so well
Beloved as I"
So great was her reign
So brilliant her glory
That long was the shadow she cast
Which fell dark upon
The young sister she loved
And grew only darker
As days and nights passed
Soon did that pony
Take notice that others
Did not give her sister her due
And neither had she loved her
As she~ deserved
She watched as her sister's
Unhappiness grew
But such is the way~ of the limelight
It sweetly takes hold of the mind~ of its host
And that foolish pony did nothing to stop
The destruction of one
Who had needed her most
Lullay moon princess
Goodnight sister mine
Rest now in moonlight's embrace
Bear up my lullaby
Winds of~ the earth
Through cloud~ and through sky
And through space
Carry the peace and the coolness of night
And carry my sor~row in kind~~
Luna you're loved
So much more~ than you know
May troubles be far~ from your mind~~
And forgive me for being so blind
The years now before us
Fearful and unknown
I never imagined
I'd face them on my~ own
May these thousand winters
Swiftly pass I pray~
I love you, I miss you
All these miles away
May all your dreams be sweet tonight
Safe upon your bed of moonlight
And know not of sadness, pain, or~ care
And when I~ dream
I'll fly away and meet you there
Sleep, sleep
Sleep~