Dawn breaks through the darkened skies
We lift our heads and dry our eyes
When day is done, we're doubly blessed
With starry sky and moon for rest
No longer bound to hopelessness
We dance as one with nature now
The sun and moon will show us how
Restless was the world we knew
And cheerless were~ the days
Of colors run together
In an endless mirror maze
But then two sisters brought us
Out of Discord's dark caprice
And gave us lights to guide us
Into harmony and peace
Day for rising; night for sleep
As in heaven, so below
Chaos banish; order keep
Ever may it thusly go
Memories are fading now
The fog begins to thin
The dreamer is awakened
Life can begin
And all that's past is preface
To the story of today
Now that harmony has come
And driven dissonance away
Day for rising; night for sleep
As in heaven, so below
Chaos banish; order keep
Ever may it thusly go
Perfect cosmic symmetry
Sisters of the moon and sun
Cornerstone of harmony
Never let it be undone
Day for rising
Night for sleep
Chaos banish
Order keep~