Giggle at guffaw at
Crack up at whoop it up with
Giggle at gotta stand up tall guffaw at to face your fears
Crack up at that they can't hurt you just whoop it up with the disappear
Crack up at that they can't hurt you just louder
Yay!
Wa ha ha!
Oh girls don't you see?
Giggle at the ghostly guffaw at the grossly
Crack up at the creepy whoop whoop it up whoop it up whoop it whoop it whoop it up
Crack up at the creepy whoop wh-wh-wh-wh-wh-whoop it up whoop it
Giggle at the ghostly guffaw at the grossly
Crack up at the creepy whoop whoop it up whoop it up whoop it whoop it whoop it up
Crack up at the creepy whoop
When I was a little filly and the sun was going down~
The darkness and the shadows they would always make me frown~
I'd hide under my pillow from what I thought I saw
But Granny Pie said that wasn't the way to deal with fears at all
Yay!
Jump jump jump jump
Louder!