Three minutes until I'm around the bend
Three minutes before sunrise in my head. Am I~
Too~ crazy to believe in a chance
To spend a while~ with you
And not care that you might forget
I wanna run, run, run to meet~ you in the mor~ning~
A blessing and a curse~ to know~ you, oh~, Mor~ning~
An an~gel in your eyes~, an en~gine not warming up~
To the i~dea that you and I can't be real~
I wish our story wouldn't reset~ itself
I wish our story wouldn't reset itself
'Cause there's no way I'm gonna sleep
With both~~ of us stuck here
With both~~ of us stuck here~
How many times~ can a moment~ dying hurt~
In spite of knowing I never stood to~ lose~ at all~
In spite of knowing I never stood to lose at all~
Though at a glance I'm real yet fleeting
Maybe I can revel in~ a promise
I will never have to live up to
So I run, run, run to meet~ you in the mor~ning~
A blessing and a curse~ to know~ you, oh~, Mor~ning~
An an~gel in your eyes~, an en~gine not warming up~
To the i~dea that you and I can't be real~
I wish our story wouldn't reset itself
I wish our story wouldn't reset~ itself
'Cause there's no way I'm gonna sleep
With both~~ of us stuck here~
With both~~ of us stuck here
Caught in our first conversation
Once~ again
Making a first impression
And expecting it to be the last~
Yet each time I'm disappointed~
Can I allow myself a moment~~~~
To pretend I could be important to~ you~
And look for~ward to when I wake up~
And just to run, run, run to hear you say~
Run, run, run to hear~ you say
"Good morning, an~gel"
"Good morning""Good morning"
"Good morning, angel~~~"
"Good morning, an~gel~~~"
"Good morning""Good morning"