There’s a place just north of town
If you listen you can hear the sound
They’re singing
“Ah aah ah, ah ah ah, ah aah ah”
Everybody acts the same
Nothing's different but the names
They’re singing
“Ah aah ah, ah ah ah, ah aah ah”
Basing themselves off the others
Part of them secretly wonders
What it would be like to finally break away~
I can’t be what they want me to be
Equality doesn’t mean that you’re free
I mean can’t you see you are nothing like me?
Conformity doesn’t mean that you’re free
I can’t be what they want me to be
Equality doesn’t mean that I'm free
Why can you not see you are nothing like me?
I just want to be free
Everything I can be
Society is hard to fight
When they decide what’s wrong or right
Singing
“Ah aah ah, ah ah ah, ah aah ah”
But you can make a different sound
And turn that small world upside down
They’re singing
“Ah aah ah, ah ah ah, ah aah ah”
Deep down we secretly wonder
Are we different from all the others?
Will we finally find ourselves and break away~?
I can’t be what they want me to be
Equality doesn’t mean that you’re free
I mean can’t you see you are nothing like me?
Conformity doesn’t mean that you’re free
You are afraid that you just can't fit in without it
What's the point of life if you can't truly enjoy it?
You are afraid that the world will never fully accept you
What's the point of hiding from the life that excites you?
Whoa oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh
Whoa oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh oh
Whoa oh, oh oh oh, oh oh oh, oh!
You are afraid that you just can't fit in without~ it
What's the point of life if you can't truly enjoy it?
You can make a different sound
And turn that small world upside down
You just gotta stand your ground
And fight to turn your life around
Don't follow this song
Just sing your own
Don't follow their song
When you can write your own
You can choose~ who to be~!
Just break away!
I can’t be what they want me to be
Equality doesn’t mean that you’re free
I mean can’t you see you are nothing like me?
Conformity doesn’t mean that you’re free
You are afraid that you just can't fit in without it
What's the point of life if you can't truly enjoy it?
You are afraid that the world will never fully accept you
What's the point of hiding from the life that excites you?
I just want to be free