There's no way to say this so-ong's
About someone else
Every time you're not in my a-arms
I start to lose my-yself
Someone ple-ease pass me my sha-ades
Don't let 'em see me down
You have taken over my da-ays,
So tonight I'm going out
Yet I'm feeling like,
There is no better place
Than right by your side
I had a little taste,
And I'll only spoil
The party anyway
'Cause all the girls are looking fine
But you're the only one on my mind
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
There's only me, There's only you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
When you were gone I think of you
All these places packed with people
But your face is all I-I see
And the music's way too lo-oud
But your voice won't let me-e be
So many pretty girls aro-ound,
They're just dressing to impress
But the thought of you alone has got me
Spun and I don't know what to say next
Feeling like
There is no better place
Than right by your side
I had a little taste,
And I'll only spoil
The party anyway
'Cause all the girls are looking fine
But you're the only one on my mind
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
There's only me, There's only you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
When you were gone I think of you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
There's only me, There's only you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
When you were gone I think of you
I pretend the ni-ight is so beautiful
Take a pho-oto wi-ith the bros
La da dee-ee, La da da doo
They won't see through my-y disguise
Right here behi-ind my eyes,
Replaying in my-y mind
La de da
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
There's only me, There's only you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
When you were gone I think of you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
There's only me, There's only you
La da dee-ee, La da dee doo
La da da me, La da da you
When you were gone I think of you.