A thousand years ago~
I was born of love~~
As the years wore on
I found it's not enough~
A father I barely knew~
A mother on her own~~
It didn't take~ me long~
To know I was a~lone~
Then I came~ of age~
My heart made~ of glass~~
I watched the po~nies play~
As centuries drift past~
I'll be their queen one day~
And their love will all be mine~~
Still the only way~
To heal my heart is time~
Power
Love
Dreams
Beauty
I'm just a loveless lovechild
Destiny calls me and I'll
Silently take my exile
Their love has made my heart vile
I'm just a loveless lovechild
Destiny calls me and I'll
Silently take my exile
Their love has made my heart vile~
Trapped in so~litude~
My heart knows no love~~
And as I watch the world turn
There's emptiness thereof~
For an eter~nity~
I'll wait in the end
On Eques~tria~
I'll have my re~venge~
Power
Love
Dreams
Beauty
What a lovely but absolutely ridiculous sentiment!
I'm just a loveless lovechild
Destiny called me and I'll
Silently take my exile
Their love has made my heart vile
I'm just a loveless lovechild
Destiny called me and I'll
Silently take my exile
Their love has made my heart vile~
I'm just a loveless lovechild
Destiny called me and I'll
Silently take my exile
Their love has made my heart vile
I'm just a loveless lovechild