There once was a pony who travelled the land
With a smile~ as bright as the sun
She went town to town as a one pony band
Sharing smiles with ev'ryone
She always sang loudly so all could hear
Her words that she sang~ with glee
And all the townponies they all~ did cheer
For this mare as pink as candy, oh…
This pink pony bard~, this bright young mare
Whose smiles~ and songs
turned towns upside down
Oh pink pony bard with your songs of joy
May there never be a day that you frown
This small pony sang
to her own heart's content
From the morning to the dark~ of night
She made ev'ryday feel like one big event
And she always was cheerful and bright
The townponies claim
that her songs were like spells
For that no bard has done that before
Her music just made all their emotions swell
She was one pony none could ignore, oh…
Pink pony bard~, one with such flare
Whose grand sing-alongs
went through all of town
Oh pink pony bard with your songs of joy
May there never be a day that you frown
When the pink pony left
there were tears to be shed
For there was no one bard~ like she
Her songs were so loved
and they all soon were spread
Across the land and through the sea
Her name though unknown by most ponykind
Her songs are still sung to this day
But if you look and you listen I'm
sure that you'll find
That pony still sings~ and plays, Oh…
Pink pony bard~, you bright young mare
Your smiles~ and songs
Turn towns upside down
Oh pink pony bard with your songs of joy
May there never be a day that you frown