Rivers ran dry, only chaos flew through it
Disco-ord's reign, nopony cared about it
No control, no constants, just like nature intended
But humility is rare and avarice corrupted
Twisted forms of obsession started
Heretical progressi-on
Against the world of eternity's successful invention
An alicorn's desire
Attempts to welcome harmony
Try to create order and to force responsibility
Overthrow the king under claims of so-called anarchy
Now all are forced to labor 'neath Celestia's tyranny
Control over the animals, control over the light
A ruler over all claims no evil, no blight
A world without fear, where we lock away the strife
An illusion to hide the empire ruling our li-i-ife
Gone are the days of the gifts of chocolate rain
An occasional variety now never to come again
Chaotic and uncontrolled is the refuge for the sane
But some have to fight, some think of it as pa-in
Now he's frozen always in stone
All of this world she rules alo-one
And every piece of land and ocean her power's overthrown
An alicorn's desire
Attempts to welcome harmony
Try to create order and to force responsibility
Overthrow the king under claims of so-called anarchy
Now all are forced to labor 'neath Celestia's tyranny
Control over the animals, control over the light
A ruler over all claims no evil, no blight
A world without fear, where we lock away the strife
An illusion to hide the empire ruling our li-i-ife
An alicorn's desire
Attempts to welcome harmony
Try to create order and to force responsibility
Overthrow the king under claims of so-called anarchy
Now all are forced to labor 'neath Celestia's tyranny
Control over the animals, control over the light
A ruler over all claims no evil, no blight
A world without fear, where we lock away the strife
An illusion to hide the empire ruling our li-i-ife