Last year I got coal for Christmas
I got put on Santa's naughty list (Again!)
Put a frog inside my teacher's desk - yeah, that was bad
But this year, I made sure I won't get missed
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Man!)
Didn't do my homework for a week (Okay, a month!)
But now I studied hard and nearly aced most every test
So this year's Christmas better be the best
Spent time with my old granny
Raking up her lawn
Took out the garbage every night (Ewww!)
Helped mama do the laundry
Cleaned up my room
Did every single chore in sight
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Aw, shucks!)
Every photo I just made a face
This year when we posed, I smiled sweetly like an angel
No more taking chances just in case
Last year I got coal for Christmas (Really?!)
Ate dessert before my dinner most of the time (Mmm! Cake!)
But this year I had vegetables with every single byte
I sure hope this year Santa gets it right (Come on, Santa!)
Spent time with my old granny
Raking up her lawn
Took out the garbage every night (She eats so much!)
Helped mama do the laundry
Cleaned up my room
Did every single chore in sight (Aw, gross!)
Last year I got coal for Christmas (For crying out loud!)
I go to bed and never brush my teeth
Now I bring my toothbrush each and every place I go
So that tree better got my presents underneath
This year, no more coal for Christmas (Yes!)
Santa took me off the naughty list (Woo-hoo!)
I might keep it up because it's really not so bad
So Santa, just bring presents
Please, dear Santa, no more lessons
Next year, Santa, just bring presents, I insist!
Seriously.