Looks like my secret's been revealed
I'm not a pony after all
But will they seek to disassemble me?
Back me up aga-i-inst the wall
I see how they look at me
Following my every move
Suspecting o-one da-ay I will attempt to
Crush them all beneath my hooves
Is this what I really am?
I can't begin to understand
Mechanized components fill my —
Systems crashing down
Bionic lenses i-in my eyes
The metallic circuits in my-y mi-ind
The gears that twist and turn inside
My memories corrupted over time
Overload in progress
Self-awareness protocols disengaged
All systems reaching critical levels
Meltdown in three, two
Why can't I forget my-y life befo-ore?
Am I machine and nothing mo-o-ore?
Systems crashing down
Set phasers to hug