I wish that Starlight was here to see
How strong friendships can be
When we trust each others
And work together
You've all taught me so much!
Friendship used to make me so queasy, queasy
But you made it all so easy, ea-sy
Now I don't have to say what I'm thinking
You already know without even blinking
You girls are the apple of my~ eye
The race that doesn't end in a tie
You are the funnel cake at my fair
The warm hug of a fuzzy bear
Best friends until the end of time~
We'll have each other's backs
And let our true selves shine~
And that's because everything we need
Is all~ right here
When we're with our team
Starlight!
A spark of magic could be
Very helpful right about now!
I can't…!
I simply can't imagine there'd be a day~
Where I wouldn't want to be walking your way
Whatever new problems there may be, may be
Our friendship is always the door with the key
You are the jewels in my friendship crown
The sparks that make my world go~ 'round
We bring the best out, that's our goal
There's no telling how far we'll go
Best friends until the end of time~
We'll have each other's backs
And let our true selves shine~
And that's because everything we need
Is all~ right here
When we're with our team!
That was lovely but
You know the game isn't over until you turn that key?