People say real fashion
Was a fossil dead~ and gone
Saw your work and it’s safe~ to say that you’ve proved~ them~ wrong
Stitching fit for a prin~cess gown
Suits that turn the world upside~ down~
Don’t suppose you’ve had customers with my spi~ky crown?
You~ started working, and when you were~ through~~
Now~ I’m just~ one more boy
In your mile~ long crush queue
Hey~ Hey Ms. Rarity I know you
Don’t exactly have time for~ me
But if the fate’s let us make contact
I’ll be your A- List date just like all of your contracts~
Maybe hold your hoof after dinner
You’ll smile~ back at me and then,
Dilettantes would all talk
The crème de la crème would all tell~~
That I’m out with Ms. Rarity Belle
Someday, if you’re in town
We’ll hit up, Flim and Flam’s fairgrounds~
The days of summer would fly~ by as we just bummed around
Laughing at stupid inside jokes
Maybe walking too slow or too close
And if your sister sees us there under Star~swirl’s Oaks
She’ll say~ "My~ sister thinks she’s parked your tail and~ locked it,
Dontcha think about~ running off, with her heart in your pocket~"
Hey~ hey there Sweetie Belle, I promise
When we’re out I’m nervous as hell
She’s so down to earth and charming
Does she know she’s world famous? It’s kinda disarming~
I’ll stay with her as long as I can but, compared~ to Manehattan’s screen gems
She’s more likely to be getting tired~ of me, but till then~~
I’m still cra~zy ‘bout Rarity
Her and me
Just fit you see
When she lets me in to the deep blue sea
Of her eyes, it’s paralyzing
I physically can’t leave her
And at the risk of being called a dreamer…
Hey~ Hey Ms. Rarity you know you’ll
Never have to perform for~ me, if you’re feeling beat and tired
From a long day of stitching, you’ll still be admired~
Even if it’s just pizza and Runway I’ll tell all my friends go ahead
Mah gals tired, well you’ll say you’re fine, but my jobs for tonight are set
And that’s chef and duvet. Don’t care if my boys give me hell
I’m hanging in with my Ra~rity Belle~~