So~me nights I wa~ke up and I
See the mo~on and I see
Swir~ling galaxies and I
Think of you
Somewhere up there's a frie~~~~nd
A friend I lost long ago~~~~~~~
Sometimes I wonder if you see me too~~~~
When I raise the sun up for you
When I raise the su~n up for you~
Lo~ng have I waited
For your moon to shine
And now~ you're ba~ck with me~
After all this ti~~me
Where do we go now from he~~~~re?
It's been a thousand ye~~~~~~ars
Can we go back to what it used to be~?
When you raised the moon up for me~~?
When you raised the moon up for me~~~
O~h Sister, I've been so ti~red
Of singing sad so~ngs
And of... being alone
But now you
Have to choose to recei~~~~~~~ve
The friendship before you I lea~ve
I'll raise the sun up for you
You raise the moon up for me
If you raise the moon up for me