So let me be honest
You really can’t stay here, no
Excuse my impatience, but
I really just don’t know you that well
Why did you choose my house
Now of all times?
I’m trying to do my chores
So just let me live my life
Where am I gonna do my clothes?
I promise that my eyes are closed
Detergent is so damn expensive
Weak excuses are extensive
Really need to do my laundry
Running low on time, I’m sorry
I really wish she’d leave me be
But Celestia’s in my washing machine
Just another quick spin cycle
Another rinse, then you have to go
Sorry that I’m rushing you
I’m sorry that I’m rushing you~
Can’t you please move to the shower?
A rude gesture’s how you answer
Sorry that I’m rushing you
I’ve got some things I need to do
Where am I gonna do my clothes?
I promise that my eyes are closed
Detergent is so damn expensive
Weak excuses are extensive
Really need to do my laundry
Running low on time, I’m sorry
I really wish she’d leave me be
But Celestia’s in my washing machine