It's time you learned a lesson
It's time that you understand~
Don't ever count on anybody else
In this or any other land
I once hoped for friendship
To find a place among my kind~
But those were the childish wishes
Of someone who was blind
Open up your-
Ah!
A~h!
A~e~a~e~a~h!
A~~~~~~~~h!
Oh!
A~~h!
See the world~ from where I stand
Me, among the mighty
You, caged at my command~
Open up your eyes~~
Give up your sweet fantasy land
It's time to grow up and get wise
Come now little one
Open up your eyes
We all start out the same
With simple naive trust
Shielded from the many ways
That life's not fair or just
But then there comes a moment
A simple truth that you must face
If you depend~ on others
You'll never find~ your place
And as you take that first step
Upon a path that's all your own
You see it all so clear~ly
The best way to survive is all alone
Open up your eyes~~
See the world~ from where I stand
Me, among the mighty
You, caged at my command~
Open up your eyes~~
And behold the faded light
It's time to grow up and get wise
Come now, little one
Open up your eyes