This world that we call home
I rule upon my throne
To save the young and old
A~nd ye~t, my heart grows co~ld
And all this sorcery i~s go~ne
Into the futu~re I long
I lo~ng to see~ wha~t I~ might know
And beat what will not sho~w
A thousand years
A thousand cri~es
To save their world
Before they die~
A thousand lives
A thousand times
To bring them life
And make this ri~ght
When everything i~s fa~lling
And we don't kno~w where to sta~rt
This sovereign divination
Will open up your he~~arts
But I kno~~~~w
You are with me
So goodbye~
I said goodbye~
I promise I'm not dead inside
I know I seem to rule with iron pride
This magic fi~lls me
With the burden to~ fight
Gaze upon this
A~rdent twi~lit sky~
A thousand years
A thousand cri~es
To save their world
Before they die~
A thousand lives
A thousand times
To bring them life
And make this ri~ght
When everything i~s fa~lling
And we don't kno~w where to sta~rt
This sovereign divination
Will open up your he~~arts
But I kno~~~~w
You are with me
You don't know how hard I cry
When all I want is to say goodbye