Is it worth a shot
Should I really change my life forever
And lose the world that I kno-ow?
Is it true or not
Can we really se-e it a-all together
Oh, I'm not ready to go-o
Some called it lu-u-uck
But is it re-ally better knowing
I'd almost rather have never met you
I'm lightning-stru-u-uck
Inside I know that I'll be going
I know I never could just forget you
You're taking me to another place
And I never even said my goodbyes
My world expands to a universe
And the light of stars reflects in my eyes
You're taking me to a different time
Where my doubts and fears are not to be found
My world expands and I fe-el alive
As my body and my soul leave the ground
Oh uh woah
A bolt in the blu-u-e
An infinite displa-ay of splendour
Like a door to worlds in my he-e-ad
Then there was yo-o-u
The guardian who bade me "Enter"
The only word that you sa-id
You're not as you se-em
And now I'm holding on for o-ur ascension
It's almost like I've do-one this befo-o-o-o-o-o-o-ore
In all my dre-ams
I never had the sli-ightest glimpse of heaven
But in your eyes I see that, and mo-ore
You're taking me to another place
And I never even said my goodbyes
My world expands to a universe
And the light of stars reflects in my eyes
You're taking me to a different time
Where my doubts and fears are not to be found
My wo-orld expands and I fe-el alive
As my body and my soul leave the ground
Oh uh woah oh
Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da Da
Da Da Da Da
Da Da-a-a Da Da
You're taking me across ti-ime and space
To realities my mind couldn't see
My wo-orld expands to a universe
Though I'll never know what you see in me
You're taking me to another place
And I never even said my goodbyes
My wo-orld expands to a universe
And the light of stars reflects in my-y eyes
You're taking me to a different time
Where my doubts and fears are not to be found
My wo-orld expands and I fe-el alive
As my body and my soul leave the ground
Oh uh woah