I saw you stand~ing there
Without~ an explanation
You say that you don't care
About my~ disposition
Well I've got news for you~~
I'm taking back what's mine~~
Just one thing left to do~~
I think~ that it~ is
Time to face the rain again as
I stand all a~lone
No need to face the pain again
I'll make it on my own~~~
I start all the fires tonight
As you wander in aimless flight
You're convinced that you were right
While I~ ignite the skies tonight
'Cause I'm back in the saddle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't matter
It's getting old
You're sad 'cause
I'm back in the sad~dle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't count
Despite what you're told
The task is now at hand
To stand up and defy you
You're doing all you can
To make sure I don't get through
Well I've got news for you~~
You're running out of time~~
Just one thing left to do~~
I think~ that it~ is time
To face the hate again
As I tear~ down your throne
If you try to lead the way
I'll have to go alone~~~
I start all the fires tonight
As you wander in aimless flight
You're convinced that you were right
While I~ ignite the skies tonight
'Cause I'm back in the saddle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't matter
It's getting old
You're sad 'cause
I'm back in the sad~dle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't count
Despite what you're told
I start all the fires tonight
As you wander in aimless flight
You're convinced that you were right
While I~ ignite the skies tonight
'Cause I'm back in the saddle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't matter
It's getting old
You're sad 'cause
I'm back in the sad~dle
Back in control
You're mad 'cause
Your love doesn't count
Despite what you're told