The race has begun
We must run fast
Jump over the mud
Hav ing a good time
Where's Applejack?
She fell in the mud
Are you okay?
We can still win this
Jump in a bucket
That looked like it hurts
I know what pain is
It's great to be alive
But when I am feeling weak
and when I am feel ing down
She is there to lift me up
Lift me up over this bo-ox
Yes, I love my sister Applejack
Bum bum bum
Eating some pie
No time to chew
Pushing some hay
No time to lose
Pushing this hay really far
Pushing hay is really hard!
Running in a circle yes
Having so much fun hooray
Got to chuck some grapes?
Throw them with your face!
Sister toss and
squish and squash and
Mak ing tacky jelly
Put it on your head
We're gonna win the race
Because I am a good racer
I am running oh so fast
Fun levels are to the max
Applejack flies through the air
Apples fall without a care
Apples are not meant to fly!
No apples get left behind
When small things get kicked around
They just might destroy the town
When I'm feeling broken down
She has always got my back
Life is worth protecting now
Place it in that giant ha-at
Yes I love my sister Applejack
Now we're racing towards the finish line
Nothing matters once you die but we're along for the ride
And you sacrifice some meaning just to have the words rhyme
In the end it all comes down to just how far we can slide!