In the ra-ain or in~ the dark
I will ne~ver lose the spark
That keeps me going when I'm lo-o-o-ow
Everybody asks me how
I get by when I get down
It's easy to get through the darkness once you know
I can show you the way
To have a bri-ighter day
It only takes one smile
To make it all worthwhile
We can conquer our fears
Laugh until happy tears
Fall to~ the gro~ound
If you're lost and afraid
All the good times will fa-ade
Just follow~ the so~ound
Follow~ the sound of laughter~
Pulling through, standing tall
We can rise above it all
With our frie-ends by our side
Face the danger with a grin
'Cause there's no battle we can't win
We will never fall
Never divide
We will find a way
To face ano~ther day
It only takes one smi~~le
To make it all worthwhile
We can conquer our fears
Laugh until happy tears
Fall to~ the gro~ound
If you're lost and afraid
All the good times will fa-ade
Just follow~ the so~ound
Follow~ the sound of laughter~
Of laughte-e-er
When you look inside you'll find the answer
Coming from the heart you can't go wrong
Do it with a smile and you'll find laughter
Find your melody~ and sing
Yeah~!
We can conquer our fears
Laugh until happy tears
Fall to~ the gro~ound
If you're lost and afraid
All the good times will fa-ade
Just follow~ the so~ound
We can conquer our fears
Laugh until happy te-ears
Fall to~ the gro-o-ound
With the friends that we've made
I know we'll never stra-ay
If we follow~ the so~ound
Follow~ the sound of laughter