I wanna be a mobile supercompu~ter
A vision of the future
Begin the cyber revolution
Mechanical fusion
The perfect evolution
With syste~matic ha~rmony
I will run o~nto ete~rnity
And although this metal's pa~rt of me
I shall not lo~se my sanity
Shatter the flesh and reinforce the bo~ne
Embrace this carbon mesh this power's all my o~wn
These simple parts of mine are intercha~ngea~ble
Unlimited connections when you're di~gi~tal
Becoming one with wires is sensa~tio~nal
Go out with the old and in~ with the new
Stomp the ground
Resonating sound surro~unds me
A power best described as godly
At life's intersection
Reaching for perfection
Requiring no~ mo~re correction
Rip away the obsolete
Clean format, update complete
No~ more emotions
Such a novelty
The future key
That would be
So clear to me
Shatter the flesh and reinforce the bo~ne
Embrace this carbon mesh this power's all my o~wn
These simple parts of mine are intercha~ngea~ble
Unlimited connections when you're di~gi~tal
Becoming one with wires is sensa~tio~nal
Go out with the old and in~ with the new
My hunger for perfection is insa~tia~ble
A prototype that's fully opera~tio~nal
This armoured alloy shell is unbrea~ka~ble
My existence is ir~replaceable
Shatter the flesh and reinforce the bone
Embrace this carbon mesh this power's all my o~wn
These simple parts of mine are intercha~ngea~ble
Unlimited connections when you're di~gi~tal
Becoming one with wires is sensa~tio~nal
Go out with the old and in~ with the new
My hunger for perfection is insa~tia~ble
A prototype that's fully opera~tio~nal
This armoured alloy shell is unbrea~ka~ble
My existence is ir~replaceable