You reach your right hoof in
You reach your right hoof out
And you shake it all about
You do the Pony Pokey
Meeting lots of folks with clout
That's what I'm talking about
You step your left hoof in
You pull it right back out
But you better help him out
You do the Pony Pokey
But you'd find a diff'rent route
That's what it's all about
You kick your back left in
You pull your back left out
You reach your back left in
Just be brave and have no doubt
You do the Pony Pokey
Feeling like you're gonna pout
That's what I'm singing about
You tilt your head in
You tilt your head out
Then you shake it all about
You do the Pony Pokey
Even though your date's a lout
You're better off without
You stomp your whole self in
You stomp your whole self out
And you stomp yourself about
You do the Pony Pokey
And you give a little shout
COME OUT!
That's what I'm talking about
You do the Pony Pokey
And that's what it's all about
YEAH!