As I lose myself to time
I can't help but stop and feel
How the time has gone since I've seen you go on
Sorrow comes through for the years that passed
Each year that I spent seeing you~~
It was so self-satisfying to tell~ my love to you
On the day we met, but it's faded away
Each birth~day of yours that goes by each year
I honor with candles and tears~~
I believe in you
I believe in your mind
Though it's been a whole year since I've seen you
I stay here for you
Though the time prowls on~
Oh, I wait for you
I would like to see you come back
But I just can't bring myself
To come to the door and see you in her arms
Those eyes of hers glow with the kind~ one light
And draw me away from your room~~
I believe in you
I believe in your mind
With the knowledge you moved on without me
You've moved on with life
And your memory stay~
Oh, without me then~
All the memories come
And they rush to me now
Our laughs and our dreams and our hopes long gone
There's only one new memory in my mind~
The thought of seeing you in tears
Oh oh oh
You said, "I don't wanna be with you anymore"
I believe in you
I believe in your mind
With the knowledge you moved on without me
You've moved on with life
And your memory stay~
Oh~, (without me then)
I believe in you
I believe in your mind
Though it's been a whole year since I've seen you
I stay here for you
Though the time prowls on~
I wait for you~
In all my memories
Oh, I believe in you~~