Well my girl ain't nothing but a butterfly
With soft and delicate wings~
And every now and then she will flutter by
And turn the jokers into kings~
My world ain't nothing, is she gonna cry?
Don't act like it's for separate things
Maybe you should wake up to the truth
And not just the beauty she brings
She floats through the air like a lullaby
Like a cradle in full swing~
The weather shines through and i'ts cold inside
And she turns winter into spring
So for deep and loving for all the while
Never let me have its sting
Maybe you should wake up to the truth
Not just the beauty that she~ brings
Well maybe all I really need is just a little bit more time
To find my way back home, to the one I love, my Fluttershy
maybe all I really need is just a little bit more time
To find my way back home, to the one I love
To the one I love, my Fluttershy~~
Ah~~
Protecting how she feels behind her smile
She knows I do just the same~
Together we pretend~ that it's worth our while
And in the end we share the blame~
She thinks I don't feel and I'm full of guile
Wants to make me bear the shame
I would go so far as put my love on trial
If she would kiss me once again
If she would kiss~ me again
Well maybe all I really need is just a little bit more time~
To find my way back home, to the one I love, my Fluttershy
maybe all I really need is just a little bit more time~
To find my way back home, to the one I love
To the one I love, my Fluttershy~~
Take my hand, I'll take you anywhere
So trust in me, I've got so much to share with you
I've got so much to share~ with you~
maybe all I really need is just a little bit more time~
To find my way back home, to the one I love, my Fluttershy
To find my way back home, to the one I love
To the one I love, my Fluttershy~~
Just a little bit, Just a little bit
...