Here I am again
I'm standing alone and wondering when
I'm trying to work up the nerve
To tell you how I feel
Colorful streamers and lights
Every month it's the same, It just doesn't feel right
The emptiness around me
Reminds me how my heart must feel
I just want to make you open your eyes
And you might be in for a pleasant surprise~
I want you to stay here by my side
I'm a party of one, and I need you tonight~
I just want to make you finally see
That not being with you is torturing me
But behind these eyes and the tears I have shed
I want you to know that the party hasn't ended
It might just be the time
Everypony has left, but you've stayed behind
I'm trying to work up the nerve
To tell you how I feel
It's finally too much
Mere words aren't enough, so our lips they touch
You flee from my embrace
I know this dream could not be real
I just want to make you open your eyes
And you might be in for a pleasant surprise~
I want you to stay here by my side
I'm a party of one, and I need you tonight~
I just want to make you finally see
That not being with you is torturing me
But behind these eyes and the tears I have shed
I want you to know that the party hasn't ended
Nightmares creeping in from all sides
Painful memories locked inside
I'll be right there to break you free
You'll finally see my loyalty
Visions come most cruel and dark
But I know friendship is the spark
My laughter like a chorus rings
And then you'll hear me start to sing
"Giggle at the Ghostie"~~~
I just want to make you open your eyes
And you might be in for a pleasant surprise~
I want you to stay here by my side
I'm a party of one, and I need you tonight~
I just want to make you finally see
That not being with you is torturing me
But behind these eyes and the tears I have shed
I want you to know that the party hasn't ended
I just want to make you open your eyes
And you might be in for a pleasant surprise~
I want you to stay here by my side
I'm a party of one, and I need you tonight~
I just want to make you finally see
That not being with you is torturing me
But behind these eyes and the tears I have shed
I want you to know that the party hasn't ended