I can feel the a-ambience in life
Lying in the backgrou~nd in silence and igno-orance
Miracles are found i-in the ballrooms of brave-ery
Courage is a dange-erous dance
Woah oh
Fear is my-y right to-o say "no" woah
Peace is my-y reason to gro-ow
Still I~ re-emain here alo-one
When will I fee~l li-ike I'm home?
Belonging is a stranger to-o me
Caught up in a snowstorm of wandering mise-ery
Staring through a mirro-or, reflections of life a-are seen
Yet I feel an abse-ence in me
Woah oh oh woah
Fear is my-y right to-o say "no" woah
Peace is my-y reason to gro-ow
Still I~ re-emain here alo-one
When will I fee~l li-ike I'm home?
Oh ooh oh
How long wi-ill I run from my~self
How long wi-ill I run from myself
Woah woah
Fear is my-y right to~ say "no" woah
Peace is my-y reason to gro-ow
Still I~ re-emain here alo-one
When will I fee~l li-ike I'm ho-ome?
Desti-iny frightens my soul, woah
And I ne~ver wante-ed to kno-ow
What lie~s ahead on this roa~d
When will I fee-eel li-ike I'm home?