It worked, it worked!
Oh, I'm so happy
You're back to normal!
Now we need your help!
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend i-in need
A friend wi-ill be there
To help the-em see
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend i-in need
To see the light
that shines from a true, tru-ue friend.
Um, hello!
Friend trapped inside, remember?
Rarity needs yo-ur help
She's trying ha-ard
Doing what she-e can
Would you try,
Just give it a-a chance
You might fi-ind
That you'll start to understand
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend i-in need
A friend will be there
To help you see
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend i-in need
To see the light
that shines from a true, tru-ue friend
Uh, what just happened?
There's no time to explain,
But we need your help
Applejack's trying to make dresses!
Say no more!
Applejack needs your help.
She's trying hard
Doing what she can
Would you try,
Just give it a chance
You might find
That you'll start to understand
A true, true friend
Helps a friend i-in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend i-in need
To see the light
That shines from a true, true friend
*gasp* Oh my, what a terrible dream I had
Or, maybe I'm still having it
Rarity, Pinkie Pie is about
To lose the apple farm
We need Applejack's help!
Lose the apple farm?
Well we can't let that happen,
Now can we?
Pinkie Pie is in trouble
We need to get there
By he-er side
We can try to do
What we can now
For together we can be her guide
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see.
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend in need
To see the light
that shines from a true, true friend
Yee-haw! Now that's more like it!
What's next?
The townspeople are furious
We need the old Pinkie Pie back
I'm on it, I know just the thing
The townspeople need you,
They've been sad for a while
They march around, faces frown
And never seem to smile
And if you feel like helping,
We'd appreciate a lot!
If you get up there and spread some cheer
From here to Canterlot!
Come on ponies,
I wanna see you smile!
Pinkie!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see.
A true, true frie-nd
Helps a friend in need
To see the light
That shines
From a true, true friend!