Ooh
Ooh~
You open your eyes
All you see is white
Push back your fright
Don't worry Twilight
The magic inside~~
Brings you to the light~~
The element you bear
Though you're unaware
Twi~light
Oh Twilight~~~~
Raw power that you hold
Keep it under control
Student of Celestia
Savior of Equestria
A few years have passed
Fashioned into an outcast
Fortress of your own design
The walls are booklined
Until you turn the pag~es
Lost to all but some sages
A myth that seem too real
You're not~ sure what to feel
You will face a nightmare
Everfree creatures don't care
Out of the dark~ness
You'll save a princess
The sisters reunited
You're soul is ignited
The power of magic fueled
By~~ your friendship~
And another year's~ gone
The six of you are strong~
Cotton candy clouds rain
Liquid choc'late in bounds~
Chaos caused by Discord~
In the maze he took a sword cut the
Six ties that bind Twilight
Even your color faded in kind
Letter from~ your mentor
Memories come in from before~
Leading on you turned him to stone
The six friends not one alone~
Raw power that you hold~
Keep it under control
Student of Celestia
Savior of Equestria~
Twilight Twilight