Save me, I'm drowning so deep in the darkness
I'm waiting for your touch to stop this
There's smoke blinding us with goodbyes
A-a-and I
Keep hope
'Cause this feeling's different and I know
I've staggered so long that it can't go
Alleviate me, I'll be fine
I-i-in time
Please remember that I miss you
Young and reckless, what did we do?
Broken promise, gone forever
Maybe one day we'll get better
Right by your side, that's where I'll be
In a heart beat if you ask me
Let's stay strangers like we're meant to
Oh, I wonder if you miss me too
Find me, I'm waiting right here whe-re you left me
Still shredded and bruised, bu-ut I'm bre-eathing
Be brave for me, i-ignore their e-yes
Ju-u-ust try
We're dancers, and I've picked petals looki-ng fo-r answers
And I've received these edges from cha-nces
Indelible, but I-'ll be fi-i-i-ine
I-i-in time
Please remember that I miss you
Not ca-ri-ng is so hard to-o do
Everything we loved toge-ether
It's not the same without you there
Feels like you were just beside me
How did ti-me go by so quickly?
Now we're stra-ngers, but I miss you
Oh, I wonder if yo-ou miss me too-o-o
Woah-oh-ohoh-ohoh
Woah-oh-oh
Woah-oh-ohoh
Please remember, don't forget me
Please remember, I still think of you and I-I-I
I'll be leaving this heart empty
Tell me what does this all mean?
Burn our bridges, are you still there?
Are you even still there?
All these endless circles do nothing
These circles do nothing
And remember, I've been wa-aiting
And I don't know why I can't just let you go
Ever since this started aching
Can we go back? Can we start again?
Now we're strangers, but I need you
Because I need you
Oh, I wonder if you need me too