Let's go
Hey Daring
Whatcha gonna do
Daring
Hey Daring
Whatcha gonna do
Daring
Please oh please will you let me follow you
Talk to me Daring
Don't you leave me blue
Daring
Talk to me Daring
Don't you leave me blue
Daring
Don't you know I love you
Daring Do
I wanna be loyal like I'm supposed to be
So I don't really mind the way you're driving me crazy
I'll never leave you hangin' even if you mistreat me
Cause I only care about you
Look at me Daring
I'm as daring as you
Daring
Can't you see Daring
I'm as daring as you
Daring
Please oh please take me with you
Daring Do
I have been an element of harmony
And I was one of those who stopped the world going crazy
So take another look before you say you don't need me
Cause I only care about you~
Stay with me Daring
Tell me what to do
Daring
Stay with me Daring
Tell me what to do
Daring
I'd be glad to do anything
For you
Can't you see that you and me will be best friends
Cause I know all your stories from beginning to end
Every single chapter that has ever been penned
Cause I only care about you
Hey Daring
Whatcha gonna do
Daring
Hey whatcha gonna do
Please oh please let me be your friend
Daring Do