Wish I could find~ a space in my head without the memories
Without you guarding my dreams they tend to get the best of me~~
Starting to think that I made the wrong decision
Could've given you the time~ of day and just listened
I'm doing my best to try to block out the screams
But I think you know~ where they find me
My rays of gold~ were never meant to shine sil~ver
I know I gave~ you too much space and time
Being chained in the cold~ all this time must have damn near killed ya
There's such a thing as too much space and time
The dark of the night has helped me to see
There's a half of the day that was never ever meant for me~~
Now half the world lay wide awake
Because I can't be there to watch over them and that's my mistake
I'm doing my best to try to block out the screams
But I think you know~ where they find me
My rays of gold~ were never meant to shine sil~ver
I know I gave~ you too much space and time
Being chained in the cold~ all this time must have damn near killed ya
There's such a thing as too much space and time
My rays of gold~ were never meant to shine sil~ver
I know I gave~ you too much space and time
Being chained in the cold~ all this time must have damn near killed ya
There's such a thing as too much space and time