I
I fall~ to my~ knees
And your sun~
Broke through~ me
I never knew I'd been asleep
You
You parted the clouds~
Over me
And I'm baptised~
In your~ ho~ly~ light
And you brought me back to life
In a prison of ice I lived my life in~ pain
Just waiting to~ be un~~chained
Oh I owe you everything
Since that~ day I~ can't control~
What you do~ to me
It feels~ like
I'm losing my~ mind
Beneath your sun
I'm burning alive in your light~
And tonight I'll breath
In your red fire~~
Into the flame
A~gain and again and your light~
Will split the night and
Rain down
Red fire~~
I feel it
It burns~
Beneath my skin
The hunger demands to feed
From purity to sin
The want~ turns into a need~~
It wa~shes over me~
I become
I learn
I'm a slave to the burn
It brings me to my knees~
Oh I beg~ you~ please
It comes in waves
It cuts through the haze
And I feel the walls
Fall down around me
Crushed and lost
But who knows the cost
I'd sell my soul
To set my world on fire~~
Beneath your sun
I'm burning alive in your light~
And tonight I'll breath
In your red fire~~
Into the flame
Again and again and your light~
Will split the night and
Rain down
Red fire~~
I run and I run
But I just can't escape
The sight~~
Of endless light
I need your
Red fire~~
We shed these chains
And forget our names
As the light~~~
Consumes the night and
Bleeds out
Red fire~~