Prancing down the street, strutting my stuff
My daddy buys me things, it's never enough
I pretend I don't know that they stare
Nobody gets me and I really don't ca-a-a-re
It should be against the law for me to look this good
I'm teenage royalty, and man I'm so misunderstood
I think I got some friends who really give a f---
I'm never out of money, so I'm never out of luck
Don't hate me 'cuz I'm beautiful
Don't hate me 'cuz I speak tru-e
Don't hate me 'cuz I'm beautiful, no-o-o
Hate me 'cuz I'm better than yo-u
Everybody's got a problem, if you know what I mean
If you ask me I think they look a little gre-en
I'm well awa-are that nothing is free
But, my daddy worked for Everything and gave it all to me-e-eYeah!
It should be against the law for me to look this good
I'm teenage royalty, and man I'm so misunderstood
I think I've got some friends, I don't give a f---
I'm never out of money, so I'm never out of luck
Don't hate me 'cuz I'm beautiful
Don't hate me 'cuz I speak tru-e
Don't hate me 'cuz I'm beautiful, no-o-o
Hate me 'cuz I'm better than yo-u
Well I said I'm better than yo-u
I said I'm better than yo-u
I said I'm better than yo-ou-u
I said I'm better than you
It's not my fa-ault that I'm just a princess
I deserve nothing but the be-est
I won't apologize for getting what I want
You're the glitz, you're the glamor when you're the debutante, oh!
Don't hate me 'cuz I'm beautiful
Don't hate me 'cuz I speak tru-e
And don't you hate me cuz my blood is blu-e
They say that money is the root of all e-e-vil
They must be jealous of what demons can do-o
So don't hate me cuz I'm beautiful, no
Hate me cuz I'm better than yo-u