Pam pam pam para para
Pam pam pam para-ah
Oh ah ah
Pam pam pam para para
Pam pam pam para-ah
Trot
Trot outside and you see the sunshine
See the sunshine
Something's in the air toda-a-ay
Oh ah ah today
Sky is clear and you're feeling so fine
Oh ah ah
Everything's gonna be A-Okay
Everything's ah-kay
Oh ah ah
If you listen carefully
On every corner
Oh oh ah ah-ha
There's a rhythm playing
Oh ah ah
Then it happens suddenly
The music takes you over and you
Oh oh oh
Find... got the music
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Music in you
Find got the music
Find the music oh-oh oh-oh
Music in you
Oh oh
Oh-oh
Everypony's sayin' you should
Oh ah ah
Learn to express your voice
Oh ah ah ah oh
But if talk doesn't seem like
Oh ah ah
It's the answer
Luckily you have a choice
When you find you've got the music
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Music in you
Find you've got the music
Find the music in you
Music in you
Got the music
Got the mu-usic
Got the music in you
Pam pam pam para para
Oh ah ah
Pam pam pam para-ah
Trot
Trot outside and you see the sunshine
See the sunshine
Something's in the air today
Oh ah ah today
Sky is clear and you're feeling so fine
Oh ah ah
Everything's gonna be A-Okay
Everything's ah-kay
Pam pam pam para para
Oh ah ah
Pam pam pam para-ah
Pam pam pam para para
Oh ah ah
Pam pam pam para-ah
Pam pam pam para para
Oh ah ah
Pam pam pam para-ah
If you listen carefully
On every corner
Oh oh ah ah-ha
There's a rhythm playing
Oh ah ah
Then it happens suddenly
The music takes you over and you
Oh oh...
Find the music
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Deep down in your heart
You can find it
Find the music in you
Oh yeah yeah
It's in you no-o-ow
Hey hey yeah yeah
Got the mu-usic
Got the music in you
He-e-ey find it
When you find you've got the music
O-o-ow why, you can find it
In your he-a-art yeah yeah
When you find you've got the music
Find the music ye-e-ah yeah
It's in you right no-o-ow
O-uh ye-e-ah yeah
When you find you've got the music
You can find the music
When you...
Yeah yeah I love the music ye...?