Oh ah ah
Trot
See the sunshine
Oh ah ah today
Oh ah ah
Everything's ah-kay
If you listen carefully
On every corner
There's a rhythm playing
Then it happens suddenly
The music takes you over and you
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Find the music oh-oh oh-oh
Oh-oh
Oh ah ah
Oh ah ah ah oh
Luckily you have a choice
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Find the music in you
Got the mu-usic
Got the music in you
Oh ah ah
Trot
See the sunshine
Oh ah ah today
Oh ah ah
Everything's ah-kay
If you listen carefully
On every corner
There's a rhythm playing
Then it happens suddenly
The music takes you over and you
Find the music oh-oh yo-u
Find the music in you
Got the mu-usic
Got the music in you
When you find you've got the music
When you...