You know what?
Little Cotton Candy here was right
And, if I do say so myself…
This town is not a nice place
For little fillies all alone
There are lots of twists and corners
That could lead to the unknown
Let me guide your way
And I'll be sure to help you through
You could really use a friend out here
And luckily for you
I'm the friend that you need
When you're lost and don't know what to do
I'm your pal, your amigo
Useful and resourceful, too
And my help, you'll concede
Is a plus, guaranteed
You can call and I'll come running
Just follow my lead
'Cause I'm the friend you need
Quite a friend
He's a friend indeed
You need a bud to spot the danger
A pal to stop the creep
A chum and not a stranger to assist
You need a bro who is cunning
That can help you take the leap
A friend who knows what's lying in the mist
Don't fear these darkened alleys
They're scary, yes, I know
Why, you could use a friend
To protect you wherever you go
And such a dazzling beauty
Covered in dirt and muck
But now your fate is changing
Now you are in luck
'Cause I'm the friend that you need
When you're lost and don't know what to do
I'm your pal, your amigo
Lookin' out for friends like you
And my help, you'll concede
Is a plus, guaranteed
Just call and I'll come running
We'll say it's agreed
Here! Tell Verko: "My place, twenty minutes"
I've got something that will magically erase all my debt
'Cause I'm the friend you need
He's a friend indeed