Applejack, Fluttershy, Rainbow Dash, Pinkie Pie
Rarity, Twilight and Spike
Sweetie Belle, Applebloom, Babs Seed and Scootaloo
Luna Princess of the Night
Vinyl Scratch and Octavia, Princess Celestia
Cadance and Shining Armor
Fleur de Lis, Cheerilee, then Cherry Jubilee
Blue Blood and Mayor Mare
Big Macintosh, Granny Smith, and Photo Finish
Both Fancy Pants and Daring Do
Then Lotus and Aloe, and Peachbottom, Gizmo
And Thunderlane, Blossomforth too!
Hayseed and Strudel and Score, Spot and Dumb-Bell
Then Cloudy Quartz, Igneous Rock
Limestone and Marble Pie, Mister and Ms. Shy
Maud, Randolf, Ivory Rook
Sunburst and Silver Spoon, Sombra and Nightmare Moon
Wind Rider, Songbird Serenade
Silver Frames, Swan Song, and Doctor Caballeron
Mane-iac, Roma, Masquerade
There's the Cake's and their children, both Pound Cake and Pumpkin
Then Walter, and Donny, the Dude
Then Lilac, Night Light, and Mudbriar, Firelight
Aura, Strike, Bolt, Dinky Doo!
Peachy Pie, Sunny Daze, Stygian, Autumn Blaze
Snips and Snails and Filthy Rich
Double Diamond, Flash Sentry and Coco's boss Suri
And Diamond Tiara's a... jerk.
Amber and Amethyst, then Golden Harvest
Featherweight, Junebug and Joe
Zecora, and Spoiled Rich, and then Cheese Sandwich
Ms. Harshwhinny, Flim and Flam Bros
Oh! There's Tree Hugger, Sugar Belle, Royal Riff, Parcel
And Caesar and Lily, Star Gazer
Golden Grape, Berryshine, Lyrica, Shoeshine
And Lightning Dust, Flitter, Cloudchaser
Davenport, Silverstar, Tender Taps, Soundbar
Then Quibble Pants and Feather Bangs (Trixie!)
Screwball and Flurry Heart, Lead Wing, Florina Tart
Jonagold, Fiddly Twang
Svengallop, Tempest Shadow, Starlight, Cozy Glow
Shooting Star, Sir Pony Moore
Star Swirl, Serenea, Savoir Fare, Vidala
Trenderhoof, Sapphire Shores
Hoity Toity then Velvet and Upper Crust, Jet Set
Stellar Eclipse, Teddie Safari
Moon Dancer, Angel Wings, Bon Bon, Lyra Heartstrings
Mane Allgood, Snapshutter, Bright Mac and Pear Butter
Vapor Trail, Sky Stinger, Bulk Biceps, Zephyr Breeze, Doctor Whooves, Saffron and Derpy!