When I was just a filly
I found itrather silly
To see how many other ponies I could meet
I had my books to read
Didn't know that I would ever need
Other ponies to make my life complete
But there was one colt that I cared for
I knew he would be there for me
My Big Brother Best Friend Forever
Like two peas in a pod
We did everything together
He taught me how to fly a kite
We never had a single fight
We shared our hopes, we shared our dreams
I miss him more than I realized
I-it seems
Your Big Brother Best Friend Forever
Like two peas in a pod
You did everything together
And though he's oh so far away
I hope that he would stay
My Big Brother Best Friend
Forever
Foreve-e-e-er
He was my Big Brother Best Friend
Forever
And now we'll never do anything
Together