Let's all work toge-ethe-e-er
To make this castle shi-i-i-ine
Once we add some spa-arkle
It'll feel
It'll fe-el divi-ine
Crates of apples and bales o' hay
Just makes you feel at home
Furry friends and some popinjays
So she won't be alone
And we'll make
This castle a ho-ome
The-ere's nothing like balloons and confetti
To greet you everytime you walk through the do-or
She'll need this and those
Posters of all my heroes
How could anypony awesome
Ever ask for mo-ore
And we'll make
A home she'll ado-ore
Bright curtains, a flowing silk and lace
This picture of me winning a race
Party cannons to give her a surprise
Hoes and rakes and some more garden supplies
Getting hugs from this nice big friendly bear
Decorate with some gemstones bright and rare
More of this and that
Don't forget the party hats
How could anypony awesome
Ask for more than that?
Let's all work toge-ether
To show that we have sho-o-own
Princess Twilight Spa-arkle
How we make
This castle a ho-ome
This castle a home
How we make
This castle a ho-ome
It's not the things that you gather 'round
It's not how much you own
The things that ho-old the meaning i-in your life
Are the memories you've sown
So we make
This castle a ho-ome
This castle a home
So we make
This cas-tle a ho-ome