Okay, wait wait wait
So you had how many brothers?
*gasp*!
That's horrible!
And sisters
I used to throw tons of parties for my sister Maud when we were little
But then, one day she just shut me out
And I never knew why
Okay, can I just, say something crazy?
All my life I've thrown a party nopony understood
And then suddenly I bump into you
But with you…
I see your face
And it's sweeter than a chocolate cake galore
Love is a yummy s'more!
Love is a yummy s'more
With you!
I mean it's awesome
What?!
We finish each others-
Cinnamon buns?!
That's what I was hungry for!
I would had never known you party just like me
You party just like me
Jinx! Jinx! Jinx!
Our mental synchronization
Can have but one explanation
You-
And I-
Were-
Just meant to be!
Meant to be!
Say goodbye
Say goodbye to the pain of the past
To the pain of the past
We don't have to feel it anymore
Love is a yummy s'more~!
Love is a yummy s'more~~!
Love is a yummy s'more~~~!
Love is a yummy s'more~!
Life can be so much more
With Cheese!
Pinkie!
No you!
Love is a yummy s'more~~~
Love is a yummy s'more
Can I say something crazy?
Will you be my special somepony?
Can I say something even crazier?
Yes!,0,0,0,,With you!
Yes!