I used to be the one
Stuck on the sidelines
But lately things have started to~ change
I would have never thought
That being the way I am could make
Everything end up this~~ way
This is never what I would have expected
There's nothing wrong but
They still want me corrected
Why can't you just let me do what I do
I'm not hurting anyone so why are you
Why are you
How could you try and change who I've always been
What did I do wrong?
I never wanted any of this
I'm sorry if I ever offended any of you
But I am who I am
There's not much more that I can do
A wise man once said that friendship was magic
The way I see it
It's been nothing but tragic
I tried my best and it wasn't quite there
A fairy tale but no happy ending for this mare?
I just don't know what went~ wrong
They don't love me anymore~ so
So~ long
Now I'm left out~ on my~ own
I wish there was somewhere for me
To call home
Is it not enough that I'm in the background?
You wanna drop me because of how my voice sounds?
Well I apologize if I ever made you sad
But I will not be sorry for being who I am
This is who I am~~
How could you try and change who I've always been
What did I do wrong?
I never wanted any of this
I'm sorry if I ever offended any of you
But I am who I am
There's not much more that I can do
A wise man once said that friendship was magic
The way I see it
It's been nothing but tragic
I tried my best and it wasn't quite there
A fairy tale but no happy ending for this mare?
How could you try and change who I've always been
What did I do wrong?
I never wanted any of this
I'm sorry if I ever offended any of you
But I am who I am
There's not much more that I can do~
A wise man once said that friendship was magic
The way I see it
It's been nothing but tragic
I tried my best and it wasn't quite~ there
So will there ever be a happy ending for this mare?