Why is there a muffin in my mailbox?
Derpy Hooves!
Just derped in
All wall-eyed
Must be hard to see
Mail hoof out
Time for delivery
You notice that she's derpin'
You know she's thinkin' muffin
You know she's gonna run in
To that table, baby
Package, probably broke it
Stuffed up in the mail slit
Derpy's gonna bust her bubble behind
She's a ditzy horse
Gonna fly off course
She's a blondie, blondie, blond for sure
She's a ditzy horse
Gonna fly off course
She will leave you, leave you, wantin'~ more
Watch her derp
When she jerks
She eats it hard
Some may gasp and ask
If she's all that smart~~
Coordination's lackin'
Head she's always wackin'
You know she's walkin' smack in
To that mailbox, baby
Package, probably broke it
Tangled in the hammock
Derpy's gonna bust her bubble behind
She's a ditzy horse
Gonna fly off course
She's a blondie, blondie, blond for sure
She's a ditzy horse
Gonna fly off course
She will leave you, leave you, wantin' more
Like I'm Derpy Hooves
And you gotta get it together
'Cause I'm goin' crazy
And droppin' anvils like the weather
And you think that I am nuts
And I don't really give a cuss
There you go
Kiss me now
Hah ah ah!
Bubbles on my butt
Muffins yeah!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Like I don't really know
What I'm talkin 'bout too
Derpin' derpin' derpin'
Eyes are crossed
La la la la la
Is this north or is this south?
Lala lala wooo-hooo!