Do you think the coast is cle-ar
No one to see, no one to hear
Me sing out my song
I think we're all alone
I don't need my name in lights
That's not where I've set my si-ights
No, oh-uh, no, not me-e
I don't ne-ed a sta-age to sing
To turn it up, to sing alo-ong
I'm not just shy
Look close, and you wi-ill see
There's so much more to-o me
I'm just fine rehearsing on my-y own
My hairbrush is my micro-opho-one
Look out now, I-'m in the zone
Yeah! Can you feel it?
I like the quiet, I like the calm
To turn it up, to sing alo-ong
I'm not just shy
Look close, and you wi-ill see
There's so much more to --
I speak soft out in a cro-owd
I whisper, "am I being too lo-ud?"
But when I clo-ose tha-at do-o-o-or
The crowd, it just wants
More and mo-ore and mo-ore
I like the quiet, I like the calm
To turn it up, to sing alo-ong
I'm not just shy-y
Look close, and you wi-ill see
There's so much more to --
I like my friends, I like my pets
I like to rock, do pirouettes
I'm more than shy-y
I'm more than you can see
There's so much more to-o me