Good morning, sun
No time to chat, I gotta run
'Cause I've got places to be
So much to do
Excited, yes, and nervous, too
A change is starting with me
I never worry 'bout upsetting carts
Hardened hearts
Or wonder, "Will I belong?"
I've heard it enough
I'm callin' their bluff
I'll never get lost in the gre-e-ey
There's something inside
Burns bigger than pride
Shines out of me, lighting the wa-ay
I've heard it enough
I'm callin' their bluff
I'll never get lost in the gre-e-ey
There's something inside
Burns bigger than pride
Shines out of me, lighting the wa-ay
Gonna be, gonna be, gonna be my da-ay
Gonna be, gonna be, gonna bе my da-ay
Hey there, hello!
The friends I make, the friends I know
Today you answer my call
Instead of hide, instead of staying stuck inside
Instead of building your wall
Come on and party with me, join the band, understand
We'll all be singing this song
Everyone's afra-aid
Always ju-udging, never bu-udging
Ain't it ti-ime we ma-ade the team
I've heard it enough
I'm callin' their bluff
I'll never get lost in the gre-e-ey
Go big or go home
Get real or get known
Get ready and raring to sa-ay
I've heard it enough
I'm callin' their bluff
I'll never get lost in the gre-e-ey
There's something inside
Burns bigger than pride
Shines out of me, lighting the wa-ay