I know you're cold
The rain's out tonight
I know you're looking for
A place to rest your head~~
I know we said
Things that~ were wrong
In the heat of the moment we got
Lost in our words~~
Now you're all alone
Wandering the streets
Looking for a new home but
Home's where the heart lies
Home's with the magic
Home's where you're all a~lone
But you don't seem to care
So let's call this night done
And crawl into bed~
I'll be right here all~ night
So just rest your head
Oh~~~
The moment is gone
Regrets all that's left
The arguing's past and now
The feelings are set
Right by my side
Is where you belong~
Our halls are empty whenever
We are apart
Now I'm on my own
Wondering where you've gone
Thinking of what went wrong but
Home's where the heart lies
Home's with the magic
Home's where you're all a~lone
But you don't seem to care
So let's call this night done
And crawl into bed~
I'll be right here all~ night
Just rest your head
I know you're cold
I'm cold too
I know you're thinking of me
'Cause I'm thinking too
Home's where the heart lies
Home's with the magic
Home's where you're all a~lone
But you don't seem to care
So let's call this night done
And crawl into bed~
I know you're all a~lone
So come back home
Come back home~~~