Paradise it seemed
Was a memory in glass
Never washing clean
As the long years pass
Clouds choke the Sun
She longs to see her children
It would not be~ undone
Without your courage gi~ven
Though the fires
Scorched the skies and seas of paradise
You would climb to reach the night
As the winds of hatred bite
Though they broke our world
And they burned our bones
On top we'll build our homes
So much that we lost
Entombed~ in dust
On those graves we'll stay
And in love we'll trust
Rain strikes the ground
Like warm tears slowly falling
From her eyes to~ the earth
Can~ you hear them cal~ling
Though the fires~
Scorched the skies and seas of paradise
You arose to be the one
Where the wolves of hatred run
Though they broke our world
And they burned our bones
On top we'll build our homes