Dear~~ Princess
Are~ you there?
I've~ been waiting
Waiting for you here
Time~ has~ come for a new world
Don't wan~der in the~~ past
Never knew that I was ready
It came on so fast~
You've made a king~dom
That will last till the end~ of time~
To tell you that you've raised~ me high
In my letter to you
From sea to~ shining sea
We car~ry memories
From everywhere
Everycreature knows their~ time
Dear~ Prin~cess
The time has come
For you~ to go
The bat~tle's won
Princess please wipe these tears from my eyes
I don't know if I can let~ go~~
And everything I've ever known
Came from you~~
So Princess please
I don't want to go
I've learned so much
I'll carry it all forever
Dear Princess
We'll try our best
To take what you've taught us
A great new quest
Though we may fall
Fly through the air
We'll always remember
The magic we shared