I've been watching you
Giving up all of the things you had
I was lo~st among the foothills too
I fled higher to this precious la~nd
Oooooh
The air is rich and soil is fertile
So give me your hand
So give me your ha~~nd
Even if you forget me in a moment's time
You'll be fine
For paradise you're moving slow
Cross precipice
And frozen snow
Keep moving you ahead
Keep moving
Remember where you last saw yourself clearly
Asking why you hated getting up early
Don't be lead astray
Keep moving your own way
There's a love
A sacrifice
Haunted by this bad advice
Given time the heart will wilt
And heal itself with what it will
Letters, songs, and bits of string
Don't let any hatred in
Always makin' references
To passages in books you've read
Reaching out in to the dark
Settling for hope instead
Only let go of the flat li~ne
Only let go~ to find a foothold
Old hori~zon
Lazy weekends, crowded streets
Behind the curtains you can see
Taking all the time away
You can't relate
Only let go of the flat line
Only let go to find a foothold
Old hori~zon
Lazy weekends, crowded streets
Behind the curtains you can't see
Taking all the time away
You can't relate
Only let go of the flat line
Only let go to find a foothold
Old hori~zon
Lazy weekends, crowded streets
Behind the curtains you can't see
Taking all the time away
You can't relate