A long, long time ago
The sisters ruled in harmony
With solace all throughout the land
And you could drink your cider there
Without the single need to care
I-if anypony's looking where you stand
But then one night, the stars were stubborn
The cries were heard and tears were falling
Shadows in the sunlight
A new face in the moonlight
The prophecy~ was coming true
And only one could see the clues~
But when she tried to spread the news~
That's where the magic began
So, Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pe-ens
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends~"
Did you see it all go wrong
As the evening tried to move along~
And the strike~ of light~ning flashed?
And did you~ meet up~ with Nightmare Moon~?
Did you think she'd be back so soon?
Oh~, everything was going by so~ fast~~~~
A loud~ clatter filled the atmosphere
When we saw the lady disappear~
The rest were~ all~ confused~
But that smart one knew what to do~~
She was a po~ny who had~ a violet mane
With a straight-A record and a dragon slave
And everypo~ny would know~ her name
The day the magic began
They were singing~, Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens~
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends~"
Now~, her whole life~ she'd been on her own~
With a heart made right out of solid stone~
But that's how she~ preferred to be~
Then the Princess told her to worry less
About things	 that she had only read
In a book that contained~ a mystery~~~~
Oh, and as the sun was going down~
The Princess sent her into town
Prepa~ring for~ the feast~
No~pony would believe~~
Because~ it had been a thousand years
The midnight hour was~ getting near~
The Princess told her not to fear
The day the magic began
She was singing~, Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens~
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends"
Hustle-bustle in an aging castle
It all took off in an epic battle
One last blow~ and flying faaaaaaaaaast
It en~ded with a powerful blast
The kingdom thrived~ for a time at last
And the Princess put her sister in the past~~~~
Oh, the passing hours~ were bittersweet~
While the soldiers kept a safe retreat
They all forgot~ the name~
Oh~, but it'd never be~ the same~~
'Cause the eleme-ents were turned to boulders
Some folks grew old and hearts grew colder
Who would have thought it'd all~ be over
The day the magic began?
They'd be singing, Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens~
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends~"
Oh~~, only hours from certain doom
Six little ponies in one room
With no time left~ to waste~ at all~
So, come on~, you know something they don't know
You know about the story below~, and
Secrets are a subtle way to fall~~~~
Oh, and as they journeyed through the dark~
Their hearts were tried and left with marks
Nothing~ from Tartarus
Could break their new-found trust~
And~ as the co~lors flew~ into the air
To cast away that cursed mare
They found~ something else that wasn't there
The day the magic began
They were singing~, Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens~
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends"
They had a party back in town~
With singing and dancing all around~
They all saw the Princess then
What they found in that ancient hall~
They'd not be forgetting soon at all~
But the smart one knew the journey
Had an end~~~~~
And after all was said and done
The war was fought, and the battle won
The Princess smiled boldly
And said, "Spike, take a note, please"
With a calming voice and a simple tone~
She changed the life of~ the one she'd known
"Welcome to your brand new home"
The day
The magic began
And she was singing
Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens~
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"
"I could never live without friends~"
They were singing
Bye~-bye, little librarian
Stop your thinking, quit the reading
Drop your numerous pens
You'll be al~right, I know I'll see you again
Saying "I could never live without friends"