Cause I'm just a backseat driv~er
Oh woah~ woah yeah oh woah~ woah
Looks like I've only got one chance
I'll tell you what you need to know it's far too easy
To break me down but for what it's worth
I'll head down where the grass is dull~er
Oh woah~ woah yeah
At least from there there's not much farther I could fall
You said when we were kids you'd always love me
But I know now that's not your sty~~le
Just wait it out one day and night longer
One more night won't make you any strong~er
Ah-ah ah-ah-ah-ah eh eh eh
So tessellate a little fur~ther
You're out of sight you're behind
You're right in front of all my raw desires
So let your colors show run down the paper
An inky mess just bottle that back up
Just wait it out one day and night longer
One more night won't make you any strong~er
And the rest of us mourners we applaud you
When you leave take our spiteful prayers with~ you
If there's anyone out there on the bright side
Let my words be advice to the wide-~eyed
You're going the wrong way
Ah-ah-ah-ah wrong-wrong you're going the wrong way
Painting with a violent pal~lette
With shades of storm and hate
And hues of every time I ever let you down
Just once in a lifetime that you have me
What is it that makes you loathe me so bad~ly?
Is this the feeling that a dream leaves you diz~zy?
You said when we were kids you'd always love me
And no matter what you'd swear it keep it real