Ah ah, ah ah ah
Ah ah ah, ah ah ah
I have changed
I have grown
Now I am
On my own
Knowing now
What is right
I am free
In the light
Open eyes
Opened heart
Of the world
Now a part
Take a breath
Take a chance
Take a leap
So entranced
You can't take my hope, my quest, my dream
To fly
To soar free, forever in the sky
With my new found bravery I will get by~~
So much stronger than before yet knowing
I'm still shy~
!?
Open air
On my face
As the clouds
I embrace
Perfect bliss
Terror gone
As my soul
Bursts in song
Ah ah, ah ah ah
Ah ah ah, ah ah ah
You can't take my hope, my quest, my dream
To fly
To soar free, forever in the sky
With my new found bravery I will get by~~
So much stronger than before yet knowing
I'm still shy~
You will understand~~
When you see the sky so grand
There is no more need to cry
I'm finally alive
Knowing I'm~
Still shy