Your present is only kind of finished, Rarity
But I guess it's better than nothing
I wanted to get you
Something oh, so rare~
A gift to show I care~
But nothing can compare
To you, that's easy to see
But I got stressed and overthought
Until the day was shot
And it was all for naught
But now it's clear to me
I'm not gifted at gifting
It's really pretty sad
I tried to show I care
But it turned out bad
I'm not gifted at gifting
So all that's left to say
Is that I really hope my gifting
Didn't ruin your holiday
Oh, Spike
A song is a lovely present
I wanted to get you the best gift ever
I just couldn't figure out what it was
Ooh! Ooh!
The gift-giver taught me that
Eh, what was it?
The best gift is more precious than gold
But it cannot be sold
When it breaks it's not hindered
For it quickly is mended
It can never be bought
Yet is easily sought
What's so funny?
It's a riddle
And the answer is
Friendship
The most magical gift
That I can recall~
It could've been big or small
Or even nothing at all
It doesn't matter~, you see
If it's from my friends on whom I depend
No matter what you spend
It will be perfect to me
The true gift of gifting
Is what it means inside
We can show we care
Spreading love far and wide
The true gift of gifting
Is totally free
And you're the best there is at givin' it
With the friendship that you give to me
We've all been friends forever
And look how far we've come
The holiday brings us close
And now it's time for fun
The greatest gift you give to me
Is more precious than gold
Never ended, always mended
And it can't be bought or sold
The true gift of gifting
Is what it means inside
We can show we care
Spreading love far and wide
The true gift of gifting
Is totally free
And you're the best there is at givin' it
With the friendship that you give to me
And a lesson was learned
There's no need to obsess
Gift-giving is simple
As long as you recall
Friendship is the best gift of all