Spread your wings, Neon Pegasus
And go flying through the night
They can take your glitter but they can't
Take away your spar~kle
And the thousand arm robot octopus
Will try to grab your golden reins
But your wings are strong
From the battle over Cupcake Mountain
Never again to be lonely
Never again to be without a home~
Never to bow to the gummy king's throne
Never again, never again!
Never again to be put down
By the Marzipan Girl at the silver lake lounge
Soaring over it all, high up in the clouds
Never again, never again!
Yeah!
When I first saw you defeating the Gummy King's
Gluten powered armada in the darkness of space
I knew you were no ordinary pegasus!
Un-break your heart, Neon Pegasus
And go climbing through the stars
Out there with your dreams~~
Your sparkly dreams
And the genetically modified salamander
With a face just like George Clooney
Can't track you down
With the Rockabilly Worm from Space Land
Never again to be lonely
Never again to be without a home~
Never to bow to the Gummy King's throne
Never again, never again!
Never again to be put down
By the Marzipan Girl at the Silver Lake Lounge
Soaring over it all, high up in the clouds
Never again, never again
No matter how insane and ridiculous they seem
You must follow your dreams!