Like a shadow, love should follow
When the sun is shining bright
I'll be around
Oh I'll be around~~
And how the moon can move the water
When the stars are in the sky~
I'll be around~~
Oh I'll be around
I've always got your back
I'll always hold it down
I'll be around
And anything you need
Won't have to make a sound
'Cause I'll be around~~
And when the times get harder
We can take~ off
You don't have to worry
If we get lost
'Cause I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~
And you don't have to wonder
You can be~ free
Anything you want
You can count on me~~
I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~
And it's much better than a promise
It's more like a guarantee~~~
I'll be around~~
Oh I'll be around~~
It's a bond that can't be broken
Connected u~nity~~~
I'll be around~~~~~~
Oh I'll be around~~
I've always got your back
I'll always hold it down
I'll be around~~
And anything you need
Won't have to make a sound
I'll be around~~
And when the times get harder
We can take~ off
You don't have to worry
If we get lost
'Cause I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~
And you don't have to wonder
You can be~ free
Anything you want
You can count on me~~
I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~
And so it seems
That everybody needs a helping hand
Now and again~~~
Well, just believe
And we'll reach our target
'Cause I've got your back
'Till the end~
And when the times get harder
We can take~ off
You don't have to worry
If we get lost
'Cause I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~
And you don't have to wonder
You can be~ free
Anything you want
You can count on me~~
I'll be around~~~~~
I'll be around~~~~