I'm here to show you who I ~ am
Throw off the veil, it's fi~nally time
There's more to me than glitz~ and~ glam, oh-uh-oh
And now~ I feel my stars a~lign~~~
For I had believed what I was sold
I did all the things that I was told~
But all that has changed and now I'm bold
'Cause I know
That I am just a pony
I make mistakes from time to time
But now I know the real me~
And put my heart out on~ the line
Just like the magic inside of you
And now I see those co~lors
Bright be~fore my eyes~~
I hear~ my voice so clearly and I know that it is right
They thought I was weak, but I am strong
They sold me the world, but they were wrong
And now that I'm back I still belong
'Cause I know
That I am just a pony
I make mistakes from time to time
But now I know the real me~
And put my heart out on~~ the line
And let the magic in my heart~~ stay true~~
Oh-oh woah uh-oh-oh woah
Just like the magic insi~de of you
I make mistakes from time to time
But now I know the real me~
And put my heart out on~~ the line
And let the magic in my heart~~ stay true~~
Oh-oh woah uh-oh-oh woah
Just like the magic insi~de of you~~
Just like the magic insi~de of you