Don't look for me in the spo-otlight
Don't think that I am the one
Who brightens your li-ives
And endlessly stri-ives
To live a life in the sun
I will never shine, I'll never be-e beautiful,
And I-I will never be yo-ours
She made it clear, I should stay right here,
So you can be sure
That I am no hero
I ca-an't answer your prayers
No matter how I feel inside
I know that nobody ca-ares
For I am no hero
And when you-u look to the sky
You will neve-er see my-y face
You'll never see me cry
This is the real me,
Unashamed, but not unafra-aid
I won't say I'm so-orry
For who I was,
I can't say I've never strayed
Far from the li-ight, away fro-om the pa-ath
That a-a-a-a-all the righteous have tre-ead
But I'll never lie, no I'll never try
To claim I-I'm perfect inste-e-ead
For I am no hero
I ca-an't answer your praye-ers
No matter how it feels insi-ide
I know that nobody ca-ares
For I am no hero
And whe-en you look to the sky
You will neve-er see my-y face
You'll never see me cry
No I am not perfect,
I just wanna be
The one you look up to
In times of need,
But you love another,
I'll never be the same
When you're lonely like me,
Don't call for my-y na-a-ame
Don't call my na-a-a-a-a-a-a-me
na-a-a-a-a-a-ame