Woo
Ooh yeah~~~~~
Ah pa pa
Ah pa da pa pa
Ah pa pa da da
Pa pa pa da da da da
Pa pa
Pa da pa pa
Ah pa pa da da
Pa pa pa da da da da
Come on come all
To the show of the century
I'll blow your~ minds
A sight you'll surely want to see~
Oh there's no one who can beat me
No one who can stop me
I'm just so good at my craft~
And if anyone dare question~
I'll extend my~ hoof and an open invita~tion
To try our skills in a battle or two~
I've got you right in my sights~
Just magic against magic
Or prove your talent
You'll meet your maker tonight~
Oh I know~ you'll have to fold your cards 'cause
I've got the better hand~~
So given the circumstance
You've got no~ chance
Wo oh oh~ yeah~~ hey~ yeah~~~
Oh~ oh~~ yeah~~
You've ruled this town~
A one trick pony for far too long
Let's question what's fair~
Let's question what's fair
Just to rule it with common sense
Oh you're not even worthy
Don't get me started on the imperfections you've played~
From the moment I first met you~
It wasn't competition, on~ly a question
Of whether or not you would find the courage
To finally stand up and fight~
It's just magic against ma~gic or prove you're ta~lented
I'm gonna beat ya tonight~
And I know you'll have to fold your cards 'cause
I've got the better hand~~
So given the circumstance
You've got no chance~
No you've got no chance~
You'd better move on
If you know what is right~
Yeah you'd better skip town
And disappear into the night
I'll be back next time~
You'll be back next time~
To fight this grudge inside~~
To fight this grudge~ inside~~ oh
There's no respect in losing a fight~
Only shame that's hard to bite~
Like magic against magic it seems to clash and yet
You fight with all of your might~
Oh I know~ you'll have to fold your cards~
'Cause I've got the bet~ter hand~~~~
Oh~ given the circumstance~~
You better watch out cause I will be back
Oh but given the circumstance~
You've got no~ chance~~
You've got no chance~~
So I'll see you on the other side
Ah pa pa
Ah pa da pa pa
Ah pa pa da da
Pa pa pa da da da da
Oh but given the circumstance~
Given the circumstance~
You've got no~ chance~~
You've got no chance~~~~