All around me are familiar ponies
All so cra-azy, all so cra-azy-y-y
Started out with just my good intentions
Getting nowhere, getting nowhe-e-ere
Ponyville is filling up with la-aughter
A disa-aster, a disa-aste-e-er
Dunk my head into a pool of mi-irrors
Getting nearer, getting neare-e-er
And I find it kinda funny,
I find it kinda sad
The copies I created
Are far more tha-an I had planned
I don't know how to tell you,
Don't think you'll understand
When Pinkies run in numbers
It's a very-y, very-y
Mad world
Mad wo-orld
All I sought was to have fun with my-y friends
Now its cra-azy, now its cra-azy-y-y
Haven't got a clue, how to make amends
Watch the paint dry, watch the paint dry-y-y
One by one they're judged and banished ba-a-ack
Pay attention, pay attentio-o-on
By the end who is the real Pi-inkie?
No one knows now, no one knows no-o-ow
And I find it kinda funny,
I find it kinda sad
The copies I created,
Are far more tha-an I had planned
I don't know how to tell you,
Don't think you'll understand
When Pinkies run in numbers
It's a very-y, very-y
Mad world
Mad wo-orld