Tell me can you hear my heart beat roar
Inside my~ chest
Though I try my hardest I'm still stuck
At second~ best
And in the end I know it's true
I fight away but there's little I~ can do
Something like a virus, replica~ting in my soul
Tearing me to shreds, my heart is dead
My blood is boil~ing, leaving me one goal
And in the end, it brought me down
Something new has come around
Come on!
So arm yourself against my fear
I'll be the shadow at your core
For all my life I've lived alone
And now's the time I fight for more
I fight for more
Ha ha!
Watch me keep the moon alive through your beloved day
Try your best to stop me: go ahead, what could you say?
For years and years I've been number two
And now's the time where I say I'm through
Standing in the way between the dreams~ I've always had
Try to seize the day, but now you've made~ the nightmare mad
Cast your spell, the shadow's won
Watch me overcome the wretched sun
So arm yourself against my fear
I'll be the shadow at your core
For all my life, I've lived alone
And now's the time I fight for more
Celestia, your time has come
I'm sick and tired of your lies
You cast me off, you bring me down
You've caused me tears and depressed sighs
But now I'm here to state my claim
To fight away the dark and gloom
'Till everypo~ny knows my name
And they will fear me~, Nightmare Moon
Seen~ this before
Just~ let me be
Don't~ fight no more
Why~ can't you see?
O~pen your eyes to~ see~ my~ pain
I'm~ just alone, I'm~ not~ insane
Seen~ this before
Just~ let me~ be
Don't~ fight no more
Why~ can't you see
O~pen your eyes
To~ see my pain
I'm~ just alone
I'm~ not~ in~sane
So arm yourself against my fear
I'll be the shadow at your core
For all my life I've lived alone
And now's the time I fight for more
Celestia, your time has come
I'm sick and tired of your lies
You cast me off, you bring me down
You've caused me tears and depressed sighs
But now I'm here to state my claim
To fight away the dark and gloom
'Till everypony knows my name
And they will fear me~, Nightmare~ Moon