I am the jelly pony I want to play
Ready or not I am a-coming this way
Don't be afraid let me show you who I am
Take off your clothes we're getting into the jam
Lay on the bed you just sit back and behave
Your applesauce is the one thing that I crave
Look down below to see my jelly has set
Hope you can swim 'cause you're gonna get wet
Oh babe your jam jar's got some beautiful curves
Tastes almost like my fav'rite fruit preserves
And did I comment on your delicious spread?
Should I do you or will you do me instead?
Strangely obsessed
Strangely obsessed with tubs of jelly
Oh wait hold up I think my lid's getting loose
There'll be strawb'ry jam all over your caboose
Some in your mane some on your belly
Do you think you're ready for all of this jelly?
<Sigh> Strangely obsessed
Strangely obsessed
Strangely obsessed with tubs of jelly