Well, if you wanted honesty
You came to the right pla-ace
Though Applejack's a background horse
Please don't get mad
It's better off this way
For every garbage meme
The DA spaghetti I've seen
Remember when my parents found
My Rainbow Dash rule sixty-three but
I-I-I'm no-ot gay
I'm not gaaaay-aay
I'm no-ot gaaay
It's i-ironi-ic
What will it take to show you that
We're diff'rent from furries?
I've told you time and time again
"Just watch the show, I swear it's not cringy!"
Ponies are really sick
I've stuck with them through thin and thick
Don't look at my page on Fimfic
Unless you're into giant dicks
But I-I-I'm no-ot gay
I'm not gaaaay-aay
I'm no-ot gaaay
I like mare a-ass
Forget about vids on Redtube
Explicit on Derpibooru
Turn up that movie soundtrack
I have a "chance" but I call it Big Mac
I'm not gay
I'm not GAAAAAAAAY!
I'm not ga-ay, no
I'm not ga-ay, no-
But you really need to listen to me!
'Cause jacking it to Braeburn once
Doesn't make you fucking gay!
Pfftt, whatever
I-I-I'm no-ot gay
I'm not ga-ay
I swear I'm not gay
It doesn't make you fucking gay
-not gaaay
I'm not gaay-aay
That was the gayest shit I've ever heard