You see us fly through the sky
Flight goggles shining bright
With wings of steel faster than anypony who can fly
We are the speedy cure
We're what you're looking for
The antidote sent to impress crowds who always want more
Some say that we're all fake
Boy that's a big mistake
I challenge anypony, life or death, your choice to make
'Cause we will not back down
I'll turn this right around
These rumors stain our legacy
Of which we are so proud
Now we refuse to let you win
You're a liar and always has been
Now I refuse to let you win
There are dark stories of our past that I bet you don't know
The truth about where we came from kept secret even though
We are so famous, these secrets shame us
Lab rats from day one until somepony dare save us
So desperate were we to be known by all Equestria
We sold our soul and so ourselves unto Celestia~
And now we don't even know where we stand within this place
Just doing as we're told and hoping one day that we'll escape
With all these years I've wasted
If only I was brave enough to face it
This was too good to be true from the very start
I should never have believed this was from the heart
We were but young ponies so absorbed in our dreams
It took so long to realize that we had been tricked with ease
Such promises of fame and fortune were too much to take
If asked the same question right now, I'd make the same mistake
For even though I do regret the things that I~ have done
I'd rather take all of the blame myself for everyone
It's better to live with it all and save the ones I need
Than just give in and let it bring all of us to our knees
(Leave us a)-lone-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-ne
-Oh!-
With all these years I've wasted
If only I was brave enough to face it
This was too good to be true from the very start
I should never have believed this was from the heart
With all these years I've wasted
If only I was brave enough to face it
This was too good to be true from the very start
I should never have believed this was from the heart