Everypony knows the name of the game
And their lives won't ever be the same
Once I have you by my side
They call you crazy but I think you're a saint
A brilliant mind a genius to the chaos
You wreak upon their lives
Bash all the things that you've ever wanted
Turn~ all the friends that you've ever known
Your coats all fade to grey as we both die~ of laugh~ter
So much~ chaos and we don't care~
We relish in the fun while you wallow in~ despair~
Because it's all a tragic plot~ to~ tear~ you~
Anything for~ Dad~dy Dis~cord
Bring our antics throughout the town~
We'll wreak chaos through the night and day~
Now, doesn't that sound fun~
Turn your houses upside down~~
Then turn your happy face into a frown
Let your aspirations drown~~~
Who cares~~ if chaos isn't fair~
Bash all the things that you've ever wanted
Turn~ all the friends that you've ever known
Your coats all fade to grey as we both die~ of laugh~ter
So much~ chaos and we don't care~
We relish in the fun while you wallow in~ despair~
Because it's all a tragic plot~ to~ tear~ you
Anything for~ Dad~dy Dis~cord~~~~
All alone I sit here by~ your side
The living tomb~stone which on~ly I confide~
If on~ly I~~~ could break you out~ alive
We'd do~ this all~ again
But until then
Discord, I'm howling at the moon
And sleeping in the middle of a summer afternoon
Discord, whatever will I do
To make you reign your~ ty~ran~ny again
Small communities grow great through harmony
Great ones fall to pieces through discord...