The School of Friendship, first day of class
Will we fa-il or will we pass?
Students come from far and wide
Brand-ne-ew friends here by our side
Take a breath, look around, it's amazing
I can't believe that it's real
Students galore, new ideas to explore
Can't contain the excitement I feel
Can't mess up, can't afford a mistake now
Think "success", keep it firmly in sight
Make sure to do things by the book
Make sure to do it all right
The School of Friendship, must get to class
Will we fa-il or will we pass?
Students learning from the best
Taking notes to pass the test
Wait, hold on! Not like that! Just a second!
I'm not sure if that method's approved
Let me take a look! Yup, right here in the book
Come on! We just got in the groove!
Can't mess up, can't afford a mistake now
We are shaping young minds to ignite
Do it like it says in the book now
Make sure you're doing it right
There's not an equation on how to have fun
The students look bored now, oh, what have I done?
Can't teach bein' honest, not sure what to do
I'm quite certain I'm lost
None of us has a clue!
School of Friendship, another class
Wish it we-re more of a blast
Thought this school would be more fun
Can't wait for our classes to be done
Can't mess up, can't afford a mistake now
No way to have fun
Oh, what have I done?
Think "success", keep it firmly in sight
Wish that we could leave our desks
Listen to this one request
Make things fun, we're really stressed
Make sure to do things by the book now
Can we tell her this thing is a mess?