Don't look back
It's too late
To turn back now
Push through
Daring do~
You're gonna make it out~
Alive
This time
You won't let the danger o~vercome~ you
You know that everypo~ny in this world~ still needs you~
Daring Do don't back down or let evil defeat you
Stop
Don't turn around
When everything falls apart~
Just don't back down~
Just keep running~ just look ahead
You might be losing but you're not dead~
Hold on
Hold fast
Keep going
And never back down
Tied~ down
Look around
Danger everywhere
No one
In sight~
The smell of adventure in the air~
When it seems like your world has turned around~
No one~ can stop you
So never back~ down
Obstacles~ are in front of and behind you~
But this fear deep inside, you know it blinds you~
Take a leap and we will catch you~ as you fall
You know with your courage you can overcome it all~
Stop
Don't turn around
When everything falls apart~
Just don't back down~
Just keep running~ just look ahead
You might be losing but you're not dead~
Hold on
Hold fast
Keep going
And never back down
Life can seem like it's a little bit rough
But the tough ponies never ever give up
Enough, I wouldn't be here if I sat and groaned
And moaned about the times that I've felt alone
I grew a backbone and I told 'em all sup
And made a promise to never ever give up
I'm a stroller, I don't need a clover for luck
High roller~, gave Ahuizotl a buck
If you stand up life only just gets doper
Never give up and your cup runneth over
Not a moper, sober when I toss my frown
I continued moving up, never falling back down
And around this time I should say to you
That you should follow the lifestyle of Daring Do
I used to be just depressed and messed
Expressed to impress like a dang contest
Bang bang, I just rapped a couple of audibles
Trust me when I say nothing is impossible
Wait where'd the beat go... ah, oh snap
Stop
Don't turn around
When everything falls apart~
Just don't back down~
Just keep running~ just look ahead
You might be losing but you're not dead~
Hold on
Hold fast
Keep going
And never back down
... like it's a little bit rough
But the tough ponies never ever give up, I said
Life can seem like it's a little bit rough
But the tough ponies never ever give up