September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
Bright inviting morn
Brilliant rays reborn
So, follow along, as the shadows have gone
Walk where time has torn
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
Ahhhh~~~~~~~
Ahhhh~~~~~~
Ahhhh~~~
December White, thy beauty ever last