September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
Light of virtue shown
Sign of one's true form
To grow only small, giving gui~dance for all
Seen while hard~ly~ known
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
Bright inviting morn
Brilliant rays reborn
So, follow along, as the shadows have gone
Walk where time has torn
September Blue, thy sorrows be forgotten
October Auburn, let this season pass
Novem~ber~ Gray, re~store with thy~ rain
December White, thy beauty ever last
Ahhhh~~~~~~~
Ahhhh~~~~~~
Ahhhh~~~
December White, thy beauty ever last