What is this?~
Chilly weather rolling in?~
Is it win~ter already?
Can't be that time~ again~
Rush to my window~
White fluffy snow is on~ the ground~
I'm gonna be late again
Throw on my scarf and grab~ my plow
I rush out to the field~
Everypony else is there
I just try to get started
Hoping they all won't stare
Just starting to get my~ rhythm
Ignoring the cold in my feet _
Till this purple pony girl~
Blows on past the snow buries~ me
Who is that~ girl?
Why~ do I feel so~ strange?~
It just took one glance~
My mind is already blank
I know this~ feeling
But I know that it can't~ be~
Will somepony slap me So
I know it's not a dream
Winter's done~
We wrapped it up on time this year~
But I can't get her out of my head
My heart is choked up with fear~
Went to her house and~
I left some flowers at the door
Why couldn't I stick around?
Instead I bolted like a dork!
What the hell is my problem?
I haven't got a clue~
She probably won't even notice
But what else can I do?
I look up to the~ sky
And see her face in the clouds~
Suddenly I hear her voice
And my gaze is drawn back down
Who is that~ girl?
Why~ do I feel so~ strange?~
It just took one glance~
My mind is already blank
I know this~ feeling
But I know that it can't~ be~
Will somepony slap me
So I know it's not a dream
She's standing there she looks at me
She smiles oh so very sweetly
Says she saw me leave the flowers
I can't breathe - I want to cower
Tilts her head asks "what's your name?"
Words won't come faint sting of pain
As the lump stops in my throat admiring her lovely coat
My feet go numb I'm feeling dumb
My body says it wants to run
But everything inside my head
is telling me to hold it steady
Finally the nerve is there doubt starts to fade no longer bare
And now at last open my mouth and... <gasp>
Who is that~ girl?
Why~ do I feel so~ strange?~
It just took one glance~
My mind is already blank
I know this~ feeling
But could it really~ be?~
There's no need to slap me
Cause now I know it's not a dream
Now I know it's not a dream