I was headed
To east Texas
On a business trip
I had a room
At the Holiday I-inn Express
I dra-agged my ba-a-ag
To the elevator
But the button
For my floor was already pre-essed
The door slid open
Then I felt
Out of place
I can only imagine
The look on my fa-a-ace
It was one of those
"Everybody dress like ponies
Do drugs and ru-ub on each other"
Kinda parties that folks like me-e
Will never understand
It's kinda we-ird
Seeing a grown-ass man
In a costume, magenta hair
Plastic eyes looking at you
On an elevator
With a pink brush in his hand
Toni-ight everybody's dressed
Like po-onies at the Holiday Inn
And I do-on't think I'm coming back
To thi-is town again
Maybe To-om Bodett has a ro-om
That I can stay i-in?
Beca-use everybody's
Dressed li-ike ponies at this Holida-ay Inn
This place is weird
I gotta go
This one or the dang continental breakfast
I gotta deal with this mess