Can you see the li-ight
In the wi-indow at the top of the sta-airs
I guess she's up late aga-ain
Divining mysteries in books she sha-ares
She puts her assi-istant to bed and
Casts a glance to reckon the ti-ime
And pla-ans the da-ay ahe-ead
With a qui-ill by-y candleli-ight
And if she's enchanted by a sta-arry sky-y
Or bewitched by a book aga-ain
You'd better believe that where-e-ver study le-eads
She'd never leave behind a frie-end
She's gotta whole lotta magi-ic
She's gotta whole lotta magic no-ow
If she's a little bit crazy-y
Well this who-ole town is any-yhow
She's gotta whole lotta magi-ic
She's gotta whole lotta magic now
If she's a little bit crazy-y
Well this who-ole town is anyhow
Deep black, it turns to blu-u-ue
As the sunrise sparks a brand new day-y
She waves as she passes by-y-y
And I wonder what her letters say-y?
Ring ring ring, just burn that thing
Why don't we take a little chariot ri-i-ide
To where the lessons begun, in the warmth of the su-un
In the ci-ity on the mountainsi-i-ide
She's gotta who-ole lotta magi-ic
She's gotta whole lotta magic no-ow
If she's a little bit crazy-y
Well this who-ole town is anyho-o-o-o-ow
She's gotta whole lotta magi-ic
She's gotta whole lotta magic now
If she's a little bit crazy-y
Well this who-ole town is anyho-o-o-ow
Like the endless ni-ight of a sister's folly
Or a hellhound with a broken cha-ain
For her well la-aid pla-ans, I have admiration
But if she lets it go and conjures up some inspiration
We can spend the time together
in a sunnier locatio-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-on
Alright
It's well past closing ti-i-ime
And the shadow from the window pa-ane
Flickers sleepily-y-y
Like her eyes as the i-inkwe-ell dra-ains
Study's the shuttle of a star-swirled lo-om
Spinning tapestries in her dre-eams
I sweep for a while
And hope for her smi-ile
I'd love to be the thread that she we-e-e-eaves
She's gotta whole lotta magi-ic
Who-ole lotta magic now
If she-e's a little bit crazy-y
Well this whole town is anyhow
She's gotta whole lotta magi-ic
She's gotta whole lotta magic now
If she-e's a little bit crazy-y
Well this who-ole town is anyhow