I thought Earth ponies were the pony ladder's bottom rung
I heard that pegasi were brutes you'd hate to be among
You smell like fishes (you're vicious)
I bet you eat your young
Meet any one of you, the thing to do is run away
But although I know we're all a bunch of different breeds
Take away~ our wings and horns and we're just frightened steeds
So let's put aside our differences 'cause what we need's a win~
Oh oh oh
Come on, rip~ out all the pages of your history books
Just because we're undercover doesn't mean we're crooks
When we walk you through the crowd and give your brand new looks a spin
You're gonna fit right in
This is a new low
It's never gonna work
They taught us unicorns were super scary maniacs
With horns like razors and tongues like tasers and teeth like tacks
They take your hooves and then they grind them into midnight snacks
The basic gist of it is unicorns are not okay
Look I know we're risking everything for this endeavor
But look at us, we're brave and strong and weird and clever plus
Closer to the finish than we've ever ever been
Wow oh oh
So, we better take a leap and put our faith in you
Get our crafty on with sparkles, tape, and super glue
'Cause we're running out of options and we're desperate to begin
You're gonna fit right in
Ha, if you say so
I know you will, now watch and learn
This is how a unicorn walks
Walks
And this is how a unicorn talks
Talks
This is how a unicorn hoops
Hoops
This is how a unicorn
Oops
Oh, geez, stop!
This is how a unicorn struts
Struts
Oh, watch you shake your unicorn butts
Butts!
Now you're in the unicorn know
Woah
Soon, you'll be a unicorn pro
Oh, a unicorn horn makes a unicorn stride
It's the more-head on your forehead
It's the source of your pride
Every unicorn who's born has worn a horn that's unique
So I'll whip them up as we speak
You'll be lookin' très magnifique
We'll fake a pony protrusion
To make a bony illusion
It's not the perfect solution
But the world's not big on inclusion
And with those rocks in our pocket
We'll reap the reward
And folks will be floored
We'll strike a new chord
Our magic restored
Lately all Equestria has lost its heart
But if we can help to find it, we should play our part
If we fail, we'll go to prison
But if not, we'll start to grin~
So, let's begin~
We're gonna fit right in
This is how a unicorn walks
This is how a unicorn talks
Now you're looking unicorn strong~~~~
This is how a unicorn ends this song