I've been away for so long everything I used to know has changed
I don't recognize this place, I'm the only one who's still the same
I try not to be bitter
I try to be strong
I try to make my voice heard
But it always comes out wrong
I scream but nopony hears me
I'm drowned out by the noise
I call but nopony answers
With my Royal Canterlot Voice
I hardly go outside but when I do the ponies talk behind my back
The nighttime is so lonely that sometimes I feel about to crack
I try not to be angry
I try to belong
I try to make myself heard
But it always comes out wrong
I scream but nopony hears me
I'm drowned out by the noise
I call but nopony answers
With my Royal Canterlot voice
Ah ~ ~ ~
I scream but nopony hears me
I call but nopony answers
I'm drowned out by the noise
With my Royal Canterlot voice
I scream but nopony hears me
I'm drowned out by the noise
I call but nopony answers
With my Royal Canterlot voice