I see a cold wind's blowing through
I see days neither fun nor free
I see a future caused by you
I see a path not meant to be-e-e
The future should be filled with magic
Dreams and wishes brought to li-i-ife
But the days ahead are dark and tragic
No time for ho-ope when all is strife
Whatever might have been
All the dreams that po-onies share
Because of you, Snowfall Frost
Now the future is a cold nightma-are
Windigoes?
They aren't real!
It's just a little fillies' story
They are all too real, Snowfall
And your actions will allow them to return
The future of Equestria shall be bathed
In a blanket of eternal snow
No! I never meant for this to happen
I didn't understand!
I didn't see how important Hearth's Warming Eve was
Please spirit, I haven't cast the spell yet
Is there still time?
I'm sorry!